Chikishiki Gentenpapa!
Good afternoon.
What are we going to do today?
Today...
There was a long time ago.
What is it?
The corner of Gentenpapa.
Oh, I see.
One person.
A child came out.
Yes.
And he heard a lot of stories about his father.
I see.
And he drew a portrait.
Yes.
And his father came out.
And I draw the portrait.
Isn't that obvious?
I really wanted to draw a portrait.
Please take a look, Mr. Tezuka.
Yes.
Now, let's have the children come out.
Come out.
Please show the children the portrait.
Your father is Iwakashi Pot, isn't he?
From the Lion.
Please tell me your name.
I'm Kotaro.
Mr. Kotaro.
Have you ever been hit by your father?
Only once.
Only once?
When did your father hit you?
He hit me with his shoes.
At that time...
I thought my father was very strict.
Oh, your father hit you with his shoes.
Why?
Because he can't speak properly?
Your mother is a beautiful woman.
Yes.
I don't know you, but don't hit me.
I'm scared.
Please tell me your characteristics.
First of all, from the outline.
The face is long.
The body is long.
Well...
It's too long.
How does your hair look like?
Doesn't it look like you?
Yes.
Really?
Do you have a side hair?
Yes, I have a side hair.
Is your ear big?
How big is your ear?
It's long.
It's big.
Hey!
It's better to draw a big face.
How about eyebrows?
It's thick.
It looks like you, doesn't it?
The shape of your eyes...
It's different from the shape of your eyes.
It's eyebrows.
How about your eyes?
Is it perfect? Is it thin?
It's long.
It's thin and long.
I'm sorry. Can't you see it?
Is it thick?
Yes.
It's thick.
I'm sorry.
It's dangerous.
How about your nose?
It's long.
It's thick.
It looks like you, doesn't it?
How about your mouth?
It's thick.
It's like this.
And it's like your son's face.
Let's ask your father.
Please, father.
What's that?
It's like you.
Let's call him again.
Mr. Harada.
Your hair...
It's good.
You're in front of everyone.
It's beautiful.
I'm not confident.
You hit your back.
It's not like that.
It's long.
I'm not pretending.
I forgot the situation.
I was angry.
You were angry.
I was angry because it was important.
I said it out loud.
That's why I was angry.
I was a playboy.
Really?
I went to my work in high school.
It was fun.
You like going to work?
I like going to work.
When I went to work...
Call me Mr. Daisho.
Mr. Daisho?
I'm your father.
I called you Harada.
Harada, bring me a cigarette.
I said yes.
I didn't say anything at home.
When you go to work...
It's like saying now.
If you get angry, you'll get angry, right?
What about getting angry?
I get angry three times.
Hey!
I see.
Don't get angry.
Today, I'm going to ask Mr. Daisho a lot of questions.
I'd like you to answer them.
First question.
What do you want your father to fix here?
Pee?
Do you poop?
You poop as much as you poop.
It's pretty big.
There's no shape in your hair.
It's not a fart.
It's about appearance.
I got it.
I want you to be careful about your clothes.
Do you always wear casual clothes?
I don't wear casual clothes.
What?
It's pretty close.
The answer is...
I have a bad sense of fashion.
I thought it was a new drama.
The last question.
What do you think of Kotaro when you see your father on a variety show?
I think it's wonderful.
What?
You don't think so.
I only answered one question.
I feel sorry for him.
It's a little different.
It's a national opinion.
I got it.
It's a public opinion.
People draw.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Hello.
It's been a while since I've dressed up like this.
It's like a comic back.
I'm going to take a walk slowly today.
I'm sleepy.
It's not the time to talk cheerfully.
I sometimes watch the video and think.
It's strange if you're in a good mood.
It's strange if you're in a good mood at 1 o'clock in the middle of the night.
Let's sing a song.
It's like a lullaby.
Sing in the middle of the night.
You said you dropped your wallet last week.
Yes.
You dropped it again.
You dropped your wallet before, didn't you?
I dropped my wallet.
You bought it again, didn't you?
Yes.
You dropped it again.
I dropped it again.
I dropped it.
It was stolen.
I went to the parking lot with my friend.
It was 6 cents.
You left it open.
I left it open.
It was stolen.
What was stolen?
I think it was a fan.
It was stolen.
It's expensive.
What?
In a sense, it's very expensive.
Really?
Really.
Are you sad?
I'm very sad.
I want you to return it to me now.
It's pretty expensive.
It's expensive.
What?
There was a plastic bag in the back of the car.
Pants.
Are you kidding me?
What is that?
It was really stolen.
The pants I changed the day before.
Where did you change your pants in the car?
You changed your pants in the car a long time ago.
I didn't change my pants in the car.
You're lying.
I had a lot of clothes in the car.
I didn't change my pants in the car.
You changed your pants in the car.
I had the pants I changed the day before.
No.
I changed my pants today.
I like cars.
I don't know.
I was driving very hard.
My pants came off from here.
I put it in the back.
How did you change your pants?
You were wearing just one pair of pants.
I changed my pants to tie the side.
You're lying.
I didn't change my pants.
You changed your pants once.
I changed my pants once.
You were so dirty.
I was already dirty when I changed my pants.
Why?
He's so light.
Maybe I was really dirty.
It's because I have a bad anus.
Because I'm a homo.
Why?
Why do you use it?
It's the same as men.
What? What? What?
I don't know.
It's because I have a bad anus.
Because I have a bad anus.
I saw it.
What?
I don't know.
I think they are watching TV.
I'm sorry.
Don't cry.
I think you're a bad person.
If there is a talent you admire,
Do you want panty?
I think I have a chance.
That's what men think.
Women want men's panty.
Do you want panty?
I'm just saying.
What?
If there is no one,
I have panty.
I'm living alone.
I don't belong to any group.
Panty is all mine.
That's a great, father.
I have panty.
My terrifying panty.
I'm only wearing panty of aniki.
Then here's magic...
This already
You would know his love.
That's right.
How can he do this?
I've seen it, but I've never seen you wearing it.
You've never done such a thing.
What?
Everyone knows that you've stolen underwear.
You've stolen underwear, haven't you?
Yes.
You've worn those underwear, haven't you?
Just once!
You've been in a commercial, haven't you?
Good evening.
Tanaka Miyuki, you've done a lot of film reviews.
But you've done a lot of film reviews in front of me.
Who do you think you are?
I don't like movies.
What movies have you been moved by?
I've been moved by Spanish movies.
Spanish movies are not good at all.
You've never seen Spanish movies, have you?
I have.
What kind of Spanish movies have you seen?
What movies?
I'm asking you here.
What kind of Spanish movies have you seen?
I don't care about Spanish movies.
Are you serious?
I don't know Spanish movies.
What kind of Spanish movies have you seen?
Well, what did you do in Spain?
Think! Think!
A bright red Spain.
Thank you very much.
I don't like movies.
Did you see the commercial?
I did.
What did you see?
Everyone said they saw it.
For example, what did you see?
I saw everything, so I can't say anything.
Why can't you say anything?
If you saw it, you can say it.
I saw it.
What are you doing now?
Kagerou.
I saw Kagerou.
What?
Who is the main character?
That's it.
That was amazing.
What?
What are you asking?
Tell me the name.
Well,
George Shimaki was in the movie.
Is that so?
I'm asking about the main character.
It's George Shimaki.
What kind of role did George Shimaki play?
What?
He was very depressed.
Was he depressed?
George was depressed.
If you said you wanted to do this gag,
you were really in the movie.
That's enough.
I was your assistant.
Thank you very much.
I'll go from here.
There's this.
Matcha's burdock.
Matcha's burdock, an alkaline fiber food.
There's something like this.
It's not a big deal.
I'm your assistant.
Thank you very much.
Sometimes,
I see Matsumoto taking off his pants.
Do you have a reason?
What do you think?
I use this kind of thing a lot.
My butt has been sticking out a lot.
Is that so?
It's sticking out a lot.
You can see my butt, right?
If my butt was on the road.
Yes.
Probably.
Right?
Yes.
Matsumoto's butt is sticking out.
If my butt was on the road,
I would think,
when will Hamada deliver it to me?
I thought about it after watching the punishment game.
I think that punishment game is too bad.
Why?
What will Matsumoto do if he catches a cold?
The people watching are embarrassed by that.
The game is related to sports,
so Matsumoto doesn't seem to win.
Try using your head next time.
Then I think both will be the same.
It's too bad.
This is strange.
The person who decided the punishment game is this person.
If you lose this time,
if you say,
let's do this punishment,
it's this person.
Even if you lose,
there's nothing to be sad about.
It's natural.
But,
I want you to think about one thing.
At that time,
I went to Nami, right?
Yes.
I was a man, right?
At that time,
you were doing something like,
go!
At that time,
even if I won that baseball,
if you go that far,
I won't hesitate,
I'll jump in without hesitation.
That's the kind of man I am.
It's annoying.
At that time,
you were doing something like...
What?
When I fell with a parachute,
why didn't you jump with me?
I jumped.
You didn't jump.
Didn't you fall in the cesspool?
Everyone doesn't know,
but I jumped.
When did you jump?
What?
You didn't jump.
I gently,
when you were in the main,
didn't stand out too much,
I jumped like this.
You didn't jump.
The camera just didn't cover it.
So,
next time,
I want you to think about
something you don't like.
I'll think about it.
Let's play a game together
and if I lose,
it's like,
unconditionally,
I'm going to be beaten up.
That's right.
If you do something
and you lose,
that's right.
The other day,
you said you wanted to do judo,
so I said I wanted to do judo,
but you threw me.
That's right.
But what's good about it?
What's good about it?
I can study
with my head.
I can't do math.
You're terrible.
Everyone was playing.
When we were in middle school,
when we were studying together,
you were playing in the sand.
You're stupid.
Or,
I'm going to solve
a drill in the first grade of elementary school.
Yes.
Let's try it.
In the first grade of elementary school,
it's a little too easy.
In the sixth grade of elementary school,
What?
It's hard.
That was good.
In the sixth grade,
it's a little hard.
In the sixth grade?
The society of sixth graders.
Society?
Yes.
What's the national language?
Kanji?
I don't know the Kanji.
If it's Kanji,
I can win.
Let's not talk about Kanji.
Let's talk about Zuko.
That's not good. You'll win.
You were pretty good at Zuko.
You were good at Toten-Pol.
I was really good at it.
You were good at Shogoku-Toten-Pol.
You threw me out in the middle, so you were good at Baba.
Don't you know?
I'm the one who can win.
Why?
That's dirty.
Think about it next time.
What do you mean by next time?
We were going to do something together.
What happened?
I have to think about it.
With Gyo-san?
Yes, with about 1000 people.
Let's do something that will make them cry.
Something that will make them cry?
Let's ask them to do something.
Let's do a puppet show.
What kind of puppet show?
Let's go somewhere like Machibiko House.
There's no such thing as Machibiko House.
Why?
Grandpas and grandmas took a bath together.
Don't you have that kind of sense?
Do you really think so?
I do.
Why do you want to wash your grandpa?
I don't want to wash him at all.
That's fine.
I want to be moved by him.
Are you stupid?
Have you ever seen a man who is moved by his grandpa?
I'm moved by him.
You should do it at home.
I can't do it at home.
Shut up.
I'll do it for you.
Wait a minute.
What?
Watch this.
I'll make you look like him.
I want to see it.
Me too.
What did you just say?
What?
The one that everyone does.
If you have an idea.
Who wants to participate?
This one.
What is this?
What do you mean by everyone?
That's right.
I'm the only one who can do it.
That's why I'm telling you to recruit.
You don't have to talk.
Are you listening?
It's been 10 years for me and Konmi.
I don't know if I can still do it.
Good evening.
So,
I'm going to do something with everyone.
I'm going to get ideas.
What kind of things do you want to do?
Have you decided on the number of people?
I think it's about 1,000 people.
If it's more than that, I won't have anything to do.
But,
1,000 people are the main characters.
We don't do much.
We basically sit in a chair.
I see.
You watch over them.
That's good.
That's right.
I'll say it again.
If we get it,
we'll watch the V-app in the studio.
I see.
It's like Kanji.
It's like Genki.
It's like Takeshi.
That's right.
It's not like Takeshi.
It's like Matsukaza.
That's enough.
I'm looking for ideas.
Please let me know.
Also,
please let me know if you have any questions.
Today,
the assistant is a normal person.
So,
I'm not going to waste your time.
See you next week.
Bye-bye.