It's the 50th anniversary of Shuku Seitan at Gaki no Tsukai Arai!
This is the Heipou no Ikiru Michi Quiz!
Heipou has lived through half a century this year.
This is the end of his life.
He has tried many things this time.
I'd like to give you a quiz from those.
Let me introduce the people who answered.
This is Mr. Hitoshi Matsumoto!
Is that what a quiz is all about?
I don't really want to know about Heipou.
If I could, I'd like to finish it without knowing.
Well, I'm sorry.
Next to me is Mr. Yosei Yamazaki!
The staff said it was really interesting.
I see.
I'm looking forward to it.
This is the person who knows Heipou.
That's what I was going to say.
I don't know if it will reach the audience.
I don't think it will reach the audience at all.
Thank you for today.
Next to me is Mr. Shodo Endo!
Well, it's been a while since I've had a good time.
I don't know anything.
And finally, Mr. Naoki Tanaka!
I've been doing Gaki for eight years.
It's the day I'm least interested in.
Well, let's have the main character appear!
The world's Heipou is here!
This program is brought to you by five sponsors.
Mr. Kaga Takeshi!
Let's do a endurance test to see how many seconds you can endure.
This man, who is turning 50 this year, doesn't even have a fraction of his posture.
Next, measure your height.
First of all, please take the height measurement.
No, you can't put that in.
No, I don't need that kind of nonsense.
It's cold!
By the way, in the profile he wrote himself...
Excuse me, my height is 160cm.
What is the truth?
It hurts!
Do it properly!
He said it hurt, but when he tried to lift it up a little higher, he saw the true nature of this man.
It hurts! You can't crush it like that!
Even if you try to deceive him...
It's 4cm, right?
No, it's not 4cm. It's 3.8cm.
Here we go!
Here's the question!
After this, Heipo will make an excuse for lying about his height.
What kind of excuse did he make? Please write it down.
The lie has been revealed!
What is this?
Hamada-san.
No, no, it's a parallel tattoo.
Just say it!
No, no, it's Shingi-kun again.
Please write it down!
The lie has been revealed!
What kind of excuse did he make?
What did he answer?
Matsumoto-san.
Everyone is deceiving me, right?
Like this.
I see.
Yamazaki-san.
It happens in the morning, right?
I see.
Endo-san.
Until yesterday, it was 160cm.
I see. It happens in the morning, right?
Tanaka-san.
56cm and 60cm are the same, right?
I didn't see it at all.
That happened while we were moving the location.
The height measurement is definitely wrong.
It's definitely wrong.
The height measurement?
The measurement of Onuma is wrong.
He hit it like this.
The height measurement is wrong.
It's definitely wrong.
What are you talking about?
It's okay.
The measurement of Onuma is wrong.
It can't be corrected by mistake.
The correct answer is that the measurement of Onuma is wrong.
The height measurement is wrong.
That's it.
Even now, you still think that Onuma is wrong.
That's right. Because it's around 160cm.
Without a doubt.
Komazawa Olympic Park.
This is where Heipo challenges the track.
He doesn't care about warming up for a high record.
First, he runs and jumps.
He challenges the 100cm height.
He clears it perfectly.
And the bar is 5cm higher.
He changes the record.
He clears Heipo perfectly.
The next is the 110m hurdle.
Here, a miracle happens to Heipo.
Ready.
Again.
You don't need that.
I didn't use anything.
You just stood up.
Here's the question.
After this, how many seconds did Heipo run the 110m hurdle?
Please write it down.
Please stop this.
This is a hard one.
Let's go.
Everyone, please show your answers.
Ready, go.
Amazing.
34 seconds, 50 seconds, 50 seconds, 1 minute.
Komazawa is the fastest.
I thought it would be anything.
I see.
50 seconds.
It's the 50th anniversary.
That's my opinion.
No, it's not.
It's not.
If Heipo runs it.
What?
I'm sweating.
You're sweating.
Ready, go.
You're slow.
I see.
This is good.
It hurts.
Are you going to retire?
Retire?
No way.
No.
It's not 50 seconds.
It hurts.
Look.
My left leg.
It hurts.
It would be bad if I didn't get it.
That's right.
It's scary.
What?
It's okay.
What's wrong with you?
The correct answer is,
He couldn't run the 100m hurdle.
We don't know Heipo yet.
We don't know.
I think he can do it.
It's true.
Let's go to the next question.
I'm going to pick up Zaito.
Pick up?
What do you mean?
I'm going to pick up three girls.
I'm scared.
In the city?
Heipo is going to pick up girls in front of Shinjuku Altamae.
What kind of technique will Heipo show us?
However,
It's been 20 minutes since the start.
There is no sign of a voice.
I don't know what to do now.
I don't care if you talk to the flow.
Which flow?
This way?
Either way is fine.
It's hard to do.
Why?
I'm in a situation where I want you to do it.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Really?
I'm going.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
What are you sorry for?
Are you waiting for me?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Heipo is not being treated at all.
What will happen after this?
Here's the question.
It's a quick question.
What happened to Heipo after this?
What happened?
What did you do?
Ayame.
I don't think it's a high-turn.
I'm too nervous.
I'm nervous and under pressure.
That's wrong.
What is it?
Ayame.
What did you do when your leg hurt?
That's wrong.
What did you do?
I was in pain.
I didn't tell anyone.
I went home.
That's impossible.
What is it?
I was drooling.
I don't think it's like that.
You're drooling.
I'm not drooling.
You're like a child.
What will you do?
I was drooling.
That's right.
Heipo is 40 minutes after the start of the interview.
I'm having a hard time.
The atmosphere is strange.
Grandma is making a strange call.
It's strange.
I'm having a hard time.
I can't do it.
It's not funny.
It's not funny that I'm doing it so casually.
That's funny.
Hello.
Are you going home?
Do you know what heipo is?
Have you ever seen it?
No.
Why?
Did you think it was Nanpa?
The reaction to the name is completely different.
Even though heipo failed to catch Nanpa,
If you use the word heipo of the child's use, you will be shocked.
That's what he said.
He suddenly changed his strategy.
He began to attack with the heipo of the child's use.
Hello.
Do you know what heipo is?
Have you ever seen it?
Don't you know me?
Not at all.
Sorry.
Hello.
Do you know what heipo is?
Don't you know?
Have you ever seen it?
Do you know what heipo is?
He suddenly changed his strategy.
Are you angry?
I don't know.
You haven't seen it, have you?
He suddenly changed his strategy.
Do you know what heipo is?
Don't you know?
It's not as interesting as you think.
I don't have anything in me.
That's why I can't do it.
I don't have any heipo in me.
I don't have anything in me.
The answer is, anyway, a lot of mistakes.
The correct answer is the child's use.
Please understand the heipo.
I really understood.
Are you a man who doesn't understand?
Next question, please.
From now on,
Is the amusement park a scream machine game?
We arrived at the Asakusa Hanayashiki.
This is the most at-home amusement park in Japan.
The heipo of the world is making a noise.
The staff is pulling me.
I arrived at the attraction I was looking for.
I can't believe it.
It's a space shot.
I'm scared.
I'm not really okay.
There's still a roller coaster.
That's the last thing I can do.
What is this?
I don't want to go up or down.
I can't believe it's an amusement park.
What is this?
I'm so angry.
Next question, please.
This is a quick-fire question.
After this, heipo is going to do something unexpected.
What did he do?
I don't know.
It's been 15 to 20 minutes, right?
Finally, the staff cut it off.
He was hit by a bottle.
He was hit by a bottle and got on it unexpectedly smoothly.
On the contrary, it was really cut off, wasn't it?
It's not a correct answer just because it's cut off.
What is it?
I reported it to Mr. Sura.
He's my friend.
He's cut off by a man who can win.
Is it a child?
That's right.
It's a lie, isn't it?
Next question, please.
I don't want to do it.
Why are you scaring me?
That child is scary.
I'm scaring you.
Let me go somewhere.
What are you doing?
You don't have to do it.
Child, get out of the way.
The correct answer is that he was cut off by a child.
By the way, after 20 minutes of heipo,
I don't want to do it anymore.
Then I'll do this.
I'll do this.
I don't want to do it.
I'm not scared.
I'm scared.
Next question, please.
Help me.
I'm scared.
What is it?
Do it again.
I don't want to do it anymore.
The correct answer is Yama-chan.
You don't have any words, do you?
When the child was cut off by a boy,
he was screaming.
I wanted to see it again.
Why are you scaring me?
Next question.
Commercial.
Let's go to the second half.
What kind of pattern is this?
Let's end it soon.
Matsumoto got 10 points.
Yamasaki also got 10 points.
The top is Yamasaki Hosei.
Let's go.
What's in the box?
Quiz.
You can't guess the word and that's how you get right.
You will get points So let everyone get a chance.
Now, please guess the word.
Scary.
As soon as game starts,
you write what了 is.
Please write as much as you can
Anything is fine
Here you go
Let's start with Matsumoto
Matsumoto was aiming for a sweet habit of the Heipo
On the other hand, Yamasaki wrote Hamada
The two of them answered a lot
By the way, Matsumoto, Yamasaki, and Tanaka
All three of them are giving the name of the director of Onoma
Who will get the Heipo?
What's inside the box?
Heipo start
I don't know
I don't like it
I haven't touched it yet
Up and down?
Nothing has started
Something came out
Something came out?
It's supposed to be there
I touched it
Nothing came out
Is it moving?
I don't know
Something came out
No way
It's better to put it in
Put it in
Something came out
What's this?
It's a living thing
It's going to die
It's going to bite
What?
It's going to bite?
You are scary
I don't like it
Do you have anything else to say?
Say something else
I don't like it
I'm scared
Help me
Mom
Touch it
I'm scared
Mom, help me
Let's do it together
You shouldn't have told me
Something came out
I don't like it
It's going to die
Something came out
Look inside the box
I don't like it
Let's see what you got
What about you?
I got a lot
I didn't say anything
You got 7
What about you?
I got 5
You got 5?
Yes
I said my name
You said your name
I got 6
You got 6
Amazing
What about you?
I got 3
You got 3
Let's see the total score
80, 70, 60, 40
The winner is Matsumoto
Congratulations
But you will get something
It's a special jumper
Special jumper?
Yes, for the winner
What is it?
Heipo
How was it today?
Did you get to know more about Heipo?
Yes, I got to know more about him
I said on TV that I was scared of old men in their 50s
But you called me a mother
I was surprised
You shouldn't say that
This program was brought to you by these sponsors