Let's buy a lot of Chikitsuki at the first Gaki no Tsukai line!
What is Chikitsuki?
If you turn this paper over, you can definitely race in a tricycle.
There is no doubt.
Today, from this Kinshicho.
I'm glad to see you again.
Let's buy a lot of Chikitsuki at the opening today.
I'll give you a cheema.
Yes.
10,000 yen.
Take this 10,000 yen and buy 10 kg of things.
Buy 10 kg of things?
Yes, 10,000 yen.
I wonder if there is a woman of 10 kg.
It doesn't mean that.
Let's buy a lot of Chikitsuki!
Start!
Let's go!
There are a lot of things here.
How many kg is this?
What are you talking about?
It's 10,000 yen!
What is this?
Can you sell this for 10,000 yen?
There is a frog on the front, right?
Can you sell that for 10,000 yen?
This frog.
No, it's not for sale.
It's not for sale?
It's not for sale.
Where did the toy shop go?
Takoyaki is also good.
I don't even have 300 yen.
I'll take a picture of your lonely back.
You are late.
What?
You said 15 minutes, but it took 30 minutes.
This program is brought to you by
Sanraku
Oyama International Products
and the sponsor of this program.
10 kg for 10,000 yen.
What did you buy?
What is this?
I bought a tempura of squid.
You are over 10,000 yen.
Do you have a change?
A change?
5,000 yen.
Why do you have so much money?
What is it?
10,000 yen.
I thought it would be better to have a lot of money.
Do you have a receipt?
I don't have it.
You can't.
Why?
You can't get a receipt on Japanese TV.
You don't have it.
You bought it yourself.
I like it very much.
Really?
What is it?
Cat sand.
It's a plush toy.
You don't need it.
Why?
I'll go.
Shrimp tempura.
It's an expensive thing.
What is it?
Cat sand.
I bought this.
What is it?
Peach tree.
What?
I bought it for a sponsor.
But I still have money left.
So I bought this from my sponsor, Sanraku.
I bought this one.
I have 40 yen left.
Do you want to use this?
It's a snack.
It's good, isn't it?
I lost 10 yen.
Stop it.
You can't move it.
I don't know why I was late.
But this guy suddenly asked me.
It's a Japanese horse.
I can't catch it.
A Japanese horse?
It's a Japanese horse.
It's hard to catch it.
You can't move it.
I'm serious.
Wait a minute.
It's 100 kg.
It's 10 kg.
It's up to here.
How much does it weigh?
It feels good.
It's 7.5 kg.
It's 9.5 kg.
Wait a minute.
You can't move it.
It's 9.5 kg.
It's a snack.
It's a dry gun.
I don't need it.
It's going to hit you.
It might hit me.
Do you want to try it?
Don't step on it.
It's 10 kg.
It's the worst to weigh more than 10 kg.
I weigh more than 10 kg.
Don't throw it away.
Here we go.
It's not heavy at all.
Look.
What?
It's 6 kg.
It's a big deal.
Here we go.
All right.
Look.
It's not heavy at all.
It's heavy.
It's going somewhere.
It hurts.
It's not going to work anymore.
It's 10 kg.
I wish I only had two of these.
My face is so heavy.
Look.
It's heavy.
My weight is 11kg.
That means I win.
It says 5kg.
You are 11kg and I am 10kg.
I ate fish on the way here.
Fish?
My stomach is full.
I want to win.
Thank you very much.
Rocking!
It has started.
This is the second video of Nihon-dori.
You know the opening song.
I am a little tired.
The audience is changing.
It is the first time to see the audience.
What is wrong with you?
There are people who come to watch this program and those who do not.
That is not true.
Please tell them that the paper has been published.
What are the rest of the people?
I do not know.
I want to see it.
Come to see it.
I do not recognize downtown as a comedian.
I am a fan of Utopia.
You are off work now.
I have to make people laugh.
What do people think when they come home?
They say it was funny.
I have a microphone.
I want to hear it.
I put it in the audience's seat.
What is this?
I put it in the back of the microphone.
It was more boring than I thought.
Why did you kick it?
I do not know.
I do not know if it was funny.
What is this?
I came to Tokyo.
I am used to it.
There was an earthquake the other day.
It was about 4 degrees.
Do not you know?
It is...
That's right.
The earthquake in Tokyo is normal.
I am used to it.
It's nothing.
There is no earthquake in Osaka.
There is no earthquake.
When we were having a party, everyone was screaming,
and I was like, are you shaking?
What kind of a person are you?
Well, Osaka people aren't used to that kind of thing.
That's true, it was a long time.
It was a long time.
And it was big.
I thought there was a big difference between the people of Tokyo and Osaka.
I wonder if the people of Tokyo,
in the earthquake,
took advantage of the shaking and went to sleep.
There's that kind of thing, right?
I'm not an old man.
I wonder if the people of Tokyo have guts.
What is it?
I don't know.
I think there's a saying,
the taste of Tokyo is stupid.
You eat it looking delicious, right?
I eat anything looking delicious.
Even if it's a thick udon,
I eat it like, haaa.
Even if it's a black udon.
That part is a little...
It's black, right?
I think it's a little strange.
Tokyo people and Osaka people still have a long way to go.
If you use Osaka dialect,
everyone thinks it's a manzai.
That's it.
If you go from Tokyo to Osaka to play,
and take the train,
Osaka people just talk normally.
They say, something happened the other day.
They say it's like a manzai.
Even when I used to work in Tokyo,
I didn't know anyone like that.
But when I went somewhere,
they said it's like a manzai.
It's a manzai, though.
Let's go to Haragi.
Huh?
You're pretty good.
I want to take a picture.
I took it before.
What are you doing?
Who told you to take a picture?
I'll give it to you later.
I took a picture.
It's not bad.
Let me introduce you.
This is Odawara, who loves matcha.
It's a little strange.
There's something I've been wanting to talk about.
It's about Matcha's real name.
My friend told me that
Matcha's name is Yukinojo.
At first, I didn't believe it.
But in the TV series,
Ran-chan called Matcha Yukinojo-niisan.
I think it's true.
I want you to hear it from Matcha's mouth.
Do you think I'm Yukinojo?
Huh?
My name is...
What is it?
My name is Hitoshi Matsumoto.
Again, you...
I'm Hitoshi Matsumoto.
I'm a parent.
You may have a child.
I don't know.
If you give me a name, I won't give it to you.
I don't like it.
Your name...
I saw you on TV in Osaka.
I asked you to give me a name.
You said, Dokuro Nisei.
Is there such a name?
I asked you to give me a name.
Like, Cantama.
Cantama...
I'm serious.
I don't like it.
Why do you say such a thing?
I want to give you a name.
I'll recruit you in this program.
Let's play with your child.
What?
Let's go this way.
Pen name...
What is this?
Mary Fuji.
Good evening, two brothers of Mamushi.
Good evening.
Mr. Hamada went to a high school in Zenryosei.
Moreover, he went to Fukuryocho.
Did you have any big event in your mind?
I was living in a dormitory.
That's right.
I want you to listen to the story of that time.
This is something you can't experience.
Living in a dormitory in high school.
Have you ever run away?
I hate it.
You are really bad-tempered.
I didn't run away.
I couldn't go home when I had to go home.
I hate it.
I woke up at 4.30 in the morning.
Didn't you run away?
No, I didn't.
Then why didn't you come to my house to get money?
Why is it so hard to live in a dormitory?
I woke up at 4.30 in the morning.
It was dark.
I was on the top of the mountain.
It was below zero.
I opened the refrigerator.
It was as cold as the temperature inside the refrigerator.
You woke up at 4.30 in the morning,
put on your jersey and cleaned the room.
If I had studied a little more in junior high school,
I would have been able to go to a normal school.
Normal?
That's why your parents...
You were abandoned by your teachers.
You were abandoned by your teachers in junior high school.
The teachers who guided you on your path
said, where should we decide?
Should we make it a straight line?
You can accept the efficiency here,
but if you make it a flat surface,
you can stop it from slipping.
When I was wondering,
he didn't say anything.
He did.
I talked about it properly.
It's over.
When everyone was talking about their path,
his teacher came and said,
Hamada,
this is about school.
What are you going to do?
Are you going to work?
Are you going to get a job?
Hamada said something.
I don't know what he said.
It's not a story I made up.
Hamada came and said,
Hamada, are you brushing your teeth?
Everyone was like,
when are you going to sit down?
It's yellow here.
I was told that,
Hamada,
I've been thinking about you for a long time.
You should think about me first.
This is from Gunma.
We did a survey last time.
The target is,
downtown, B21 special,
Uchan Nanchan.
The target is these members.
If you make them your lover,
1st place, Uchimura Mitsuyoshi.
I know.
Why?
What?
2nd place.
I watch this every week.
You watch it every week.
1st place, Uchimura Teruyoshi.
2nd place, Matsumoto Hitoshi.
You guys are honest.
3rd place, Hiromi.
I don't like it.
4th place, Chin.
What about me?
5th place, David.
There is no one below.
So,
Nanchan and Hamada are not included.
If you make them your lover.
I see.
I'll look forward to the next one.
Please look forward to the next one.
Chinpira looks good on you.
Liar.
It's true.
1st place, Hamada Mitsuyoshi.
I did it.
And,
Hiromi, Nanchan, me.
They are included.
And, who has a good personality?
Yes.
1st place, Uchimura Teruyoshi.
I don't like it.
Is that so?
2nd place,
Matsumoto Hitoshi.
That's not true.
Chin is also included.
I know Chin.
Chin has a good personality.
Right?
Why are you 2nd place?
Are you weird?
Did you write it?
Did you see my bad personality?
What?
I'll tell you a story.
Every month,
I send money to my parents' house.
Of course.
If you earn a lot, you will send money.
Do you send money?
Of course.
What are you talking about?
How much do you send?
I don't care about money.
What about 3rd place?
3rd place is David.
He has a good personality.
That's right.
And, he has a bad personality.
1st place, Hiromi.
I know it.
We are together.
2nd place,
Hamada Masatoshi.
I applaud you.
3rd place, Kiyotaka Nambara.
I don't care about money.
Why?
What?
I want to ask you a proper questionnaire.
Really?
Yes.
I want a proper questionnaire.
You guys do it.
Osaka people are amazing.
In a TV program, there were 50 people who pressed the switch.
Yes.
When we did that,
We did a thorough investigation.
Yes.
There were about 35 people out of 50 who wanted to have sex with me.
Let's do it in a TV program.
It will cost a little money.
Let's do a thorough investigation.
I want to ask you a lot of questions.
There is an adult video.
If it is 1 million yen, can I appear in it?
There were about 10 people.
If it is 2 million, I can't appear.
I want to ask if it is money.
I want to ask you to do a costume for the grand prize.
We can do a costume.
Thank you.
We will go to the audition.
Yes.
We will participate in the bird contest.
I will fly in a plane.
Of course, I'll fly.
Of course, you'll fly.
No wonder, this girl is called P-chan.
It's okay.
Well, that's all for tonight.
That's all for tonight.
Yes.
Thank you very much, everyone.
Well, it was difficult, wasn't it?
It was difficult, wasn't it?
What?
Ah, shopping, right?
That's right.
But, if you want to spend 10,000 yen in 15 minutes, it's difficult even if you say it's expensive.
Well, you bought a stuffed cat, didn't you?
I bought it.
You bought it, didn't you?
That...
I'm lucky.
You bought it again, didn't you?
That's for the viewers of the TV.
If you want it, I'll think about the program.
Because you're always asking for something like that.
I said my name.
What about the sand? The cat sand?
The cat sand...
Well, I don't know what to do.
Well, if you want it, it's okay.
Yes.
But, it costs money to send it.
Well, I don't know what to do.
Hey.
lt's...
l want to hold his hand.
This...
I received the advice from my advisor,
He thought about an idea and made decisions.
I'm looking forward to it.