In the 1st episode of Gaki no Tsukai Arahen, Chikichiki Telekura Daisakusei!
What's up?
We're in a store called Uiz in Ikebukuro.
Even though it was popular a while ago, it's still booming.
If you really make a promise, it'll come true.
Everyone can feel that with their own skin.
This is different from the usual opening.
It's totally different.
The staff is like a tracking staff.
You're so good!
Please come in and let's do a challenge.
Please come in!
Yamada-kun, you're coming in too?
Do your best.
Masato-kun.
Actually, this monitor...
The height of the 4th room...
That room is being filmed.
I'm setting up a hidden camera.
Of course you don't know the height.
I don't know.
Actually, I asked a girl to call Takasukun.
I asked her to make an appointment with me.
I like you.
I like you too.
I think Takasukun will be quiet.
I think he'll meet that girl.
I see.
That's what I asked the tracking staff to do today.
You're a pervert.
The other members...
I don't really know Takasukun, but...
I think he'll meet that girl today.
That's what I think.
So, Aoshima-san and Chika Takami will do the VTR.
That's right.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
I won.
Where are you?
Where do you live?
Where I live?
I'm in Otsuka.
Otsuka?
Yes.
I see.
You know a lot.
What are you talking about?
Right now?
My company is closed today.
I was told to call you, so I'll call you.
Really?
Do you call often?
Not that often.
You're asking a lot of questions.
Do you talk to everyone?
I'm in Otsuka.
Minamiguchi?
Yes.
I see.
I understand.
Really?
Yes.
I'm in Otsuka.
Really?
Minamiguchi.
I'm in Otsuka.
I'm alone.
Oh, you?
I'm sorry.
I'm still working hard.
Seriously.
You're amazing.
Who do you look like?
You're cool.
Who?
Taishu Kase.
You're so funny.
You're funny.
Do I really look like you?
I don't think so.
You're cool.
Don't say my name.
I'm just so happy to hear it.
You're coming?
Yes.
She's not coming?
You're funny.
Are you at home.
Yes.
Around 10?
Let's meet somewhere at 10.
You said that we were meeting at 8.
It's not 10 o'clock, is it?
Well, you know...
I'd like to meet you, but...
I might be lying, but...
I used to be a fan of yours.
By the way, I...
Well...
I can't meet you at 10 o'clock.
It's okay.
Do you know where the station is at 10 o'clock?
Yes.
What are you going to wear?
I'm going to wear a white polo shirt and a navy skirt.
I'm going to wear a navy skirt and a navy skirt.
You're definitely coming, aren't you?
I'm going. I'm going.
Yes.
I'm definitely coming.
I'm waiting for you.
All right.
Now, let's report the results of the test.
I'm the only one.
One?
How old are you?
I'm 21 years old.
You must have been nervous.
162 years old.
In college.
I'm 21 years old.
How many tests did you take?
I took three tests.
I'm the only one.
I'm the only one. At 8 o'clock.
I'm sorry.
How did you do it?
I'm the only one.
You're really the only one.
And you said you'd be waiting for me at 8 o'clock on the show.
10 o'clock.
I have to wait until 4 o'clock.
What?
In front of Osaka Station.
Was it Minamiguchi?
Yes.
I'll go now and see if there's anyone waiting for me.
All right.
I'll go.
Good luck.
Welcome back.
What about you, Takasu?
I didn't have enough time.
I didn't ask.
I see.
It can't be helped.
Good luck.
There he is.
He's white.
He's white, so I can see what's going on.
There he is.
He's a fool.
I'm making him fool around.
How many tests did you take?
I took 21 tests.
21 tests?
He's talking.
I'm asking for your name.
My name is Tomo.
Tomo.
He's talking to someone I know.
He's desperate to find me.
It's perfect.
He's a fool.
He looks like Tsukou-san.
I'm waiting for you, old man.
His knees are shining.
I'm not surprised at all.
I'm really impressed.
I'm not surprised.
He's really big.
I'm going to open up a strike zone for you.
You can take a break.
We can play.
What are you talking about?
You can take a break.
We can play.
We can take a break.
You can take a break.
You're a fool.
Even if I come out that way, they'll definitely be able to see me from here.
I can come in that way.
It's over there, isn't it?
There's a person on the 4th floor.
He's trying to go over there.
I can't go over there.
How is it?
I'm going to go there.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I don't think he'll come out.
You don't think he'll come out?
That's a swear word.
I'm asking you.
It's hard to pull more than that.
I don't think he'll come out.
That's what I'm talking about.
That's what you're talking about.
You don't think he'll come out?
I don't think so.
That's a swear word.
Let's look over there.
Which way?
From over there.
That's not it.
Let's wait a little longer.
I don't think he'll come out.
That's a swear word.
It's definitely this way.
This is the first time I've seen this kind of thing, so I'm not sure if it's a good idea or not, but I think it's a good idea to try it out and see how it goes.
I'm not sure if it's a good idea to try it out and see how it goes, but I think it's a good idea to try it out and see how it goes.
However, this is a horrible thing, so it's probably okay.
It's a little bit difficult to see.
I'm sorry.
What does it mean?
Do you know Takahashi?
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
Ouch!
No way!
That's for sure!
I've never seen anyone with that face.
I'm not eating this!
I'm on the other side of the road.
What's wrong with you, Takatsu-san?
Takatsu-san!
Stop it!
Why did you say that?
That's not cool.
All the voices are here.
Come here! Come here!
You're crying, aren't you?
Yeah, my eyes are a bit dirty.
Ah, I can't take this anymore.
Usually, people who ride a horse that much and go home are usually lonely.
Why is this happening to me?
I've been tricked!
The camera is here, so face the camera.
1, 2, 3, go!
Stop it! Stop it! Let's go home!
Thank you very much! Thank you very much!
Thank you very much!
Well, you know...
I'm sure you're all doing well.
That's right.
Well, you know, everyone, this program,
I think we've had quite a few meetings.
Ah, probably.
Really, you guys, you have to show yourself.
Show what?
The golf story before the actual show.
What?
What is it?
What are you guys doing?
It's not like we have a meeting on this program.
We don't have one, but it's like,
what's going on over there?
This has nothing to do with it!
It's annoying!
Well, we have a lot of staff,
so if you want to come in,
we can have a downtown party.
We can have a competition,
with all the staff.
But you can't come in!
You can't do anything!
You can't do that!
You can't!
Okay, I get it.
If you want to put that kind of ball in the hole,
I've put in as many balls as you want!
I've put a lot of balls in the box!
That's enough!
But, you know,
putting it in like this isn't fun.
It's more fun to sell it and put it in.
I've put in a lot of balls.
If this feels good,
you don't have to put it in from a distance.
You can just run and put it in.
Yes, yes!
That's the most fun!
If that's the case,
I'll go out once.
I can still accept tennis.
I'm good at tennis.
Seriously.
Why can't you say that?
I can use both hands.
I don't need the opposite hand.
You don't need this?
If you don't have a backhand, you don't have it.
If you come from this side, you can take it to this side.
Don't say such a good thing!
Try putting in balls.
If you come like this, you can put it in like this.
Do you have the will to do it?
You can't even make a mistake!
Let's play next time.
Let's play.
We can do an opening.
That's right.
So stop playing golf.
It doesn't matter.
Leave me alone.
You all like baseball, right?
I like baseball too.
Baseball is stupid.
I don't think baseball is as cool as it is when it's sandwiched.
It's lame!
That's because it's in the back of the net.
It's sandwiched between the ball going this way and going that way.
You can't run away from it.
It can't be helped.
What does the ball actually mean?
What do you mean by that?
The beginning of baseball is...
I don't know if you know about the ball, but I'm going to make a bomb statement here.
What does the baseball ball actually mean?
It's about poop.
The beginning is poop.
Did you know that?
It's a story from an era when baseball wasn't even a thing.
One day, Mela Rekko threw poop.
It was dirty, so she hit it back with a stick.
That's how baseball started.
That's definitely a lie.
It's true!
That's why she threw poop and it ended up like this.
She threw poop and it was dirty, so she ran away.
That's right. That's the beginning.
That's not true!
If you follow the original shape of sports, it's really embarrassing.
What else is there in sports?
There's a lot of sports.
Swimming.
What?
Why are you desperately swimming?
Originally, humans were fish.
What?
Huh?
You don't know?
No, I don't know.
Before monkeys, they were fish.
What kind of fish were they?
They were mackerel.
They were mackerel?
From mackerel, they became monkeys.
What?
What do you mean?
Their faces are completely different.
That's right.
How did they evolve?
They were monkeys, and they had this kind of face.
So mackerel swim like this.
And there was a guy who wanted to go out.
He wanted to go up to the land.
One of the mackerels thought that.
There were so many unpleasant things.
In the sea?
There were so many unpleasant things in the sea.
It was boring.
That's right.
Go up!
That's why he wanted to swim.
I don't agree with that.
You can't do this as a joke.
If you go up to the land now, you'll be a monkey.
Please stop playing golf.
That's all I ask of you.
That's great.
Let's go once.
What?
Once.
You can't do that.
I'll do it.
Let's go once.
Hey!
I've told you so many times.
You can't do that.
How much money does he have?
I don't have money except for you.
The staff gave me a lot of money.
But you're the only one.
You're like a child who did something bad.
What?
That's not true.
I'm not like that.
I'm not a person who was born with sex.
I'm telling you clearly.
Really?
That's right.
How did you come into this world?
What are you talking about?
Me?
Who are you?
I'm an angel.
Are you that kind of person?
Do you always have wings?
That's okay.
Show me.
Show me now.
Your wings.
Show me your wings.
If you want to show your wings, you have to fly.
You can fly.
You can only fly.
It's okay.
I'm an angel.
Your butt is round.
That's not cool.
You can fly, but you can't show your wings.
If you show your wings, your butt will be round.
That's an angel.
Your pants are open.
Your pants.
Your butt is round and you have wings.
I want to see it someday.
You want to see it someday?
Yes.
I want to fly at the opening.
Look outside.
If you fly outside, you can fly freely.
But you can't turn the camera.
Why?
Because the radio is round.
I'll blur it.
That's not cool.
You blur the angel wings.
How do you show your wings?
That's an angel.
It's romantic.
Can you show your wings like this?
It's cute.
You're an angel.
Really?
How do you show your wings?
Like this.
It's scary.
Matsumoto.
Yes.
Today's opening was great.
Takasu's dirtiness.
That guy.
He's here.
How long have you been working with him?
I've been working with him for 20 years.
He's a tough guy.
He kept quiet.
He didn't tell me anything.
The guy who usually rides your car and goes home.
He's not here today.
What are you talking about?
What did he do?
He's alone.
You're lying.
Takasu, you look like Taishu Kaze.
Assistant.
Everything is the same.
What kind of writing do you want?
I'll be waiting.
I'll wash your armpits.
Goodbye.
I'm surrounded by amazing staff.
Thank you.