Next time on Gaki no Tsukai, Tsukitsuki!
Ameagari! Miyasako Shihengen!
What's up, Haruki?
You're here!
Last time, my partner, Hotarohara-kun, completely slipped
No, it was an accident
I'm glad it was an accident, but to be honest, I don't remember what I did
You were 4th place
That's true, but I don't remember what I did
There were a lot of things
Today, it's Aikata
Aikata!
Last time, Miyasako said, looking at Hotarohara-kun, that he was pathetic
Yes, he said that he was pathetic
Today, I really did my best
What are you talking about?
Today, I really did my best to get back at him
You're acting strange
He looked like Yomi from Babylon 2
Your bear is amazing!
Did you sleep well?
No, I was shaking and I didn't sleep at all
This program is brought to you by these sponsors
What are you doing?
There's a lot of stuff
This is a high tension festival with a lot of people
Will there be a lot of people?
Of course there will be
There's a lot of live performances
Personally, I want to do this
Don't do that
What happened to Tanaka's car?
I'll be there soon
Really?
Yes
If I can drive a Ferrari
You bought it?
I bought it
It's a serve
I like serve
What should I do? Fuji Safari Park
It's really a lion
What should I do? It's so cute
What should I do? Fuji Safari Park
That was good
That was a bad start
It was a bad start
That was cowardly
I'll never laugh again
What will you do then?
Are you going to record it?
I don't think I'll come
I'll just do it
I'm hungry
Thank you for the food
Thank you
Did you do it?
I don't know why
I can't see the story
This is bad
This is really bad
I'll never laugh
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 1
1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6
Everybody put in
Yama-imo
Sato-imo
Please don't put it directly on fire
Takashima Homiri
Ah, it's the end of the pay
It's the end of the pay
Why is it the end of the pay?
It's the end
It's the end of the pay
No, this is the first one
Count it
I didn't say it
Tanaka Mamota
26,000 yen
It's 3rd place
3rd place
Ohtomo lost
It's 3rd place
This was good from the beginning
Everybody put in
It's the end
It was good
How was it?
I thought if I did it in the first try, I would be able to get rid of the tension
What?
Miyasako did it like this?
...
Yōkan Usai wa Nakayoshi da
Itsumo Futari de Mitsuyōkan
Yōkan no Dana
Yōkan no Yame
Yoru wa Kuri Yōkan
Yōkan no danna wo sekurishan
Ate kono te te mameyo
Oh, that's not good
Yōkan no danna
Yōkan no yome
Dana wa ume yōka
That means he's sick, right?
I like you, I like you when I think about you
If you die, I'll die too
If I think about you, I'll think about you and then I'll die
Ihi kanitama
Yōkan futsai wa tetsurinda
Ikumo betto de mushi yōkan
Yōkan no danna
Yōkan no yome
Kyō mo kuri yōkan
I think I get it now
Thank you
Amazing
But this is only for today
Well...
I told you before the show
It won't sell
I thought it would sell
It's been a while since we talked
That's right
We haven't talked for a long time
We've been doing a lot of things
But we have a new challenge
What is it?
It's a macho plan
It's progressing step by step
My neck is going to get fat this summer
It's going to get thicker than the width of my face
Your neck?
My neck
It's going to go up from here
It's going to be like raitan
What?
It's going to be like gold raitan
I see
What are you doing today?
What are you talking about?
I don't get it
It's going to be like that
I'm going to try my best
You don't have to say it
Just do it
It's been a while since I did it
I don't do it often
I can only do it 20 times
You can only do it 20 times?
I can't do it even once
What does that mean?
It's like the day before
Muscle pain?
They say I can't do it anymore
I see
I can't do it anymore
I'll do it again
I'm going to do this too
But I can't do it at home
Why don't you go to the gym?
It's kind of cool
Why?
It's like I'm desperate
I'm going to do it
Everyone is desperate
I don't want people to see me with black hair
Black hair?
It's black hair
I see
I think so
I don't want people to see me with black hair
I see
I want people to see my nipples
even if I'm facing forward
It's going to be around your illnesses
It's like a muscle
Even if I do this, I feel like I have a nipple around here
That's just a muscle
Near춰
I can't do that
I'm thinking of it
I do think I can do it next week
It's fast
I don't really fit
I see
What's easier to stick to?
Like a spirit?
I don't know that.
Muscles.
Ah, muscles.
Why did you say it twice?
I said it twice.
It's easier to stick to, right?
That's what my grandfather used to say.
A little stronger.
My family is a family of muscles.
This is not that effective.
It hurts a little.
Ah, muscles.
It's in the body.
I see.
It doesn't seem to say that much.
Ah, right.
It seems to be from Osaka.
That it's in the body.
It's a muscle pain.
It hurts, right?
It's in the body.
M...
It's M.
It's in the body.
It seems to be related to the your body.
Do you know?
I don't know if you're from Tokyo or not, but there are many types of Osaka dialects that have the same meaning.
There's only one standard word for it.
I think that vocabulary is the best.
They're not from Tokyo.
Most of them are from the countryside.
You like that, don't you?
You like catching people and telling them about the countryside, don't you?
Telling them about the countryside and telling them about the rules is weird.
What are you saying?
Well, that's how it is.
The Golden Week was amazing, wasn't it?
I was surrounded by Niigata and Iwate.
The cars?
That's how it was.
I see.
I recently found out what it was.
It was a firecracker.
The firecracker was amazing the other day.
He's an idiot.
If you turn on the engine, the firecracker will come out.
Don't mess with me!
That's not how you turn it off.
It's not complete yet.
What do you mean?
If you pretend you're on a high-speed train and you can't get on it, it means you're on a high-speed train.
You're not getting on it!
You're on top of it!
That's what happens when you get off the high-speed train.
You're getting off!
That's not good.
It's good, but not good.
You're slow.
What do you mean?
You have to keep the speed limit.
Because your grandmother can't handle it.
Your grandmother is in the train.
When you reach 60km per hour, your grandmother is like,
She's like,
I'm almost there!
She's already got it on her.
She's like,
Your grandmother, your grandma, is like,
What do you want me to do?
I'm looking at you from above.
I don't know if you're on a high-speed train or not.
You should look at me from the side.
I'm serious, so I'm looking at you from above.
I'm going to fall from the side.
Where are you from?
I'm from Kumamon.
I'm from Aobahanna.
You!
You have countless scars all over your body.
What is the first scar you have on your body?
How many scars do you have?
Do you know how many stitches I have on my body?
If I add up all the stitches I have on my body,
I can make two G-Pants.
Basically, how many G-Pants do you have on your body?
I don't know.
But you don't have any scars on your body.
I'm a talent.
I want to protect my face.
You want to protect your face and the woman you're in love with.
Where are you?
My back is flat.
Flat?
Is your back the biggest?
I think my back was the biggest.
How wide is it?
I've gone wide.
What? All of this?
I think I can put in dumplings.
Wait, wait, wait.
Why did you make a mistake?
It's your back.
It's definitely not dumplings.
Wait, wait, wait. What are you doing?
I'm just saying.
Your back is flat.
And you said that you've gone wide.
Why did your back get flat?
That was amazing.
I was just saying.
You went wide.
Let me explain.
It was really bad.
It was two times worse than Tokyo Dome.
Over there, they had a cutter knife.
It was amazing when I noticed.
What do you mean you noticed?
I was there too.
I said it.
Why?
From here.
I'll tell you an interesting story from here.
I work part-time at a rental video store.
I'm having a hard time paying attention to customers who don't return the money.
Please tell me how to pay attention to customers.
I'll definitely return the money.
Wait, wait, wait.
What do you think?
Actually, it's best to tell him to return the money.
But he's probably weak-willed.
I can't tell him.
So you should be able to tell him on the phone.
I see.
Please tell him that.
Then you go and return the money.
Yes.
Excuse me.
Please be careful.
You're not returning the money.
If you want to tell him that, you have to do this.
I think he's laughing.
But the stroke is short.
You have to make it longer.
I'll clean this up.
Excuse me.
Yes.
This is...
Excuse me.
Yes.
Please return the money.
It's cold.
Why didn't you tell me?
I didn't see the video.
Why?
I forgot.
I want to rewind that.
Happy birthday to you.
When was the last time you were on this show?
The second time.
The second time you were on this show.
You have to tell him.
I see.
Yamaguchi-san.
Yamaguchi-san is going to say happy birthday in English.
In English.
I see.
Thank you.
Everyone, please tilt your glass.
Please hold the glass.
Please say happy birthday in English.
Please.
Look.
This is...
This program was brought to you by these sponsors.