Ladies and gentlemen.
Hello.
Today is a little different from usual.
Mr. Uraigyou is here.
Today is a little more than usual.
Today is a special.
There are about 20 people more than usual.
It doesn't change at all.
There are a lot of people from Tokyo.
About 5 out of 20 are Filipinos.
It's almost the same.
Today is an hour.
I can't use the children today.
It's a special.
If it's a special, I'll use a little more money.
It's exactly the same.
It seems that the most expensive thing today is the venue fee here.
It seems to be quite expensive here.
No, it's not.
There is only one board.
I'm glad to hear that.
There are usually three, but today there are four.
There is a special under downtown.
Anyone can make it.
It's a special.
I'll tell you this.
It's usually at 1 pm on Tuesday nights.
It's 40 minutes.
I've been told.
It's amazing today.
There are a lot of young people here today.
It's always a 30-minute program.
That's right.
What do you hate about it?
We have to make this a long-standing manzai.
Everyone has a story, right?
I have to do it at the end.
That's right.
Don't react so much.
I think it's okay to stop.
It's better to put out a young man's manzai.
We have time.
That's right.
It's okay.
We don't have a story.
Today is mainly a young man from Osaka.
That's right.
We're here to support you.
We're tired today.
I have a headache.
It doesn't matter.
You have a headache every day.
That's right.
I have a headache every day.
When I was a kid, I ran away from somewhere.
I was hit by a car.
That's right.
I've been hit by a truck before.
This guy is amazing.
This guy is serious.
When I was a kid, my father told me to smoke.
When I cut the curve, it broke down.
The truck slowly backed up on the broken surface.
Goton.
You're a bad guy.
I thought I was dead once on a skateboard.
When it was popular in the past.
I hit my head on the heavy road.
I heard a sound.
Your head?
My head. I can hear it.
I don't like it.
What happened?
I didn't move.
I heard a sound.
Everyone, listen.
I can't tell you what I heard.
I heard it from my head.
I can't tell you.
Let's go back to the starting position.
Yes, please.
Seriously.
Today is the opening.
Please show me the monitor.
It's been a while since I saw you.
You can laugh again.
I can laugh.
I haven't seen you for a while.
I'm the manager of Nitta Aso-kun.
Everyone knows about Yoshimoto Kouki.
I don't think many people in Tokyo know about him.
What kind of talent does he have?
There are many people who say that he played Yoshimoto.
That's right.
I don't think most young people know about him today.
I'd like to explain it to you.
What is this?
Yoshimoto Kouki.
I'm on it.
This is today, June 16th.
June 16th is now.
It's now.
It's in the way.
It's in the way, so I'll take it.
First of all, Yoshimoto Kouki.
There are 50,000 Yoshimoto Kouki talents.
Do you know how many there are?
Hey!
There are about 250 talents.
I'd like to explain it to you.
As you all know, there are a lot of talents.
The top one is...
Yasushi Kiyoshi.
Actually, he's not here.
Where is Yasushi going?
Yasushi, what's going on?
What's going on?
I'm going to use the toilet.
Yasushi Kiyoshi.
There are a lot of things.
This is a big deal.
It's a big deal, so it's just...
If you think about the number of years and regular numbers, it will change.
I think it's okay to think that there are a lot of Yoshimoto Kouki talents.
Yasushi, Kiyoshi, Katsura.
Yes, there are a lot of them.
There are about 250 talents.
Next,
I will explain it to you.
I'm going to explain it to you.
I think it's about this.
It's just the number of years and regular numbers.
Just the number of years and regular numbers.
It's okay to think that there are a lot of talents.
I'll explain it to you.
It's like this.
Right?
Ah, ah, ah, no, no.
And it goes like this.
It's included in this book, too.
In this book, too.
So, as a senior, Kyo-san is there.
Hanshin, Kyojin, Katsura, Bunchin, and so on.
Yes, yes, yes.
Well, well, well, that...
Well, there's something, isn't there?
Well, well, I'll just say it.
Like this, look.
You see?
He's there.
But, well, well, well, well, well.
Isn't it fine?
There's no such thing as that.
Who are you making excuses for?
I don't know who's watching.
Well, well, well, well, it goes like this.
And in this volume, there are a lot of people.
But, well, look.
Let's do it, shall we?
This volume, right?
This volume is also a little bit of a turning point.
Kyo-san is there, but...
Yes.
Well, well, well, well, well, the time is also the same.
Because there's no time.
Well, it goes like this.
That sound is good, isn't it?
Right?
Well, this is also...
This is all about the business!
What?
You can't say that, it's all about the business.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Well, well, well, it's fine.
It's really just around here.
But, well, well, it's fine.
It's fine.
It's here.
And, well, what changes a little from here is that
the line extends to the side.
What does this mean?
Well, there's the Tokyo office, right?
Yoshimoto's office.
And, since it's the Tokyo office,
well, well, well, it's here on this line.
It's a very easy-to-understand story, isn't it?
Right?
It's very educational, isn't it?
I think it's very educational.
And, well, Naoko Nozawa is here.
And, well, for some reason, in the Tokyo office,
there's this kind of person.
It's Marianne.
Marianne is, well, for some reason, in the Tokyo office.
This is, well, this is the strange thing, isn't it?
Well, Hamada-kun, where should I put this?
This is the strange thing.
You...
Don't turn things around like that.
Well, what should I do?
Well, it's the Tokyo office.
Yes.
Well, what should I do?
There's nothing, there's nothing.
This is just the present, isn't it?
I don't know what will happen.
But, if you look at it a year later,
you might not know the difference at all.
I don't know.
Right?
Maybe this is, well, okay.
Uh, she's making a joke by herself.
What is she doing?
I think I'm a very talented person.
I see.
Koji Imada is in the frame.
Yes.
Look at this.
This is Koji Imada.
He's in Osaka right now.
Why are you pulling your face like that?
Wait a minute.
Where are you looking at?
Imada, look at the lens.
It's a lens!
The lens?
The lens is the camera.
Then where are you looking at?
Hello.
I'm a poor man.
I'm poor, but I don't ever go crazy or go dark.
If you live a bright life, good things will happen to you.
You're a good man, Charlie Brown.
There's an empty can of coke in here.
There's some left.
Thank you, God.
Good things happened to you, right?
Thank you for the food.
Boo!
I thought so, but it was pee inside.
You're a good man, Charlie Brown.
There's a pair of long shoes in here.
It's going to be useful.
Let's check the size.
Perfect.
Ouch!
I thought so, but it was pee inside.
But I don't take nutrition, so I don't get poisoned.
You're a good man, Charlie Brown.
I have to put on my own shoes.
Here we go.
Ouch!
The bug is moving this way.
Let's take it with us.
You're a good...
There's a wild boar over there.
Let's get rid of it.
Wait, wild boar!
I thought so, but it was pee inside.
But I don't take nutrition, so I don't get poisoned.
You're a good man, Charlie Brown.
But I have something to brag about.
My family is very happy.
We're 15 siblings.
My eldest son is already 45 years old.
But he's my favorite big brother.
We're home.
I'm saying this with my mouth.
I'm home. How have you been?
Oh, you're a 4-year-old Hichimi.
You're hiding something.
Take it out.
It's a toy.
I don't give you money to buy toys.
What's wrong?
I see. You stole it from the store.
Hichimi, that's a 10,000 yen bill.
Hichimi?
That's a 10,000 yen bill.
That's very smart of you.
You're great, Hichimi.
You're going to be a great woman.
Anyway, I have a gift for you.
It's a secret.
Actually, I've been looking forward to this for a long time.
I succeeded in stealing the Osudake pot.
Now, the moment of justice begins.
It begins.
It's Osudake pot.
Okay, I'm going to boil the water.
I'm nervous.
Will it come out well?
It won't come out even if I push it.
Next, there's not much difference between these two.
You can put them side by side.
He's a man.
He has a beautiful face like a comedian.
Wait a minute.
He's a man.
I don't like it.
I'm going to be bullied by everyone again.
Let's start with the leader group.
What's the leader group?
Don't move.
It's growing.
The girls are watching.
Stop it.
Line up.
Everyone, line up.
Don't hide it.
Don't dig a rock.
It's gold.
It hurts.
Who is it?
It's dangerous.
Don't make me angry.
Is it the leader?
I'm going to get angry.
Are you going to do it?
Damn it.
I'm getting angry.
Leader.
It hurts.
Damn it.
The leader is strong.
Don't put sand in it.
Damn it.
I'm getting angry.
I'm going home.
What is it?
Stop it.
Don't make me angry.
What is it?
I don't like it.
Why?
Why didn't you tell me that you like Hanazawa?
I don't like it.
I'm going to call his house.
Why didn't you tell me?
Okay, I'll tell you.
I like Hanazawa.
Don't laugh.
Don't hide it.
Don't make me angry.
I'm going home.
Damn it.
I'm home.
What's wrong?
The blackboard?
Who is it?
The one that Hanazawa and I drew?
Don't make me angry.
Don't draw it with white magic.
I'm going home.
Are you having fun with the blackboard?
Damn it.
Don't make me angry.
I don't like it.
I'm going home.
Don't make me angry.
Is it the infirmary?
It's closed.
Damn it.
Hanazawa.
I've been sick.
I've liked you for a long time.
Hanazawa.
No, no one is looking.
No, no.
Hanazawa.
Go.
Who is it?
I'm in the infirmary.
Boss.
Please be my friend.
Thank you very much.
Let's move on.
There was one person until now.
This is a combination.
130R.
130R sometimes comes to Tokyo.
I've seen it.
I don't know if there are some people.
This is 130R's board.
This is a man.
This is real.
This is a real man.
Well.
Please take a look.
This is a real man.
Well, this is.
This is very good.
This is a man.
This is very popular in Osaka.
Good evening, everyone. It's time to get angry when you get beaten up by a big bouquet.
When you are studying hard in your study room on the second floor like him, you get very angry when you get beaten up by a big bouquet from the room below.
So today, let's have a lot of people who come to beat up a big bouquet.
This is a study room on the second floor.
First of all, it's the father's side.
Takahiro! Takahiro! What is it, father? Can you hear me? Yes, I can hear you. That's good. Hey! That's good.
No, it's not good. Father! Please! Takahiro! Takahiro!
What is it? What is it? Wait! Don't ask me! Talk to me! Please!
Next, it's the mother's side. Takahiro! Takahiro! Taka-chan!
What is it, mother? What is your name?
What is it? You bastard!
Takahiro! Takahiro! Taka-chan! Taka-bou!
What is it? There's one more.
Did you hit me? I'm going to take off all my joints.
Next, it's the dog that lives at home.
Taro! Shut up! Be quiet!
Takahiro!
Hey! Get out, you idiot! Don't talk to a dog like that!
What is it?
I'm talking to you!
What is it? I'm talking to you!
I'm sorry.
You scared me.
There's something like this.
Next, it's the police car.
Police car? Did something happen?
Takahiro!
Wow! A police car! A police car!
Next, it's the American who stays at home.
Takahiro! Takahiro! Takahiro!
Steve! What is it?
Fujiyama Geisha!
I don't understand!
Steve!
Fujiyama Geisha! I got it!
I'm studying right now. I'm studying history.
Sorry.
It's the second World War. It's complicated.
Talk to me.
Takahiro! Takahiro! Takahiro!
Steve! What are you angry about?
Apologize to Shinjiwan.
Why do I have to apologize?
Tiger, tiger, tiger.
Hey, it's fine. Don't go back to the past.
Orange beef.
Toyota Nissan.
It's a Sony.
Steve, I'm sorry.
It's fine.
Next, it's the grandma.
Takahiro! Takahiro!
What is it, grandma?
I'm scared!
I'm scared! You're dry, aren't you?
You're dry, aren't you?
You'll get hurt if you stay in my room.
Next, it's the last one. It's the grandpa.
Takahiro! Takahiro!
What is it, grandpa?
I'm taking a bath.
Grandpa, I'm studying right now.
Grandpa, did you just take a bath?
Idiot, what have you been doing for 30 years?
What are you talking about?
I don't know what kind of grandpa you are.
Idiot.
Takahiro.
Idiot!
Next, it's the oldies.
Both of you really like women.
Really?
Simply put, we all like women.
Both of you really like women.
Let's take a look.
What kind of picture is this?
This is Tochino Kimura.
This Kimura has a bad habit of being a woman.
Is that so?
He has a bad habit of being a woman.
If you don't let him do it, he'll kick you down the stairs.
Is that so?
That's right.
Did you witness it?
I witnessed it.
He also likes women.
What about Tochino?
He is said to be a girl killer.
Good evening, everyone.
Today, I would like to think about Batamon with you all.
Today, we have the president of the Batamon Research Association, Mr. Kimura Yuichi.
Good evening, Mr. Kimura.
Good evening.
The real and fake in the world.
The fake is called the Batamon.
That's right.
There are many people who are jealous of the fake.
Many people are.
Many people are deceived by the fake and buy it.
There must be some inside.
The fake of Renoma is called the Alema.
You'll know if you see it.
That's right.
The one I'm wearing is also a fake.
The one you're wearing today is...
Can you read it for me?
Kikuchi Takeo?
Takeo Kikuchi.
That's what you think, right?
Yes.
Actually, there is a mystery to this.
To this?
Yes.
This is not Takeo Kikuchi.
What?
It's Takeo Kigokuchi.
Ah, Kigokuchi is good.
You know well about the designer Kigokuchi.
Now, let's go.
Let me introduce you.
Yes.
Michiko London.
Ah, this is popular.
It's famous.
Yes.
This London in England.
That's right.
The Batamon of this.
Ah, the Batamon.
If you look closely, you can see the D.
The Batamon of this.
Michiko Lonoon.
The D is the king.
The king.
You'll buy this by mistake, right?
I think it's French.
Ah.
There is a commercial called Cecil.
It's famous, isn't it?
Cecil, Ion, Hosonomono, Sosonomono.
It's like French.
Ah, is that so?
Yes.
This is well made, isn't it?
Aba House.
It's a bit of a mystery.
Yes.
This is often bought by people who buy dogs.
It's said to be bought by mistake.
The Batamon of Aba House.
Pochi House.
The Batamon of Pochi House.
Pochi...
The one who tears the chains and runs away.
The Batamon is one of the A?
That's right.
There are two Kandas.
Ah.
I think I know this one.
Something like this, the one that is not suitable for you...
Is it okay, president?
It's okay.
I'll be able to ask you.
Next.
Vivayu.
Got it.
This is, for people who often wear it, they like yakiniku.
Oh, for the person who's wearing this, yakiniku.
Oh, this person.
He's laughing.
Let's go.
Take courage.
Let's go!
We're on a plane.
That's right.
Biba Yu's Batamon.
Ho!
Birinba Yukke.
This is a bit smelly.
It's a bit.
It doesn't suit you.
Let's go to the next one.
It's dangerous.
It's a place where it's a spoiler.
Oldies?
It's about us.
We're young Kansai idols, aren't we?
Oldies also have Batamon.
Is there a Batamon in this group?
It's like we're Batamon ourselves.
Is that so?
Oldies also have Batamon.
Toha Tohru Riiru.
Is there a Kanji in this?
It's hard to tell.
Who would make a mistake like this?
It's hard to tell, but it's easy to tell.
Let's go to the next one.
Komusa Demo.
It's a very chic black dress.
It's a nice dress.
Oldies also have Batamon.
Yes.
Punchi De De.
You only say De.
You only say De in the middle.
It's about a man getting dumped.
Komusa Punchi.
No, no.
It's fine.
No, it's not fine.
Batamon is...
If you're so angry, let's make you even angrier when you see the next one.
I'll make you angry.
You have to be convinced.
Routriamon.
I often ask for it.
What is it?
You often buy it.
That's right.
Yes, yes.
This is Batamon.
Is this also on the list?
There are a lot of Enka singers.
Enka singers?
To be clear,
Suwara Yoichi is often...
Suwara Yoichi?
I was deceived and put it here.
Routriamon is Batamon.
Yes.
Outside the window is Aman.
This is also Kanji.
Who is this?
I don't know if it's Batamon.
This tower outside and this tower...
That's it.
Until next week, everyone.
Goodbye.
Now, finally.
This is...
I...
Why did I read this guy?
He's really an amateur.
I want you to see the bottom of Yoshimoto now.
This is the bottom.
That's why I put it here.
It's even lower.
It's called Yamada Hanako.
This is really...
It's not enough here.
That's right.
It's even lower.
I think it's about that.
Onsei-san, step on it.
Yes.
It's a woman like this.
Let's take a look.
It's ugly.
Look.
This is ugly, isn't it?
This is...
Even though it's a night shift job,
he made one wallet.
Normally, if it was a woman,
wouldn't she be able to change clothes?
It's so small.
What wallet is that?
It's like...
Hangyodon.
What's with you?
You bit it before it fell.
Yes.
If someone like you takes it,
what will happen to what I've done so far?
Huh?
Hey, why did you bite it?
Even though it was before it fell.
That's why I bit it.
How many of those do you have?
One.
Wow!
You have a lot of money.
Do you have a boyfriend?
I don't.
You have a boyfriend, right?
Yes.
Look at that!
Do you do that in the summer too?
Say it again, say it again!
That's about it.
That was Hanako Yamada.
Now, after this,
we'll do a little bit of it,
so please look forward to it.
Then, here.
Right?
This is Dan Dan Hamada.
It stretches out like this.
Isn't that your dad?
That's my dad!
Why do you have something like that?
It stretches out like this.
That's my sister!
I'm the one who called her Kako.
That's my name!
I'm sure you all feel the same way,
but I'm not.
When I first saw it,
I thought it was a prank camera.
I'm Dan Dan.
Hello, everyone.
The show is over, isn't it?
That's right.
That's good.
Right?
The mic was too short for Hanako.
But recently,
there's one more comedy show, right?
We haven't done it yet.
The quiz show is the most popular, isn't it?
The quiz show.
The quiz show is very popular.
If you look at the news,
what was it?
Itsumi-san is doing it.
She's doing it.
The quiz show is the best.
Is that so?
That's right.
I'm also thinking about a quiz show.
If I do that,
it'll definitely get a lot of views.
It's the same thing these days.
It's the same pattern.
There's a good one.
What is it?
There's a quiz called Doremi Fadon, right?
I'll add a normal quiz to that.
For example,
there was a quiz about the height of Mt. Fuji.
Fuji?
I'll think of a question to answer.
You know it?
You don't even know the question.
It'll get a lot of views.
It'll get a lot of views?
Is that so?
No one can win.
I'll give you a quiz today.
I'll give you a question.
Okay.
I won't give you a question.
Even if you watch a quiz show,
you can't think of anything.
Travel or prize money.
Normally, you'd say something like
how many million or Hawaii trip.
If you do something,
I can't do it.
If you answer the question,
I'll teach you how to put on makeup.
I don't need that!
I'll think of a question to answer.
Why don't you teach me that?
Why?
Why can't I do that?
I can't do that.
Philippines.
If that's the case,
I'll take a trip to the Philippines.
It's impossible to travel.
Can you become a Filipino from tomorrow?
I don't need that!
If I get it right,
how can I become a Filipino?
Why don't you transfer the residents?
Why are you going that far?
Isn't it fashionable?
If you become a Filipino.
Idiot!
From now on,
I'm going to be an ebuki.
If that's the case,
I don't want to be a resident.
I'll go.
I'll think about it.
Question 1.
Taro-kun went to the flower shop
to buy flowers.
Well, what is it?
Peck-peck.
Peck-peck?
free.
You went to the flower shop to buy flowers.
Well, what is it?
tiye?
What's that?
happening with that word.
I'll ask other people.
What's that?
You went to the flower shop to buy flowers.
Well, what is it?
Please eat exotic plants.
Come on!
pues explain pas-pr downloaded
Exotic Quiz.
What is Exotic Quiz?
What is Exotic Quiz in the name of a quiz?
Simply put, it's the second question.
Well, there's no second question.
Well, that Exotic Quiz is good.
Yoshio-kun went to the bathhouse.
Well, what is it?
Tick-tock, tick-tock, tick-tock.
Yoshio-kun went to the bathhouse.
What is it?
Is it different from Yoshio-kun?
Yoshio-kun went to the bathhouse.
What is it?
This is a new pattern.
What is it that Yoshio-kun went to the bathhouse?
What kind of question is that?
It's a question that's hard to understand.
No one can answer it.
If it's hard to understand,
if you think of it as one rupee and three yen, it's easy to understand.
What are you talking about?
I understand.
Let's make it easy to understand the question.
Don't get angry.
I want to get angry.
This is the first time I've done this.
Why?
I'm about to lose my temper.
But I'll do it.
Do it properly.
I don't understand your problem.
Yoshio-kun went to the bathhouse.
Listen to this.
That's because Yoshio-kun loves baths.
There's something like shampoo and conditioner these days.
Yes, yes.
Yoshio-kun doesn't like that kind of thing.
Yoshio-kun likes shampoo and conditioner separately.
Yoshio-kun...
Well, what is it?
It's the same thing.
It has nothing to do with shampoo and conditioner.
It's easy to understand.
Executivo quiz.
What?
Executivo quiz?
Yes.
What is it?
Executivo quiz is...
That's enough.
You can choose the question.
Oh, me?
Performance, history, society, geography.
Yes.
You can choose.
That's good.
Please choose.
Performance, history, geography.
Geography?
Yes.
History.
History?
Bim bom, bim bom, bim bom, bim bom, chance card!
Thank you.
It's a chance card.
If you can answer this, you'll get double.
What?
Me?
You'll get double?
It's big.
I want to see it, so I'll get it right.
Do your best.
It's history quiz.
Yes.
I got it.
Oda Nobunaga!
What are you doing?
What?
I don't know.
What are you doing?
Change the question.
What? Change the question.
What?
Do you know?
What are you doing, Oda Nobunaga?
What?
Siding Queen!
Bim bom, bim bom, bim bom.
I'm standing.
I said it randomly.
It's a standing quiz.
I got it, Mr. Hamada.
What?
I'm going to quit the previous quiz.
You said it from the beginning.
Let's make it a choice quiz.
What is a choice quiz?
There were three choices.
Yes.
Let's go with that pattern.
That's good.
That's easy.
It's not fun with three choices.
It's a 20-choice quiz.
It's even more difficult.
It's different.
Baby, it's different.
What is it, Mr. Hamada?
What kind of question is that?
It's a quiz question.
Are you ready?
The question is very easy.
Let me tell you the question.
The question is
Who is the current Prime Minister of Japan?
Is that the question?
It's very easy.
Yes.
Wait a minute.
Do you have 20 strange questions?
Do you know the answer?
When you hear the question,
press the button and answer it.
I'm sorry.
Answer the question as it is.
I know the answer.
You know the answer?
It's not easy.
Don't worry.
I'll ask you until I get the answer.
That's good.
Let's go.
Tanaka
Harada
Haino
Kusakabe
Kanami
Jerry
That's definitely wrong.
That's wrong.
Ota
Jiro
That's a lower name.
That's impossible.
Kaifu
Pimpo
Mr. Hamada
Please give me the answer.
Kaifu
Mr. Hamada, tell me the number.
Tell me from the beginning.
You can say Kaifu.
Even if you don't say the number.
It's Kaifu.
Saichenkui
Amazing.
What is Saichenkui?
Is this China?
This is the last question.
Why did you say Saichenkui in the last question?
Let's meet again, Saichenkui.
Saichenkui
Mr. Hamada
That's too bad.
That's no good.
I'm sorry.
Really.
That's enough.
I'm sorry.
This is the last quiz.
This is very easy.
I'm going to say all the numbers I've done so far.
Numbers?
You can't even get one right.
That's right.
Good luck.
This is really easy.
Is that so?
Let's move on to the next question.
What is the weather like in the Tokyo area on June 16th?
I think you're going to get it wrong, Mr. Hamada.
Why don't you say it?
I want to pinch you.
Go ahead.
Why don't you say it?
Tell me the answer.
I don't know.
I'm sorry.
I'm watching TV.
I think he's stupid.
It's okay.
I'll give you time today.
You can go outside and watch.
That's enough.
I don't know.
I'll say it clearly.
You tell me the answer.
The answer is
rain.
the sun.
The answer is
the clouds.
I'll leave the rest to the editor.
That's all for today.
If you have another chance,
this member will be on the show.
That's right.
There are still other members other than today.
We don't have much time.
Anyway, this member will be on the show.
There are other members.
That's right.
This member will be on the show.
I hope you watch the show.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
I love you.
Thank you very much.
How was it today?
The members who will be on the show.
That's right.
Well,
I spent more money than usual.
You didn't.
The members who will be on the show.
Everyone is cheap.
That's right.
I thought about it.
Using such cheap members,
I thought I would make the show more exciting.
But I can't do it.
Well,
Actually,
I thought I would make the show more exciting.
That's right.
It's one of the tricks of Mr.Ozaki.
I don't understand.
Is that so?
Who is it?
No, no.
If there is a chance,
I hope you watch the show more.
Thank you very much.
I will come back as usual.
That's right.
Please watch the show.
Well,
Mr.Sumon will be on the show.
Please look forward to it.
Also,
Mr.Ashishi will be on the show.
He will be on the show with me.
Please look forward to it.
Mr.Ashishi will be on the show.
He will be on the show with me.
Please look forward to it.
See you next time.
Good bye.
Please look forward to it.