Kirara!
What, Urara?
Today is the final match!
That's right!
Do your best!
Let's do our best, Urara!
We've come this far.
That's right.
This year was especially tough.
It was a tough fight.
The first match was really tough.
That's right.
We lost to that attack.
It was meaningless, but we stepped on the tap.
That's right.
Today is the final match.
We can't lose to them!
Who are your opponents today?
Today...
Ucchanko Nanchanko!
They're the ones with the worst skin!
We can't lose to them!
Do your best!
I understand.
Your face is a little scary.
Are you okay?
But they're pitiful, too.
That's right.
They can't beat us.
Your serve is the best in this country!
That's right.
It's a serve from over there!
It's coming!
Now is the time to finish it!
We did it!
We finished it!
Next is the serve from over there.
Don't give up!
It's our serve!
It's my serve!
That's right.
I haven't done anything like this before.
Do your best!
Take it well!
I'm going!
What are you doing?
Your serve is the worst!
Take it well!
I'm going!
What are you doing?
Next is my serve.
That's right.
Do your best!
I got it.
I'm going!
How could this happen?
Kirara.
What?
At this rate, we might lose.
Urara!
What are you saying?
It's okay.
We have to use that.
That?
Are you talking about that?
If we use that, they might die.
It's okay if they die.
No!
We're going to win!
We're going to do it!
If you say we're going to do it...
We're going to combine!
I got it.
If you think you can do it, do it!
It's the reception from the washroom.
It's not like that!
I told you it's not like that!
In the middle of the night, the boy's serve started quietly.
Actually, this program was the reason for the title.
Hello, everyone!
Hello!
That's right.
No matter how many times you say it, it's a popular number.
It's finally here in Tokyo City.
Yes, it's here.
It's downtown!
That's right...
It's here.
I was feeling good from the very last conversation!
I amHanamame!
Hanamame?
No...
I think you've kissed before.
What did it taste like?
Please tell your father.
Hey!
It's a long time ago, so I forgot.
No, no, no.
I'm sorry.
It's okay.
From this one word,
I was born in the era of the child's servant Arahen.
Time is the time of the great Edo Pacific.
The world is playing with the name of the 800 wild birds.
Where this man goes,
a storm will blow again today.
I'm scared.
Help me!
Shit!
What the hell is this?
Help me!
Throw it!
What the hell is this?
I'm waiting for you.
Shobai! Shobai!
Let's think together.
On the popular program in January, Shobai! Shobai!
Next, from downtown, from the era of the child's servant Arahen, two people from downtown.
I'll ask the two of you.
Everyone who appeared today,
the whole program is a golden hour program at night.
By the way, only this downtown program,
is a midnight Kanto local program.
There is no one who does PR here.
Really.
I'll talk to you later, Itsumi.
What are you making?
This is it.
20 seconds.
17 seconds left.
I know how to explain it.
I can't stop it.
Hurry up and run.
It's a local program.
Do your best.
Don't come after me, Itsumi.
Downtown special.
It's a manly program.
It's hard.
Trendy golf competition.
The players of the Motten team are
Ishida Junichi.
Thank you.
Kanna Masaki.
Number 3, 160 yards, short hole in Ikegoye.
Why are you shooting from the edge?
If you shoot from this side,
the tree will come out.
Oh, I see.
You're making a mistake.
You're big.
It's bad.
I forgot to put putter on bread in the morning.
It's Ishida's barbie putter.
It's a strong shot.
It's a good shot.
It's on the line.
Oh, nice.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Big.
I don't have anything to teach Junichi.
I didn't say anything.
Kanna, you're out.
The number 3 is here.
Ready, start.
It's still going.
The match between the two teams.
The penalty game is a tie.
Yoshimura is fast.
It's a tie.
The penalty game is won by Mr. Watarabe.
I'll let you go to your next job as you are now.
My next job will be a target special.
Hey, stop it.
Damn it, I'll go first.
The target special is the 20th anniversary special.
It's a big deal.
What are you doing?
I'm watching TV right now.
Next is Masayuki Watanabe.
Stop it.
I'm sorry to leave you alone during the live broadcast.
There was a group called Downtown.
What are you doing?
I lost the game and went to my next job.
I was joking.
I'm sorry to leave you alone during the live broadcast.
I'm waiting for a return of a hot guy.
I don't know such a guy.
Good evening.
The temperature in Tokyo is 23 degrees.
The wind is cool, isn't it?
It's getting warmer.
I can't do it.
I can't do this.
I'm bleeding.
I'm sorry to say this, but I don't hate it, but...
You say it over and over again.
I don't hate it. I don't hate it.
I don't hate it.
It's been 25 years since I debuted this year.
I don't hate it at all.
Park Win's skiing match!
Alps' long-sleeved shirt!
It's almost time.
Yeah!
If Yoshizumi-san loses,
you'll have to play a penalty game.
I won, so I'm going to take over this place.
I don't know what you're looking at.
Start!
No, no, no, no!
My foot is still open!
I don't want to lose!
I'm going to score a goal!
Are you stupid?
Here we go!
I'm going down!
No, no, no, no!
Penalty game!
Captain!
I'm so happy!
I'm the happiest when I'm with the captain!
The first kid's skier!
Chiki-chiki!
Ogiri Takahashi!
Hanashika-san and the others, come on out!
Ayu-yo! Osakabe!
First, Japanese television.
This is called work.
It's the best!
Let's go with work.
The best, the best company!
C!
I don't know anything about UFOs or ghost shows.
S!
I'm a good producer, but...
Don't say that!
C!
I have a lot of sex-loving employees.
S!
I'm a good producer, but...
Don't say that!
Hanachan!
Let's go with work.
C!
I have a lot of sex-loving employees.
I have a tight wife.
C!
My lips are drooping...
Don't say that!
K!
The more I open my pores...
I'll decide how to do it.
Don't say that!
Chikichiki!
Seat-tripping war!
Ah-chi-chi!
As you can see, we're going to roller skate today.
My butt is in the way.
If we get caught, we lose.
That's why people from both teams go to grab each other's butt.
I see.
It's not a new project or anything.
C!
Hamada!
Can you take my attack?
Who is it?
There he is!
Hurry up!
Push him!
If you push him, he'll fall!
Ah-chi-chi!
Chikichiki!
Coordination strategy!
Okay!
Let's go.
Coordination strategy.
We'll choose each other's clothes.
Let's choose.
And then we'll do the fashion show.
That's right.
This is tough.
Even adults can do this, right?
No, no.
Why?
You can do this.
I'm a kid.
What is this?
A hip pad.
A hip pad?
To improve your style.
I'll definitely buy this.
Here comes the fashionable Hama-chan.
Hama-chan, come on out!
The theme is one shot.
One shot.
One shot. Mom's help.
This pants.
I was curious about this.
This is for 2 years old.
Let me tell you something.
What is it?
I'm an 8 month old kid.
My theme is, what kind of person are you?
Now, please come out.
What is this?
This is for you.
Happy new year.
Idiot.
Let's go!
Are you Souchanka Granbury part 1?
Who is the person who looks like a big poop?
Who is the person who won the grand prize?
Now, please think about it.
Rimei Onishi.
Matsumoto Iyo.
Matsumoto Iyo-san.
Iro-chan.
Who won the grand prize?
Matsumoto Iyo-san.
This is the first time Matsumoto Iyo-san has been revealed.
He is Matsumoto Iyo-san's older brother.
He revealed the story of his younger brother's childhood.
He was looking forward to the rain.
When it started to rain, he didn't put on his shoes.
He went to the sky and said,
You idiot! Come down!
Come down!
I saw something.
And a big guest appeared.
First question.
What was your middle school name?
This is...
A man who buys with his face.
I thought it was me.
What is your name?
A country panda.
What is your middle school name?
I don't know.
Kawaii-san.
Idiot.
Pig glasses.
I hate you.
What are you doing?
And Matsumoto Iyo-san's mother appeared.
He is the third child.
I'm sorry to say this, but...
He is like a pet.
How was New York?
New York?
Did you have fun?
I couldn't stand the long flight.
When I was walking in the city,
I saw a black man.
I was very scared.
It wasn't my mother, but...
We were walking in New York.
The camera was rolling.
He looked very scary.
He looked like he was eating two and a half.
When I was lying down,
he pushed me.
I was about to hit the two and a half.
What are you doing?
When I looked back,
he looked like he was going to hit me again.
That was really scary.
I had a good street fight with a black man.
I thought it was okay to fight.
It was okay.
I wasn't scared at all.
I wasn't running away.
I was luring him.
He was obviously running away.
I thought he was coming this way.
There was a trap here.
If you sprinkle salt on a slug,
the body will melt.
But if you keep sprinkling salt,
what will happen in the end?
It will disappear.
It will disappear?
I see.
But the salt will remain, right?
The salt will remain.
I see.
That's not the case.
Oh!
This was an experiment.
Of course.
First, I looked for a slug.
I knew that if I sprinkled salt on a slug,
it would melt.
I see.
So I sprinkled salt on the slug.
It started to melt a little.
I see.
I sprinkled more salt.
It started to melt even more.
I see.
What will happen in the end?
I brought more and more salt from here.
More and more salt.
I sprinkled more salt.
What happened?
I told my mother to get angry.
I want to cut this part.
Thank you very much.