In the first episode of Gaki no Sky, Tsukiji will announce the opening title of the first half of the show,
Donatte Kandara Kyoufu no Batsuta!
Coming soon!
Today, we're going to talk about how we made the opening title.
The one we did, or the one we just made.
The other day, when we were talking about Mild Seven,
Kokoriko didn't talk at all.
That's right.
He didn't talk at all.
He didn't say anything.
He didn't say anything!
His annual salary is 1.8 million yen.
It's fine if he didn't say anything.
Please don't say anything.
He just said it earlier, didn't he?
If you get stuck or bite someone, you'll be punished.
That's not going to happen.
He didn't say anything.
Why did you say that earlier?
Ouch!
It hurts so much!
What is this?
It's a non-skub, isn't it normal?
I'm trying to change it.
It's like a good time.
It got weird after you put on that little glasses.
Can I take it off?
No!
It's not weird. It's not weird.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
The punishment game is called,
The battle of fear is about to begin.
What is this?
What's going to happen?
It's going to fly up.
If you avoid it, you'll be punished.
That's the worst.
It's the worst as an entertainer.
Now, Mr. Yamazaki's question is this!
It's coming up.
Look!
Yes.
There was something like this.
Let's go!
Three, two, one, go!
The first time, at the Gaki no Tsukai Arai,
The manager of the downtown,
Chikichiki Nakimokuro, Okamoto Ta...
Are you okay?
No!
Are you sure?
Yes, I'm sure.
No!
Are you sure?
This is shocking.
Mr. Okamoto!
Wait a minute, it hurts so much.
I don't want to get a stomachache.
It's like this.
Oh, that's how it is.
Wow, really?
Then I'll go.
My body is getting used to it.
No, I'm still not used to it.
This is it.
Yes.
This is good, though.
Let's go with full power.
Yes.
Three, two, one, go!
Gai Gai Gaki no Tsukai Arai, Chikichiki Hamada Mizoshibasu Eikinen,
Amefuto Tournament!
I knew it.
I'm used to it.
Let's go.
Endo.
Endo is in trouble.
He said, I'm used to it, but it was weird.
No, it's not like that.
It's not like that.
Endo's is this.
I did it, I did it.
I finally did it.
I did it.
Let's go.
Three, two, one, go!
Dai Tai Gaki no Tsukai Arai, Chikichiki Magoroshi no Chinjuu,
Shiro Techo, Konmori Aikyo...
Shiro Techo?
You read it wrong.
Shiro Techo.
The old man's is this.
I'm Sakame.
This is tough.
You're so stubborn!
What is that?
Wait a minute.
When did I say that?
You just happened to say that.
Three, two, one, go!
Dai Tai Gaki no Tsukai Arai,
Matsumoto Kashitayo Hamada,
Karitenai itte 3000 yen,
Kettei Kikaku, Chikichiki, Hamada,
Magoroshi!
That's a long one!
It's a long one.
Hamada.
And he changes the attachment to a special weapon.
He can't afford to fail.
The pain of fear is waiting for him.
This is tough.
I'm being stubborn.
Yamasaki's is this.
Three, two, one, go!
Dai Tai Gaki no Tsukai Arai,
Heta no Yamasaki, Hitori Dachi, Chikichiki,
Yoru no Ohara...
Are you okay?
Osei-san, are you okay?
He's in great shape right now.
He seems confident.
This is the question.
Okay, let's go.
Wait, wait, wait.
You're still doing it right.
This is tough.
Okay, let's go.
Three, two, one, go!
Dai Tai Gaki no Tsukai Arai,
Chikichiki, Mezase Shidonin Shirodan,
Suimi Shouzetsu Shippetsu Taikai!
Amazing.
Did you say Chikichiki?
I did.
Dai Tai Gaki no Tsukai Arai,
Jichan Bacchan, Chikichiki,
Jetsu-chan...
Are you okay?
You sounded like Jichan Bacchan.
I can't react to this.
I don't want to see you react like that.
That's weird.
If this goes on for too long,
I'm going to have to resign.
Why are you doing this?
I don't get it.
Don't count me out as a hero.
I don't know about that.
I don't watch TV.
Here's the question.
Three, two, one, go!
There's a reason for this.
Why?
Can I say it?
Can I say it's a water thing?
Yes, a water thing.
Here we go.
Three, two, one, go!
Dai Tai Gaki no Tsukai Arai,
Okamoto Suichuchu Tago Kaina,
Chikichiki Matakaina,
Suiwono Kaina!
That's weird.
What's Suiwono?
It's a water thing.
Ouch!
You didn't say Chikichiki either.
It was a different place.
Ouch!
What is this?
It's weird.
This is easy, isn't it?
Little bird.
Here we go.
Three!
This is bad, this is bad.
What is this?
This is called Okamoto family.
What is Okamoto family?
Here we go.
Here we go!
Three, two, one, go!
Dai Tai Gaki no Tsukai Arai,
Shinkon Hoya Hoya,
Chikichiki Matakaina,
Suiwono Kaina,
Chiki Chiki No Basho, that happens a lot.
Stop pushing!
Could you please change this?
It stopped.
The
The next game to be punished
is the Paenage Jigoku.
It's my turn.
Just wait.
It's so hard to do it.
I'm so frustrated.
Tanaka, you have to make the most of your reach.
Wait, that's a punch.
It's not a punch.
The answer is this.
3, 2, 1, go!
The first Gaki no Tsukai Arahen!
Naita Naita Korai Kiyosu Ni Naitake Grand Prix!
The answer is this.
This is so nostalgic.
This was about 6 years ago.
3, 2, 1, go!
The first Gaki no Tsukai Arahen!
Chikichiki Taihaiya Obayashi!
What are you saying? Taihaiya?
You're so young.
The second Gaki no Tsukai Arahen!
The answer is this.
What is this?
It's just the order.
Wait a minute.
Give me another chance.
Have you done this before?
Have I done this before?
If there's something different, you can do the one you've done before.
This is the first time I've done something new.
If it's like this, throw me a pie.
I don't care.
Come on.
1, 2, come on.
I don't care.
I'll do it until I make it.
You've done it before, haven't you?
Yes, I've done it.
Wait a minute.
The first Gaki no Tsukai Arahen.
What's wrong with you?
This is cool.
3, 2, 1.
Go!
The first Gaki no Tsukai Arahen.
Super Ultra Super Miracle Magical Rolling
Fighting Melodeus Intro Bon Challenge!
The second Gaki no Tsukai Arahen.
How many seconds do I have to cool down?
28 seconds!
The first Gaki no Tsukai Arahen.
Super Ultra Super Miracle Magical Rolling
Fighting Melodeus Intro Bon Challenge!
You're doing it the right way.
No matter how you think about it, it's a white group.
You haven't done it yet, have you?
I've come this far.
Amano-san, you're so beautiful.
Let's do it quickly.
I can't show you the question.
Guess what's written on the back.
Here's the question.
This is amazing.
You're making a rhythm.
I can't do it.
Why are you holding it?
3, 2, 1.
Go!
The first Gaki no Tsukai Arahen.
Super Ultra Super Miracle Magical Rolling
Who's the first one?
You're the first one.
You're the second one.
There's a mountain of them in my ear.
Super Super Miracle Magical Rolling
This is the punishment game.
Next week, look forward to it.
From now on,
We're going to use a new set.
I'm going to do it the way I designed it.
Why are you doing it the way you designed it?
I'm a fan.
I don't like ants either.
I'm wondering if it'll change during the mid-to-half-past.
I'm a little more moved.
You're right.
I'm a little more like, huh?
You're so mean.
It's a bit late today.
It's already a good time.
What?
Eri is expensive.
Eri is like this.
I can't. I really don't like it.
Then wait a minute.
Let's do it properly.
I'm so sick of it.
You're the worst.
I can't think of anything interesting.
Only the tie and Eri are left.
This is the only one left.
Please stop.
I can't do it.
I really can't do this feeling.
What's this?
I like that kind of feeling.
Let's do it properly.
Especially this.
What is it?
I feel like I'm Captain Okita.
It's bigger.
Captain Okita.
But I can't take it off.
Let's do it properly.
The guy wearing a T-shirt told me to do it properly.
Do it properly.
What is it?
Let me stop.
I can't. I really can't.
I can't do it.
Even if I get hit.
It stopped.
It stopped properly.
It stopped until my eyes.
What is it?
Do you know interesting news?
Osaka's convenience store.
Do you know it?
Please laugh a little more.
I don't know it, but I can't laugh.
I was on the newspaper.
A convenience store worker came in.
He said he wanted money.
The gun was made of wood.
I said I wanted money.
The manager took me outside.
He threw me outside.
The worker woke up.
He said, this is all I have today.
He went home.
It's a masterpiece.
That's my line.
The manager said.
It's funny.
What are you doing?
Who are you?
It's a funny story.
Don't put it in.
I'm doing it right.
Put it out.
Shut up.
I'm sorry.
This is the last problem.
It's really bad.
I think there's a reason.
What do you do when you wear a jacket?
Do you stop it?
I don't stop it when I wear a jacket.
I don't do that.
The secret is still a secret.
Is that so?
It's been a while since I've seen you up close.
What were you doing up close?
I was working up close.
I'm a loner.
When I'm alone, I think,
Did you see something?
I've never seen it.
It's like a white wall.
If you keep looking at me like this, I'll definitely see it.
That's what it's like.
I've said this before, but there's a lot of strange things.
When I buy a new car, I think,
I'm going to buy a new car soon.
What are you talking about?
I want to go home soon.
You want to go home?
You're going to buy a new car, right?
I was thinking about buying a new car.
My car went wrong.
You can't figure that out in science.
The worst thing I've ever done was,
I was driving on New Year's Eve.
I don't know what it is, but the wiper.
The wiper came off.
It can't come off, can it?
Do you understand?
I was driving on the highway, and the rubber came out.
It came out.
No way!
The rubber came out.
That's a bad habit.
It just happened.
That's not true.
When you do something like that,
you don't have love for your car.
I have love for my car,
that's why I don't hate it.
I love it so much,
I want to work hard until the end.
That's not true.
You don't want to leave me.
That's why I don't want to leave you.
That's why I want you to take care of me.
It's a problem for the owner.
It's a problem, but when I fix it
on a rainy day,
I feel good.
I get angry when the rubber is in.
Who says that?
I get angry.
I don't like it.
The car.
Do you understand?
I understand.
Is all ok?
It's not all.
Mostly, right?
I get it, I get it.
Hey, Sora, that's fine.
TAKUAAA!
That eccentric voice...
Thank you very much.
It's a question for Komadamu's famous Matsumoto-san.
It's Sora-san, yes.
In general, it's fine, but what is Matsumoto-san's My Boom, which is the only thing that's popular among you?
Right now, My Boom is over, but...
It's a song-and-dance battle within the company.
I see.
What's next?
What do you mean? Listen!
Eh?
Ah, ah, ah.
What kind of feeling is that?
You see, my car has about 6 CDs.
While listening to them in the car,
Nakajima Miyuki is also in it, but...
It's a battle between the red team and the white team.
I see.
Right now, the red team is Yusei.
Next time, I'll call A-chan and say,
Oh, the white team is working hard, too!
I see.
It's a song-and-dance battle within the company.
I want the name of Heisei's Socrates.
Matsumoto-san, who has been coming every year since a few hundred performances...
Ah, wait a minute.
I'm already done writing.
My My Boom is still going on, even after the commercials.
Ah, is that so?
That's one thing.
Well, that's one thing.
The rest is...
I did this earlier, too.
Yes.
When I went to the bathroom...
Well...
Let's talk about the actual story.
This...
I'm going to show you this.
Hey, wait, wait.
Where is it locked?
Is it here?
No, no, no.
It's locked like this.
What?
This is how you do it.
Well, this is how you do it.
You can't do anything, can you?
I'll show you, but...
Yes, yes, yes.
At that time, it's a little funny that I can't use my hands.
A little...
I'm laughing.
What do you mean?
I took it out with my hands and did it like this.
Well...
I can't support it at all.
What am I talking about?
Explain it properly.
I thought I could support it at all.
This guy was called and jumped out.
But even though I took it out, I didn't support it at all.
So I thought I couldn't do anything, so I just showed it to him.
That's why it's funny.
I want the name of Heisei's Socrates.
I'd like to ask Mr. Matsumoto who comes to the park every year.
Yes.
Three philosophical talks of Mr. Matsumoto.
Is that okay?
What is happiness?
What is life?
What is a best friend?
I see.
Don't be so quiet.
It's okay.
I'm a philosopher.
I'm a philosopher of Mr. Matsumoto.
Yes.
What is happiness?
Yes, please.
It's not realizing that you're unhappy.
You can't say that.
That was really cool.
What is life?
That's what I'm thinking right now.
Don't put it out.
What?
When you're on the phone, you say hello first.
Please tell me what that means.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Actually, I want to change it.
But it's hard to change.
You have to change this.
It's the age of the universe.
If you can change it, it's revolutionary.
I want to expand my view of the universe.
I want to change it to Cosmos.
Cosmos?
Cosmos!
It's just a pun.
What's wrong with a pun?
It's hard to change your view of the universe.
I want to change it to Cosmos.
But you're thinking it's a good idea.
Cosmos?
Cosmos!
I'm sure you can say that.
You said that, right?
I think he said it in the car on the way home.
Cosmos!
This program was brought to you by these sponsors.