In the 8th episode of Gaki no Tsukai Arahen, Chiki-chiki!
Celebrity! Are you really going to the Grand Prix?
This segment, you won't be able to see it on air.
If you come here, you'll be lucky.
Now, let's introduce today's guests!
Chiki-chiki!
Next, we have Otate Matsumoto-san!
This is my show, so I can't make it any more interesting.
What are you talking about?
I'm not going to risk my life to work today.
Next, we have Watanabe Marina-san!
Now, you just have to write more and more.
Yes, understood.
Why don't you choose your job?
Watanabe Marina-san!
Before we start, please take this.
This is an announcement from Otate-san.
I'm going to do a live performance.
From May 3rd to May 8th...
No!
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
The first is this!
Ta-da!
Your mother is calling you by your nickname!
Do you want to do something at home?
What is it?
Are you okay?
No, I'm not okay.
Please write it down!
Do you want to do something at home?
Do you want your mother to call you by your nickname?
Isn't that obvious?
Isn't that you?
Hurry up!
Otate-san, please write it down.
Don!
Minamon!
What is it called?
Monta-chan!
Marina!
I don't know.
I don't know, but I think it's something like this.
Matsumoto-san!
Well...
It's Ducchan.
It's different from the one I've seen before!
Ducchan's actions are like that.
Kusanosiro-san.
Tatashima brothers.
Nomura Hironobu.
Kusanosiro-san.
Tatashima brothers.
Kanda Masaki.
Ogata Naoto.
Kanda Masaki-san.
Otake Makoto.
Matsumoto-san.
Kandashiro-chan.
Kanda Masaki.
Kandashiro-san.
Matsumoto Hitoshi-san.
Kanda Masaki?
Kanda Masaki-san won the Grand Prix!
Everyone out!
I was called Mako-chan the other day.
Next is this!
Have you ever been caught in a car accident?
You don't need to know this.
Please think about it.
Is it a woman?
It's only for women.
What?
What do you mean I'm Tama's running guy?
Do you understand?
In a sense, if it's a male version, it's correct.
In a sense, if it's a female version, it's correct.
I would never do it.
That's a lie.
Are you serious?
Let's move on.
I don't think it's true.
I've been to a check-up.
It's like, it's a lie.
It's a lie.
I'm scared to accept it.
If you say something like, it's not true,
I'll laugh my ass off.
The next one is Marina's.
I can accept it.
Please don't say it.
Even if it doesn't appear here, I think it's true.
It's a lie.
That's why I came here today.
It's really not true.
I don't know such a thing.
What do you mean?
I don't think it's true.
What do you think?
The last one.
I don't know, but it's Azuma's.
It's a harsh line.
I don't think it's true.
Wait a minute.
What if the camera is off?
What if the camera is surprised?
I'm scared.
Naomo Yozawa.
Akiko Matsumoto.
Masami Kisamoto.
Fumi.
I think I can eat anything.
Hikaru Ishida.
Shizuka Kudo.
Akiko Matsumoto.
There was such a rumor.
Everyone is wrong.
You said there was a rumor.
There was such a rumor.
What kind of rumor is that?
Then here it is.
You're out of school.
You're only out of elementary school.
Everyone is wrong.
You said you were going to school.
What are you laughing at?
This is the worst.
What do you think I said?
What did you say?
I know.
You wanted to be on this show, didn't you?
Let's start with Nago-chan.
I'm going to guess this.
This is an image.
Toga-chan.
Marina.
This is the image of Otake-san.
What are you talking about?
Matsumoto-san.
Adachi Yu.
You're just like that.
If it's like that, you can eat as much as you want.
This is wrong.
This is the image of the Kuroa brothers.
This is a little funny.
This is the image that everyone has seen on TV.
Jimmy Onishi-san.
Hosokawa Fumie.
Iijimai.
Komoto Natsuki.
Nozawa Naoko.
Jimmy Onishi.
Komoto Natsuki.
Nozawa Naoko.
It's stupid to do things like this.
Komoto Natsuki.
Iijimai.
It's funny.
This is the image that everyone has seen on TV.
Everyone is wrong.
The next question is this.
You eat eight meals a day, right?
Wait a minute.
Don't watch TV.
It's hot.
This is the image that everyone has seen on TV.
Please don't say that.
What is it?
When I write something, it looks like I'm writing something bad.
This is the image of Tama.
This is the image of the All-Mighty Joker.
This is the image that everyone has seen on TV.
You are wonderful.
This is the image of MAKO.
What are you talking about?
This is the image of KUN.
This is the image of MARINA.
I really thought of this.
I thought of this.
You didn't say it.
This is the image of MADOMO.
I don't know the name.
This is the image of the comedian club.
This was a video shot after pandemonium.
List of mankind's 5 13 creatures
Matsumura Kunihiro
Wada Akiko
It seems like it's eating by body.
Matsumura Kunihiro
Wada Akiko
Takagi-P
Yamada Kunikou
alerts
Matsumura Kunihiro
Matsumura 뭐야
Matsumura Kuniho! Everyone out!
Yamada Kuniko-san is in 3rd place.
Wait a minute!
You're pretty close to the finish line.
Now, finally, the last question!
The last question is this!
Omae OO!
What?
I'm going to die if you don't answer!
You better be prepared!
Long time no see!
It's been a while since we stood here and talked.
We stood on the New York stage though.
There were a lot of Japanese people.
There was a lot of excitement there.
The black guy in front of us.
I didn't like it.
It was really cold just talking about the black guy.
I didn't like it just looking at him.
He was like this the whole time.
I'm going to die if you don't answer!
It was hard.
How was New York?
New York?
So you're in 2nd place?
That's right.
Did you have fun?
I was in 4th place.
It's your first time.
I'm a member of a video company.
A rental video company?
In New York?
Yes.
I still have to go back to New York.
There were a lot of returnees.
Well, well, well.
I'm the face of the company.
The face of the company?
What are you talking about?
That's a weird match.
How was it going there for the first time?
First of all, I can't stand that long airplane.
I've been on it for 14 hours.
I've never sat on the same chair for 14 hours in my life.
I'm the face of the company.
I don't know why.
I'm scared.
Your butt?
Why?
I've been sitting behind you.
When you sit down and stand up, it's like going to the bathroom.
Can't you move freely?
I know that.
I was given a chance.
Were you scared?
Yes.
You have to sit down according to the number.
You're like a village chief.
That's not true.
I just drank a lot of wine in the chair I was given.
That's right.
You shouldn't drink so much.
You're crazy.
I'm not crazy.
I'm a crazy person.
I expect a lot of things on the plane.
I can say a lot of things other than that.
But I don't know if I'm holding back.
I didn't know that.
What are you talking about?
I was eating udon.
JAL is making cup udon.
I wanted to eat udon.
I couldn't eat it.
I was sleeping in front of you.
I looked like I was going to eat udon.
I looked like I didn't have udon.
But I couldn't say it.
I was sleeping with an eye mask on.
Didn't you know that?
I usually eat food on the plane.
Why did you only order oolong tea?
You like me, don't you?
Why do you sleep for 14 hours a day?
There are many mysteries on the plane.
When you cross the change line, you can close the window.
Why is that?
Can't you see it?
Is there something?
There must be something.
What is it?
There is a mammoth walking on the plane.
There are many mysteries on the plane.
I can't see it.
I can't stand 14 hours a day.
That's where we're sitting.
Downtown and Okamoto are the executives.
He went to the chair to make fun of the staff.
What are you eating?
It's a leaf.
That's fine.
It's the staff.
It's the staff, so it's the other general staff.
It's different.
The bread is in the bag.
I want to put the bread in the basket and bring it to you.
Do you want to eat it?
It's better not to go there.
I've been there.
The sad thing about Japanese people is that they go there and try to speak English.
That's not cool.
I'm a dignified person.
I was sleeping in that room.
I was sleeping.
The cleaning lady came to me.
There was still time until the meeting time.
I opened the door and started singing.
I don't sing anymore.
Wait a minute. I'll be out soon.
That's clear in Japanese.
It's clear.
What about you?
I don't sing anymore.
You are a dignified person.
When I go there, I'm more dignified.
Why?
I feel like I can do it alone at night.
Alone?
Alone at night.
How do you feel?
I was surrounded.
You were surrounded?
I was surrounded by 30 people.
What are you talking about?
Where are you from?
I don't know.
I told you.
You told me.
He didn't say anything.
Where are you from?
Why did you tell me?
I didn't say anything.
Where are you from?
I'll go there again.
No, no, no.
It's heavy.
Let's shake hands and break up.
Why?
I'll still send you a letter.
How did the cockroach in the middle of the nostalgic cockroach Hoi Hoi go inside?
That has a female elephant.
What is a female elephant?
A cockroach goes like this.
It's a cockroach Hoi Hoi.
Okay.
There is food in the middle of the cockroach Hoi Hoi.
There is food.
So, if I shout,
it's going to be powerful.
Why?
It's already sticky from the first step.
I don't have anything to eat, so I'm desperate.
I want to get there first.
I shout.
When I get there, it's like this.
You notice it for the first time.
It's like this.
For example, the first stupid cockroach goes like this.
I can't do it anymore.
I can't give up.
It's too fast.
On top of that, the cockroach, cockroach, cockroach.
If you open it, there is a cockroach in the middle.
There are times when there is a cockroach.
My friend is sleeping.
There is a cockroach on top of it.
Really?
What are you doing?
You have to see it first.
I can't do it anymore.
What are you doing?
It's sticky.
What?
Are you okay?
Did I do it?
You should stop.
Shut up.
Are you okay?
Try it.
What are you doing next?
I can't do it anymore.
That was funny.
Do you know this?
What is it?
Where do the shoes of worn shoes go?
I don't know.
There are a lot of people walking.
If it's accumulated from top to bottom, it should be like this.
Where do those shoes go?
That's right.
Everyone is gathering at night.
The shoes are gathering.
Young people.
Young people are gathering.
You can be a leader there.
Gather.
And?
What about the long boots?
You can talk about various things.
When did you come?
Where were you born?
I'm a slipper.
Are you serious?
There are people walking in slippers.
I don't treat slippers well.
You don't treat them well?
I don't treat them well.
Do they disappear somewhere?
They gather at night.
They gather and become Hamamura Jun's shoes.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you.
What are you going to do?
I'm going home.
I haven't decided anything yet.
I see.
Don't watch TV.
I was really working hard.
Everyone is working hard.
Thank you for your hard work.
Thank you.