On the 3rd episode of Gaki no Tsukai, Chikichiki, Nakibokuro, Okamoto, Kojine Tokai Saksen!
This is the 3rd episode of our show. I think this is the first time.
I always get thrown out at the first episode.
Let's take a look at the goods.
Ta-da!
This is the goods for today.
It's finished nicely.
Today, we're going to look at the bigger ones.
How much have you changed today?
This jumper was quite expensive.
It was about 20,000 yen.
In total, it was about 25,000 yen.
Where are the other 5,000 yen?
We've prepared a lot of things for you.
Thank you.
You look cool.
Wow, look at his belly!
Look at his chest!
What a dirty body!
Look at his underwear!
He's wearing nice underwear.
Gyo-san, you smell like Trunks.
Look at his eyes!
Nice!
This is nice.
You look cool.
As a member of the society, I borrowed this from Yasu-san.
Let's look at this one.
He looks cool.
He looks like an artificial human.
Good, good.
Take your time.
You look cool!
Wow!
I want to go to the bathroom.
I want to go to the bathhouse.
How about this one?
It looks like Kyoko Kishida.
It's a bit funky.
Can you say, good morning?
Thank you.
Wow, you look cool.
You look twice as good as I thought.
You look like a stylist.
What is this?
You look like Machiko Machi.
You have a hand like this.
I can't see your face.
Wow, you look cool!
This is nice.
Can you play something on the guitar?
What do you want me to do?
Can you play Alice?
You look like Inazuma.
Good morning.
I don't know if our sense of coordination is good or not.
That's right.
We have a judge.
Let's see if this is good.
Thank you.
That's all we can do.
But Okamoto-kun did it too.
He did it too.
The manager is Okamoto-kun's mother.
Hey, you should behave yourself.
It's a funky school.
You didn't go to college to do this, did you?
Yes.
I want to thank my mother for raising me.
I'll do my best in this school.
You didn't go to college to do this.
Ladies and gentlemen.
Everyone is quite an adult.
Although I'm an idiot.
This is the most difficult age.
What are you talking about?
I'm serious.
How old are these people?
22 or 23.
This is the most difficult age.
You were laughing a lot.
With a light touch.
You're laughing.
If I were a high school student, I would laugh like this.
No, no, no.
It's enough to laugh like this.
I'm just saying.
It's a difficult time.
Everyone is shining.
You don't have to worry about yourself.
Everyone has worries.
I have a lot of worries.
I don't have any worries.
What are your worries?
I'm worried about my family.
Your family?
I got it.
Your family smells bad.
It's a smelly house.
It's not the smell of the house.
It's the smell of the house.
It's not that smelly.
It's smelly.
You have a smelly house.
I said it's a smelly house.
It's a smelly house.
I also put on my school uniform.
You don't have to worry about your school uniform.
It's a smelly house.
Everyone is wearing a school uniform.
I'm sorry.
When my parents and my father became blind,
the smell came out.
Electricity, bang!
It's the smell that was generated by the chopsticks.
Is my own smell the same as my family's smell?
That's right.
However, because there were four families,
the energy is amazing.
The house is excited.
I was wondering what it was.
You, really.
It's rude.
But everyone thinks so.
So if you get married and have a family,
you can create a new smell.
Furthermore,
I don't know if it will be even more powerful.
And the strange thing is that the taste of water is also different.
Depending on the house?
Depending on the house.
I don't care about the water in my house even if it's tap water.
I can't drink it well.
The water in that house is different.
I understand.
Also, the rice balls held by the mother of the person
are very strange.
Uncertain about appetite.
I understand that, but
the mother of the person over there also holds it beautifully.
It's not bad or smelly.
I don't like it.
I don't care about the mother of my child.
I don't care about the mother of my child at all.
That's not a woman.
I don't like the mother of my child.
Why?
It's good that someone studied it properly.
Why do people eat the same thing and live the same life?
Why is the smell different depending on the house?
I don't know.
It's a mystery.
So look,
There are people who get married to their friends' sister or younger sister.
I don't know about that.
Your sister smells like you, so I can't do anything about it.
What do you call this smell?
It's a very unique smell.
Why is it unique?
To put it simply, it's the smell of your house.
Why?
Is that so?
I don't know.
Your house smells like dried grass.
I don't know about that.
Why does it smell like dried grass?
Didn't you worry about such a thing in the past?
About such a thing?
Why am I such a little bastard?
I don't worry about such a thing.
Everyone worries about it.
I don't worry about it.
I'm big.
Do you worry about such a thing?
There was a time when I was worried about it.
I thought I would be smaller than others.
Now that I think about it, I don't worry about such a thing at all.
There are times when I was worried about it.
Is that so?
Yes, there are.
I think there are a lot of girls.
What kind of girls?
Girls worry about their nipples.
It's like a girl.
What's wrong with your nipples?
Do you have a nipple?
Some girls have a pretty long nipple.
Some girls have a long nipple.
They have a long nipple.
Their nipples look like indica.
And there is a tip of the nipple.
It looks like a coffee bean.
He said, bring me some coins, I'm about to get bored of this.
He's so desperate.
Yeah, I'm worried about that too.
Everyone's like, eat this!
I'm sure you've thought about this before, in the midst of this conversation.
Well, it's the other half of today's guest.
The show we did the other day was totally different, but
People often tell me that the guy from Kiko is a liar.
Yeah, that's true.
Kiko is a liar, right?
It's true.
He's not going to do something like that with our characters, is he?
That's right, I have a character called Mr. Maric.
When I was called by him, I definitely thought I was going to break up with him on a live broadcast.
I hate him so much.
I don't think he's going to fall.
I hate him so much that I can't move.
He does this.
He has a lot of energy here.
I have a lot of energy too.
But when I was called by him, I had this much energy from training.
Just by doing this, I have a lot of energy here.
And then...
I'm not fooling around.
No, no, no.
It's strange.
He said, do you feel it?
I don't know.
I felt like there was some air coming in.
I feel it too.
What?
At that time?
No, no, even now.
I know it's there.
Don't say that.
Hey!
It's true.
Do it.
I have this much energy here.
It's not like that.
He was waiting like this.
I pushed him like this.
And he was returning it like this.
Let's do it again.
This is wood.
Wow, it's strong!
It's strong, isn't it?
I'm going to write a letter to His Majesty.
This is wood.
It's strong.
Well...
What is it?
It's not enough.
You guys are a little crazy these days.
My power is getting worse than before.
I used to be a little more affectionate.
I don't like your stupidity now.
I'm going to punch you.
Why do you have a good ratings?
I can't feel the phenomenon of comedy at all.
If it goes on like this, Japanese TV will be made fun of by foreigners.
Please do something about it.
You can do whatever you want.
I don't know about the drama the other day, but...
The drama the other day...
The live-action version, right?
The ratings were pretty good.
Knowing that, I'm going to do it on TV.
I'm not confident anymore.
Why?
The day I got that kind of ratings...
You're definitely more interesting than a man.
What?
Is that so?
Sakai-san.
Sakai-san from the drama the other day.
He said he saw it.
It's there.
Get out of here.
It's about a third of it.
It's there.
That's right.
That's not right.
He said he saw it.
Well, this is...
But he didn't see the previous one.
What did he see, Sakai-san?
Boom!
Did you just hear that?
It's not like he saw the previous one.
It's like he wanted to see someone who was in it.
Right?
Who did he want to see?
Sakuma-san.
Sakuma-san?
He's always like that.
That's right.
Sakuma-san.
He's always like that.
He's the one who came out the earliest.
Watsuko Asano was with Sazae-san.
Right?
And Takuma...
What was Takuma again?
Shin?
Takuma-san and Shin?
Who was it?
Masuo-san.
Oh, this Masuo-san.
Right?
Why?
Eh?
Ikariya?
Ikaria-san?
Ikaria-san isn't said much.
Ikaria-san is pretty good.
He's a nice guy.
What about you?
Yoshiyuki Kazuko-san?
Ah, yes.
Ah, Yoshiyuki Kazuko-san.
That person too.
Well, well, well.
I like her.
I don't have anyone else.
Eh?
What about you, Seiroji? Norisuke-san?
Ah, Norisuke-san.
What about you, Taigo-san?
Eh?
Kokusho?
What's Kokusho?
Ah, the big guy with the big face!
Ah!
Ah, yes.
This is different.
It's different, right?
It's different, it's different.
Takuma Shin is, well, around here,
in terms of artistic history,
even if you think about it after coming out,
you still have to do Tara-chan.
It's still too early for Matsuho-san.
It's too early.
Eh, who is it? Takuma?
Takuma, what?
Shin?
No, no!
That's not it!
No!
In the other day,
in the video,
there was an amazing film,
titled The Young Master of History,
The Young Master of Alps.
Even now,
I continue to make this series.
The Young Master of Wood is
It is said that it is a ULUWA video, but what kind of story is it?
I do not know.
Even if it is said that it is the young minister of the Ereki series, I do not know what to do.
Who is it? Who does not know what to do?
The young minister of Ereki came from over there.
I do not know what to do.
No, I do not see it.
Thank you. Thank you. The young minister of Ereki.
And?
It's cold.
What are you talking about?
But I want to make a movie someday.
What kind of movie do you want to make?
I want to make a Godzilla movie.
Godzilla vs. King Ghidorah.
I'm tired of Godzilla. Godzilla vs. Yonezuke.
I do not see it.
Why?
Godzilla.
Who is watching Yonezuke?
Godzilla and Yonezuke are not fighting.
I do not see it.
I often see it.
Why do you think the girl who has a tan looks like she will do it soon?
I see.
I do not see it.
Do you think she will do it soon?
She is a little bit of a cheater.
Listen to me.
Yes.
Hanage is in Japan.
I have been watching Hanage all the time.
There was a check before the show.
Matsumoto said that Hanage is in Japan.
But I could not do anything.
I could not do anything.
I have been watching it.
I did not see it.
I do not see it.
If you are in the video, you should be in the video.
This is not Hanage.
This is Hanage.
This is...
It is really like this.
I do not care about this.
There is no one who has a tan today.
But I think it is better not to have a tan as a girl.
I do not think it is good.
Do you think it is cool?
I think so.
There are more men with long hair.
Yes.
That is from Yosuke Eguchi.
Is that so?
He was doing radio in Higashino, Imada.
Yosuke Eguchi was doing radio before them.
He came to Higashino, Imada from Yosuke Eguchi.
The radio was connected to Higashino, Imada after a little cross-talk.
Yosuke Eguchi said, I do not know Higashino, Imada.
What are you doing?
You should have said that.
I think Yosuke Eguchi is strong.
He looks strong, but he should not have said that.
You should have said that.
You should not have said that.
That is...
That is not good.
You should not have said that because you do not know.
You used to have a bad face.
I used to have a bad face too.
But...
You should not have said that.
I do not care.
They often wear hats.
What is that round thing on the top of the hat?
That is...
It is called a round thing.
That is a hat.