Dantan's Gaki no Tsukai ga Arai Nde
It's started
The first episode of Gaki no Tsukai ga Arai Nde
Chikitsuki nice control
Hocke Hocke
It's raining
Today's product is amazing
Today we have prepared a prize
Please take a look
Like this
Is it like this?
It's like this
It has to be inside this frame
After that, as a punishment game
The one who loses will have to write on his face
It's like this
This is the 5th round
The first prize is a cordless phone
It's a wonderful prize
I don't need anything
Gaki no Tsukai ga Arai Nde
Chikitsuki
Let's go
The one who gets the cordless phone
Don't come out
I'm going
If you come out even a little
I have to give you a gold ball
Can I get a gold coin?
The one who loses will have to write on his face
You don't do it
If you come out
It's your fault
I'm tired
It hurts
The third prize is a game
It's dangerous
It hurts
Let's go
Let's go to the second round
I'll accept it
I don't like it
It hurts
It's no good
What's the punishment?
The one who loses will have to write on his face
Buy 10 ice coffee
Wait
I don't know
What is ice coffee?
It's canned coffee
It's 110 yen now
Thank you
Sorry
It's not me
The third prize is
What does it mean?
You can't go to the middle
Here?
I can go
I think I can go
It's dangerous
The fourth prize is
It's no good
Why are you laughing?
It stinks
Let's go to the next one
It still stinks
It smells like a gorilla
I think I can go
Go
It's close
I don't know
I don't want to go
The last one
The last prize is
If it's a diamond, will you edit it?
I want to say that at the meeting
It's close
It's bent
It is not dirty
Please do it
What are you doing?
What?
It's a car!
Hey, hey!
What?
You shouldn't ride it!
No, the ceiling...
No, the ceiling is fine!
I'll just ignore the ceiling.
I've never done this before, so I don't know what to do.
Huh?
What?
Who's riding it?
I'm not riding it!
Ladies and gentlemen.
Hello.
Well...
Let's go.
Your fans are here again.
Well...
I love you.
Is that so?
I don't love you at all.
That's not how it works in the world.
You still look like you're going to say something.
I've been looking at you for a while now.
You're wearing a collar like this?
That's fine.
No, it's not like that.
You know what?
No, no.
She's my fan.
That hurts.
So I'm going to hurt her a little bit.
This is something that's allowed.
You can't say that.
But it's this kind of clothes.
It's cute.
It's not cute at all.
So even if I had a role,
I'm supposed to tell a lot of people.
But...
That's not true.
You don't tell people when they're stupid.
I'm already stupid for wearing this kind of clothes.
To an amateur.
If you're a weak-minded person,
you'll be depressed.
I've been watching the show.
I'm going to write a letter.
I'm going to go see the mirror.
I'm going to wear a collar.
I'm going to open the door.
I thought it was this.
That's what the talent said.
What are you saying?
I was told that.
I'm going to go see the mirror.
So.
Stop shaking when you see the mirror.
There's still a different outfit.
It depends on the person.
You can't do this.
Hello, Kei-chan.
How was the show today?
Did you have fun?
What are you drinking?
Stop it.
Don't drink sleeping pills like this.
Don't say such harsh things to an amateur.
I'm not.
I'm laughing.
That's good, isn't it?
Hey.
That may be the moment when the candles go out.
It's okay.
Why are you laughing so much?
Stop it.
So.
That's it.
What is it?
Well.
Don't say such things.
Let's do the show.
Again.
It's a story.
I want to do this show soon.
Is that so?
I'm thinking about it.
With Gyo-san again?
With Gyo-san.
You've been doing it all night, haven't you?
Sometimes.
Yes.
I haven't done it once since this time.
If you say so.
Is that so?
Yes.
I want to do something.
I wonder how many people will come.
Yes.
I'm doing it once.
Have you decided the number of people so far?
I've decided.
1,000 people.
Yes.
It's a time that even people with school can come.
You're annoying.
Why are you doing this?
I'm not feeling well.
I have a lot of phlegm.
And.
I have a lot of dandruff.
You're about to die.
When cats are about to die.
I have a lot of dandruff.
Is that so?
You're going to die.
I don't want to be away from people.
Cats die somewhere.
Somewhere I don't know.
I have a lot of dandruff in the middle.
It's terrible.
I want to be away from people.
I think I'm going to die.
I don't know how I'm going to die.
Hey.
I think I'm going to die.
Everyone thinks I'm laughing.
I don't know how I'm going to die.
If you open it, it's going to come out like this.
I'm scared.
What I'm often told is that I'm going to die in an accident in a car.
That's the coolest thing.
Is there anything cool?
I don't have such a beautiful face.
I'm going to die with a beautiful face.
I think I'm going to die with a smile and a calm face.
I'm going to die in an accident in a second, but I can't laugh.
I'm going to die in a second, but I can't laugh.
I don't have anything to remember.
So no matter how big the accident is, when I open the crown.
Are you still planning to die?
I'm not planning anything.
Your face is like a cherry blossom.
It's a calm face.
Let's break it again.
I'm going to open the crown.
Look, look, look.
Your eyes are open.
My eyes are open.
I'm scared.
What kind of face is that?
I have a calm face.
A calm face?
I have an angel-like face.
Look at it.
No, no, no.
It's different.
What?
It's no good.
If you have such eyes.
I have a boy-like eyes.
That's no good.
I'm not dead.
You're not dead either.
No, no, no.
I don't care about that story.
What is it?
Well, I'm not a prophet.
I'm planning.
Why are you talking about planning?
I'm going to gather a lot of people and see what to do.
I see.
What about the place?
What are you going to do next?
I'm going to gather unlimitedly.
I don't know how many people will come.
I'm going to go to a pretty big place next time.
That's right.
What are you going to do?
Gather a lot of people.
What can you do with a lot of people?
I don't know what you're going to do next time.
There was the opinion that you would gather a lot of people and join hands with them.
I'm going to bring it.
What are you going to do?
I don't know if I'm going to bring it.
What do you do with a lot of people?
Do you want to do a concert?
Hello, Bachchan, Hama-chan.
Good evening.
There was an interesting song in the middle school student songbook, so please take a look.
Kanon, Kanon.
It has a very good meaning.
I see.
The fly came, the fly came.
Crush it before you get stabbed.
The sky has come again.
The fly came.
This is a tough scene, isn't it?
Probably, the fly came, the fly came.
Crush it before you get stabbed.
The sky has come again.
The fly came.
It's a very pop feeling, isn't it?
It has a very good meaning.
I can understand the atmosphere.
Can you sing it?
Well...
The fly came...
You should be pop now.
Kanon, you...
You are a fool.
What?
The Hungarian Mion is like that.
At first, it gradually becomes pop.
Don't say such a strange thing.
I'll fly you from the beginning.
The fly came.
Crush it before you get stabbed.
The sky has come again.
The Hungarian Mion is like that.
At first, it gradually becomes pop.
Crush it before you get stabbed.
The fly came.
The sky has come again.
You should be pop now.
At first, it gradually becomes pop.
The fly came.
Crush it before you get stabbed.
The sky has come again.
You are a princess, aren't you?
Yes.
Where did you get excited?
The fly came again.
You should be pop now.
It hurts.
You hurt me.
Send me the song.
It doesn't matter if it's a record or tape.
It doesn't matter if it's a tape or tape.
If the whole world became yours, what would you do first?
This is a common story.
If all mankind were destroyed and you were the only one left.
I don't think so.
Why?
It's fun to be alone.
This is all yours.
It's all yours.
That's right.
You can park your car as much as you want.
It doesn't matter if it's a small thing.
You can drive with your feet.
I can do it.
No one is talking to me.
No one is talking to you.
I don't think you're on TV.
No one is talking to me.
You are on TV.
What?
Are you watching me?
I'm not watching you.
What kind of world do you want to conquer?
I don't care what happens.
In your case,
Don't you think so?
What?
What's going to happen?
No matter what kind of question you ask,
If your wish comes true,
If you can be a transparent person.
No matter what you say,
You only think about death.
A transparent person is a transparent person who can pass through the wall.
It's not like that.
It's just invisible.
I see.
It's invisible, but it's hard to be a transparent person.
If you're a transparent person who can pass through the wall,
It's hard to be a transparent person.
Why?
Because it's transparent.
I thought it felt good, so I thought I'd touch it.
But there's nothing.
You can't touch it.
I can't.
I don't have to worry about it.
Why?
You have to think about this.
If you think about it,
You can pass through.
It's okay.
It's okay to pass through.
It's okay at this time, but you can't wear clothes in winter.
It's not transparent as it is.
It's transparent.
Then you're a transparent person.
It's transparent tie.
It's transparent.
It's okay if you disappear as it is.
Then you have to wear clothes like this.
It's okay.
It's invisible.
It stinks.
I can't see anything, but it stinks.
It stinks here.
I can't break it.
You'll be found out.
He's here again.
Who is he?
It's transparent.
It's hard.
It's okay if you're a quiet person in winter.
How can I be quiet?
I don't have an apartment.
You can go to someone's house.
Even if I go to someone's house, I can't get in because the door isn't open.
That's why you should follow the person on the road.
I can't get in.
I can't close it so fast.
The door is open.
It's open like this.
I see.
I can't do that.
Even if you get it right, no one will know that it's transparent.
It's strange, when you enter a house.
So, it's not like that.
The whole world will be yours.
Ah, then, I got it.
Humanity will all perish.
I don't like that.
So, you are left.
There's only one person left.
Well, if that's the case, then that's the case.
I don't need a man.
Why don't you need a man?
Isn't that right?
Are you going to have a man?
A horse?
Eh?
What are you doing?
Even more so.
The train doesn't run anymore.
The bus doesn't run either.
The cars don't run either.
Humanity will all perish.
What are you going to do with a horse?
If that's the case, then that's the case.
Ha!
What are you in a hurry for?
If you're the only one who doesn't perish,
then why don't you just die?
What is this?
Why don't you walk slowly?
Ha!