Next time, at Gaki no Tsukai, Chiki Chiki! Yamasaki Happy Project!
The real me is interesting!
Matsumoto-san, I don't understand the meaning.
I don't understand the meaning.
It's just that, Gaki no Tsukai, let's do our best with the four of us.
Yamaguchi-san also dropped it.
He dropped it?
It can't be helped.
Oh, it came out! A genius comedian!
A genius comedian came out!
That means there's only one.
Hamada-san also said it, but I don't really understand today's meaning.
To be honest, I talked about it with one person before.
At that time, the reputation was pretty bad.
First of all, Adachi's...
If you sympathize with me, give me money!
Don't get cold!
You're a weirdo too!
He raised his own lack of talent and ran away from the stage.
Yamazaki wanted to make his image worse because he worked as a comedian.
I've been in the industry for a long time, and I'm getting less and less work.
Seriously!
I'm not kidding.
My image is pretty bad.
I've been thinking about a lot of things to improve my image today.
A genius comedian appears!
I'm not kidding!
This program is provided by the sponsor you see.
Basically, I'm going to have a big party with you guys.
I'm going to have a big party with you guys.
Everyone, please stand me up.
What do you mean?
So, for example, there are times when you give me an interesting answer.
I'll decide the answer to that question.
You're going to say something like this?
Yes.
I'm going to do a rehearsal and decide everything.
Only the people I like are coming today.
Only the people I like?
The people I like...
The people who like me.
What are you doing?
It's an image-up strategy.
Why don't we cooperate?
We're definitely going to slip, aren't we?
We're definitely going to slip.
I don't want to do that.
You can't do that if you're laughed at?
I won't do that.
Really?
Let's do a rehearsal.
Everyone is so excited.
But...
In the end, he was forced to do it.
He couldn't accept it, so he went to the rehearsal where Yamazaki was acting.
You're saying a rehearsal in a big way.
Mr. Matsumoto is number one.
Tanaka is number two.
En is number three.
All of them are in the house.
Well, well, well.
Are you going to be in this order?
Yes.
And this is the clothes.
What do you mean?
Everyone, this is the moss green one.
It's plain.
It's a color that's hard to understand.
Is that pink you?
Yes, it's me.
I'm a little pink.
Do you all wear the same color?
The same color.
There's a flower.
Let's start with a head greeting.
You don't have your own opinion, do you?
No, I don't have my own opinion.
Excuse me, this is Mr. Hamada's comment.
This isn't a comment.
You can't say this.
No, I can't.
Please say that.
Yes, I'll do it.
Bokuchin.
Mr. Matsumoto, when you say something, it's bokuchin.
All the time.
When you're talking about yourself.
Bokuchin.
Bokuchin recently learned how to cook.
He wanted to make a hot dog.
He warmed up the dog.
This is Mr. Matsumoto.
Yes.
Next.
The other day, I was walking around town.
There was a very sexy vehicle running.
Wow, it's a train.
You're always frowning.
I'm always frowning?
It's very embarrassing.
You're very nervous.
Just a little bit.
A little bit?
Why?
I'm always looking down.
Look down.
You're very excited.
I'm very excited?
Hello, turtle.
Last Friday, I had a job in Osaka.
I'm Endo Shouzo.
Really?
Why?
Am I very excited?
Yes, you're very excited.
You're full of confidence.
Really?
Yes.
And then...
I'm a comedian.
I don't get angry at all.
Even if I'm handed over, I'm in trouble.
Hey, wait.
I'm your junior.
I've always wanted to say this.
And then I say,
Wow, here it comes.
Hirokawa Yakushibara.
And then...
And then Hamada-san's...
Which one?
Are you a genius?
And then...
Hit him hard.
Are you a genius?
And then...
I'm a genius.
I don't want to do this.
What is the funny story that Arnold Schwarzenegger said?
What is the funny story that Shuga-chan said?
Can you think about this for a moment?
Yes.
Hmm...
I can't eat anymore.
I'm speaking Japanese.
I'm a foreigner.
What is the funny story that Arnold Schwarzenegger said?
I put my butt out in Terminator 1.
I'll say that in the show.
What?
Even if you don't stop me, what is this?
What I'm talking about right now...
You all think about it.
Are you lying?
I'm not lying.
Isn't that Matsumoto-san?
Isn't that the answer to Matsumoto's answer?
It's not a bag!
It's not a bag?
It's not a bag.
It's a document.
That's a document.
I'll say this in the actual show.
A reference document.
But Yamazaki-san, if you don't get any, it's over with just one, right?
That's right.
Then, I'll end it with this one.
This.
I can't eat anymore.
This is Matsumoto-san.
Wait a minute.
I can't eat anymore.
I see.
Yes.
What's the funny thing that Shua-chan said?
Why don't you look it up on P.E.A.R.?
This is a bit funny.
Should I say that?
Shua-chan must have heard it.
Probably, from someone.
What about you, Do-san?
No, I'll take it.
Huh? You'll take it?
Yeah.
Huh? I don't have anything to say, right?
You're on vacation this time.
Vacation?
What do you mean, vacation?
Tanaka only says it once.
No, Tanaka doesn't say it once.
The viewers either cut it out or couldn't eat it.
What are you talking about?
Wait a minute.
I can't eat anymore.
Matsumoto-san's answer is
Yamazaki's idea of a vacation tomorrow.
Endo's answer is
to see if we can see this.
And the delicious Yamazaki,
Hama-chan's answer is
BAM!
After the BAM!
What do you want me to say?
Um...
Don't apply to the world.
I was a little scared at that time.
It's like a home.
Even if you put on an atmosphere,
You're not here anymore?
I'm not here anymore.
The moment you sit down,
It's fun.
Say it again.
I love you.
I don't really understand the meaning.
It's dangerous.
Everyone's watching TV.
It's okay.
I love you.
I said it again.
What is the last word of the person who fell into the bath?
Matsumoto-san's last word is
Help me.
Tanaka's last word is
Kyah!
Kyah?
It's your first time saying that.
You're hot.
I'm...
This is the last one.
Yamazaki-san's last word is
I'm melting.
And then,
The last is a rehearsal of a joke using things.
Matsumoto-san.
Please.
What is it?
With a file.
Hello.
Use a file.
If you don't say anything, just go.
It's cold.
Sorry.
If you don't say anything, just go.
It's cold.
Sorry.
You say, too.
Say, too.
But I can't hear it at all.
What?
I can't hear it at all.
You can't hear it at all, but you're using a file?
I'm...
I'm resting.
Are you still thinking about it here?
But, in a sense, it's fine.
I want to do that, too.
Just go.
If you take this with you, your legs will...
You have a good one.
And then,
Yamazaki's enthusiastic fans fill up the venue.
Yamazaki Image Up's big strategy is in the second half of the show.
Ladies and gentlemen.
I have some sad news.
What is it?
I'm sorry to disturb your excitement.
Today's opening is almost 20 minutes long.
The talk section is 5 or 6 minutes long.
I don't give a shit.
The closing time is about 5 minutes.
I'll take it back.
What a voice.
I don't give a shit.
I was so angry last night.
About what?
You didn't do the laundry, did you?
By myself?
Yeah.
I didn't.
You didn't, did you?
You didn't, so I couldn't tell.
I was so angry.
Why?
You did the laundry, didn't you?
Of course, I'll do it myself.
No, no.
I'm serious.
I don't care, but you're so energetic.
Who are you talking to?
I'm going to take it out of the dryer.
What the hell is that?
Your underwear is upside down.
Do you understand?
You did that before you put it in the dryer?
No, I don't like that.
I always take it out when I take it out.
I do it gently.
I always do it, but when I take it out of the dryer, it's upside down.
5 out of 6 are upside down.
Your shirt is upside down, too.
What do you think about that?
It turns when I wash it.
It does.
It turns like this.
Your underwear and shirt are upside down?
It's upside down at that point.
It's okay if it's upside down, but why is it upside down again?
Why does it end upside down at the end?
I don't know.
I thought you were wearing pajamas in the dark, but you were wearing it upside down.
I thought you were wearing it upside down, but you were wearing it upside down.
Mr. Matsumoto, you can imitate anything.
Please imitate the next three people who threw a spoon at the croquette.
The croquette threw a spoon.
Are you ready?
Akira Takarada
Can you do it?
Yes, I can.
Please do it.
Akira Takarada
There are a lot of people who run away in the cold, but I hate it, so I'll do it from the beginning.
But before that, I'd like to ask Keisuke Kuwata.
Wait a minute.
What does that have to do with anything?
It's not like I can do this.
Okay.
I hate it. I hate it. I hate it.
Thank you.
This is the main subject.
Akira Takarada, Koro Inagaki, and Mr. Okada.
Please do it.
Before we do this, I'd like to ask Keisuke Kuwata.
Stop it!
Listen to me first.
I can't do it.
You can't do it?
Wow, that's cool.
Do you think you can do it?
I'll teach you.
Keisuke Kuwata, you're a lovely person who stays in my heart.
I don't know how to say it.
Sing first.
It's number two.
What do you mean by number two?
I'm number one, so I'm number two.
Is that okay?
In the entertainment world,
you gather a lot of impersonators and you're number one and number two.
Number two?
What about number one?
I'm number one.
You're number one is the point, isn't it?
Is that so?
Let's do it.
I'll teach you again.
You're number one, aren't you?
Let's do it.
Let's introduce ourselves one by one.
First, next to me.
I recently learned how to cook.
I wanted to make a hot dog, so I warmed up a dog.
What is it?
My name is Hitoshi Matsumoto.
Nice to meet you.
Next.
Recently, when I was walking around town,
I saw a very sexy vehicle running.
Wow, it's a train.
What is it?
My name is Naoki Tanaka.
Next.
Hello, turtle, turtle.
I had a job in Osaka last Friday.
My name is Shogo Endo.
Why is that?
Nice to meet you.
Last one.
Without laughing...
Without laughing, I'm in trouble.
Oh, here it is.
Yakujimaru Hiroko.
You're a genius, aren't you?
Nice answer.
Happy Kevin.
Next.
From now on, I'll give you a question.
There's a flip-flop in the back.
You'll write the answer on the flip-flop.
The person who gets it will be the winner.
The first question is this.
What is the funny story that Arnold Schwarzenegger told?
Raise your hand if you got it.
Okay.
Okay, Matsumoto.
What is the funny story that Shiwa-chan told?
I can't eat it anymore.
Why?
Next.
Okay.
End.
Can't you see this flip-flop?
Next.
Okay.
Okay, Matsumoto.
What is the funny story that Shiwa-chan told?
Tomorrow is a long trip. I'm happy.
Why?
Okay.
Yamazaki-san.
What is the funny story that Shiwa-chan told?
Okay.
I got my ass kicked by Terminator 1.
Yamazaki-san.
You'll be famous all over the world.
I got it.
I'm scared.
Next.
You don't have any?
I'll go now.
Okay.
What is the funny story that Shiwa-chan told?
You should look it up on PIA.
I'll get excited if I'm with you.
It's funny. Let's do it again.
Again?
You're crying, aren't you?
The next topic is this.
What is the last word of the person who fell into the water?
Okay, Matsumoto.
The last word of the person who fell into the water.
Help me.
Why?
Okay, next.
Okay.
Oh, Tanaka.
What is the last word of the person who fell into the water?
Why?
That's not a good way to say it.
It's not?
You shouldn't have said that.
It's a waste of time.
Okay, end.
What is the last word of the person who fell into the water?
It's hot.
Why?
Okay.
Okay, Matsumoto.
What is the last word of the person who fell into the water?
I'll melt.
I wish you were my partner.
Who's going to say the pun?
As you can see, I've prepared a lot of things behind me.
Please say the pun using those things.
Okay, let's do it.
Okay, I'll say it.
Okay, Yamazaki-san.
I'll say it using IREBA.
I'm awake.
No, IREBA is over there.
You're good.
I'm counting on you for the big laughter party in Japan.
The big laughter party.
Okay.
Matsumoto-san.
I'll use a file.
Use a file.
Give me a file.
I'll use a file.