The next day
Good morning
Kiyomoto
Yes
Who?
Ats конц, she has another boyfriend
boyfriend
What?
Hayate
Do not know
Still gone
I wonder
Oh, wait
Hey, Hamada.
Can you stop smoking?
Why?
I don't like the smell of the collar.
Turn it off.
He's smoking.
He's cool when he's smoking.
Hello
Eyes though
I'll take it seriously
Is that a woman?
There's nothing wrong with that.
I know.
Yamagaki has been here a few times.
Oh, really?
Eri, do you want some food?
I'm fine.
No, you're not.
Which one?
Tanaka!
Choose one.
You can bring it over here.
Oh, okay.
Which one do you want?
Which one is better?
Then, let's decide which one is the best.
Okay.
Ready, set...
Huh?
It's the same!
The numbers are different.
The numbers are...
Huh?
I think it's a little bit related to the lunch box.
It's not related.
Here.
This?
Oh, there's beef and chicken.
Okay.
Looks delicious.
Please give us a briefing for tonight.
Hello.
Today, we're going to do owner-atelier.
How many times can we do this?
One time?
One time.
For now, we'll do it a few times.
What is this?
So you mean 5 people?
Yes, 5 people.
I think I've done this 50 times.
You went to the Fukuoka festival with me the other day, right?
I took a picture of you.
Really?
Yes. Do you want to see it?
Yes, I want to see it.
Let's see it together.
It's like a miracle.
It hurts.
Amazing.
It's like a miracle.
It's good that you're here.
Well, someone else, put in a different one!
Like Tajima, that kind of guy.
He looks like he can't do it.
It's a question of how to succeed.
That's good.
I was a little scared.
It's like something's coming up.
How many people are there if you put in two?
There are about 40 or 50 people.
Oh, look at this.
I've seen Puget.
Puget.
What are you doing?
I'm standing.
I'm watching the show.
Yesterday I went to the museum and found something really nice.
What is it?
Can you see it?
This.
I'll show you.
What is it?
I wonder what it is.
A present.
Really?
Yes.
Thank you.
Everyone worked hard.
How is it?
Wow, wow, wow.
This is the room.
Wow, it suits you.
Really?
It looks really cute.
It suits you.
I think this is good for the students.
This is perfect for today because it's cold.
It's for 5 people.
It's really good.
This is good.
It's like a girae-sa.
I'm glad.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Thank you.
It's nice.
Then, shall we go to the Super Town?
Yes.
Let's change.
Thank you.
I...
I think I'll go with this.
Why?
I'll go to the toilet.
You'll go to the toilet?
Yes.
It's easier to do it in a jersey.
I'm wearing this because I'm wearing a jersey.
But it's a little weird.
It suits you.
It's a natto so it's easier to wear a jersey.
What do you think?
I think this is good.
I think this suits me.
I don't know if you can change it right away but...
For now, this is good.
In short, you can hold this.
Yes, yes.
Later, yes.
Then, will you see my pocket?
I'll be right there.
Yamaguchi-chan, this is for you.
Where are you going?
I'm going to the toilet.
Oh, really?
What should I do with Eri?
Eri's car...
It's a car, right?
What do you mean?
I want to go with her.
Eri's car is coming, right?
So...
Yamaguchi, can you drive?
No, no, no.
Can you come with me?
I'm going to take the bus with Eri.
I'm going to drive.
No, no, no.
I don't want to go home.
Don't come.
Don't be so funny.
I drive Audi.
I quit smoking.
You quit?
Yes.
Thank you.
And I'm a gambler.
Yes, you're a gambler.
Let's go.
Yes.
Please.
Please take care of me.
What do you do in the movie?
Oh, my cell phone is missing!
Really?
No, what should I do?
It's somewhere in the back, right?
It's not here.
No, I can't go there.
Please, look for it.
It's silver.
No, what should I do?
Endo, look for it.
I can't go there.
Look around.
Tachibana!
Put your phone down!
It's my silver phone!
I'm telling you it's your phone! Why don't you put it down?
Where's the last one?
Ah!
There it is!
Sorry!
Ah, there it is. That's good.
There it is.
Sorry.
That's good.
Let's go, let's go.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
You scared me.
I haven't done so.
Errp.
Dam Phu Yen.
Youanız, I haven't done it before.
Then why would only you and I find it interesting?
Haha...
I really enjoyed it.
So the song has to be heard by last, Matsumoto, at the end...
Yes, yes.
And, for now, let's go to the 50th floor.
The 50th floor.
It's that far?
It looks like a car.
What?
It's cold.
It's 4 degrees, and we're having a meeting.
Hurry up, it's cold.
I'm so stressed out from driving.
So why did you come with us?
They're old people.
Will you come, Azuma-san?
Please.
Azuma-san, it's the 5th floor.
We'll do a meeting, so you'll be the fifth.
Fifth.
The fifth in the order of the meeting.
If you succeed, you'll get 100,000 yen.
Eri and Ton, you know.
Of course, I'll get red.
If it's just the five of us.
I'm sorry.
You're looking at me.
Excuse me, the stand-in.
Mr. Amasawa, please come to the stand-in.
Where am I?
You're lying.
It's not like that.
It's starting.
I'm sorry for wearing it.
I'm sorry. I'll bring it.
I'll take a picture.
Don't touch it!
The first owner's jump competition!
Yay!
Thank you!
Are you ready?
This time, the five of you will go in order.
If you can get 50 times, the prize money will be 100,000 yen.
It's difficult.
It's about the same as a school request.
50 times.
If you succeed, it's 100,000 yen, so each person gets 20,000 yen.
That's right.
I'll do my best!
Thank you!
Alright!
Thank you.
Are you okay?
Are you okay with the opening?
I'm not okay.
Let's start from here.
1, 2, 3, 4.
Mr. Asaba, this way.
This way.
To the left.
Let's go.
Let's start!
Stop it!
Yabachan!
Sorry.
It's okay.
Let's do it properly.
What are you doing?
Matsumoto!
Let's do it!
I'm doing it!
Let's continue!
Please!
One more time!
Let's do it again!
It's delicious!
It's good.
You're not doing it.
The camera is rolling.
I'm doing it!
Let's go.
I'm sorry.
You're too slow.
It's hard.
Wait a minute.
I want to go to the toilet.
Why can't you go in?
I'm sorry.
What is it?
I want to go to the toilet.
You can go.
There is a toilet.
Mr.Soda, please guide him.
She is a girl.
I'm sorry.
I can't let you do that.
Isn't it beautiful?
I'll take you to the toilet.
I'll go with you.
I'm recording.
No, you can't.
Let's do it.
I can't let you go alone.
I'll take you to the hospital.
If you don't feel well, you can go with me.
You'll catch a cold.
Yes, I'll catch a cold.
You're crying.
I'm sorry.
You'll be fine after a while.
I'll take you to the hospital.
What is this?
What should we do?
Where did you go? Did you go to a hotel?
Around the hotel?
You can go to the public toilet there.
I was told that I should think about it.
You were told that you should think about it?
You are a girl.
It's still quite a long way to go.
I think it's about time.
The sun is already setting. It's cold.
We're back.
It's about time.
What should we do? Should we try the same pattern again?
Let's take a picture of the five of us together.
They're not coming back.
What are you doing?
What's going on?
They're fighting.
Why are you fighting? Come back from the front.
the other day
That woman is brazen
oh you the woman
you tried to pick up at the opposite way
you can not do it
фильader
I do not like to
Oh, you've gone back
Yeah, on the contrary
I'm going home
Y hurricane
Tama, please bring him
Yes
Hurry up!
Let's go!
Let's start the show!
What?
Eri is angry
Let's do it
Yes
It's dangerous
Let's start the show
Eri!
Let's go!
Hurry up!
4, 3, 2...
Eri!
Let's go!
Hey, Masumoto!
Masumoto!
Hurry up!
Hey!
Hey, Eri!
Wait a minute!
Masumoto!
Eri?
Where are you?
Sorry about that.
Hey, Masamune-san?
Hello?
Hey!
Eri?
Hello? Hello?
The signal is bad!
Hey! Eri?
Hello?
Hey!
Let's go home.
And I hear your voice
What's this?
This year was the Asian Par-piyon
Hamada is also an Asian Par-piyon
Hamada is also an...
AHHHHHHHHH
You speak to me only.
This year was the Asian Par-piyon
Hamada is also an Asian Par-piyon
But as expected, Mama...
Tama-san, let's wrap it up.
Well, since you guys didn't watch the opening, you probably don't understand it well.
I don't like that kind of thing!
You don't like it?
I don't like it!
But you're embarrassed?
Embarrassed?
Well, that kind of thing is popular right now, right?
What is?
The one who is dating with a talent
They are doing it in many different songs
If I was given that kind of thing, I would not go back
I don't like being sucked into it
I don't like it
Why? You don't know what it is, right?
I can't think of it
And you don't know who will come
I'm sure that I will do it with my grandmother today.
I want to have a good time with her.
Well, you have to do your best from the middle.
You will do it.
I will do it with my grandmother all the time.
Well, this is...
It's difficult.
Why can you do it?
I don't know.
I think you can do it.
I was wearing a cctv in the car and talking to myself.
I was like, I'm going to have an accident.
I'm going to have an accident because I'm scared.
I'm sorry.
I can't do this anymore.
I'll end this.
I'll end this. I'm embarrassed.
I can't think of anything.
But this is a show.
No, no, no, no, no.
I'm not doing this for real.
If the camera follows me like this, I can still do it.
I can work somewhere.
I mean, we're so far away from each other, so if you're walking with your hands in Shibuya, it's not going to work.
I can't even think!
But if you're a regular person, it's impossible.
I'm really, really, I'm sweating.
If you say that, you might get an offer.
No, no, no.
I'm not going anywhere.
I'm telling you, I'm not going anywhere even if I get 100 million yen.
Never!
Why?
You don't want to see me like that, right?
No.
You're not doing that behind my back, are you?
No, no, no.
What do you mean by a date-maker?
It's been a while.
I've been doing this for about two weeks now.
Well, well.
It's fine.
Well, well, I guess I'll stop talking about the show.
It's great.
But, you know, I can't really support it.
I watched a really interesting DVD the other day.
Well, it's an AV.
It's an AV, but it's a documentary.
I'll invite two AV actresses.
He was a famous AV actress who was pooping in front of people.
That sounds interesting.
It's really funny.
I don't like it!
I can't think of anything!
Why?
That's not something you do in front of people.
That child is a good child.
I see.
Actually, Sonoko was bullied when she was a child.
And then she got a little bit traumatized.
She couldn't talk to people because she was so depressed.
To overcome that, she pooped in front of people.
Why?
Why? You think, right?
But that woman said,
I know that, but...
Hey!
I got it!
I got it, you!
And then,
I said,
I'll do it!
And when I said I'll do it,
I said,
What year were you born?
And I looked back at old photos.
I looked back at the old photos!
I looked back at them, you!
In terms of profile?
Like profile photos.
I see.
That kind of stuff comes out.
You're making it up.
Two girls come out, but they end up doing it.
They're doing their makeup beautifully.
The makeup artist does it.
Now they're doing their makeup to poop.
But, you know,
There's no such thing as a straw.
I said, and he was like, I've decided!
He was really excited.
I see.
There was a red carpet with carpet lights.
Two people came out.
That's right.
There were about 30 people.
They were clapping.
And there was a stage in the middle.
The stage was really crowded.
It was like this.
It was amazing, right?
It looked interesting.
The first girl who was doing it in love said,
Well then, I'll do it.
But I was so nervous that I couldn't do it.
I thought, I couldn't do it.
The next girl who had to do it,
was watching it from the front.
I see.
I couldn't do it.
I don't know what she thought.
The next girl who did it said,
Do your best!
If you do that, the other guests will also say,
Go with all your might!
There are other ways!
And then, on the way, they'll start crying.
Saying, I can't do it!
I'm already this cool.
I can't do it.
Then, the director will say,
If you don't come out, it's like starting a new year tomorrow.
What?
And then, the second one.
The second one was just saying that he'll do his best.
He was full of motivation.
And then, all of a sudden...
Hmm...
Pooh!