In the first episode, we'll show you how to get rid of badminton with the help of kids!
It's so cold!
Badminton is something you can do at this time of the year.
That's right.
It warms you up.
I'm Kikuchi Otajima.
Mr. Downtown and Mr. Kokoriko are going to have a badminton match.
We can be Kokoriko.
You don't have to count.
I'll be like Doki.
No, no, no.
I'll show you how to do it.
If you say that, it'll get worse.
It'll get worse.
Mr. Otajima, if you get 15 points, you win.
Okay.
Let's get started.
That's enough for today, right?
That's enough.
What do you mean?
You're standing normally.
It's okay.
Do you want to touch each other?
Please touch me.
Okay.
Let's start with Kokoriko.
Please.
Let's talk about something funny.
You're so funny.
A good story from Mr. Kawada.
This program is brought to you by the sponsors of the five groups.
Okay, let's start the Badminton Tournament.
Okay.
Good.
100,000 yen.
Okay.
Let's go.
Good.
Okay.
He's winning.
He's still winning.
Good.
Wait a minute.
Is the sound okay?
It's okay.
You can do it.
Let's go.
Good.
It's hot.
It's a tie.
Okay.
It's cold.
It's a tie.
Is the sound okay?
Wait a minute.
It's cold.
Why are you still singing at this time?
Because I have a smile on my face.
Oh, this is Itao.
It's Itao.
Itao.
What are you doing?
Good morning.
Itao suddenly appeared at the recording site of the game.
What is his purpose?
What's wrong?
I'm having a hard time right now.
It's cold at this time of the year.
Are you sleeping?
There are many people who exercise.
There are many people today.
I'm sorry, but the camera is facing this way.
Yes.
The camera is in the back.
This is the only place I can go around.
Why?
Really?
I think Itao will understand.
When I exercise, I have a smile on my face.
I understand that.
But my life is on the line.
If I don't sell it, I'll be in trouble.
How many did you sell?
I only have about 10 left.
Is it limited to 10?
Yes, it's limited.
I can't make it.
Tsugawa-san, did you make it?
I can't help it.
Do you want to eat it?
That's right.
I'll give you the rest.
Really?
Yes.
I'll give it to you.
Really?
Thank you very much.
10 packs?
10 packs.
How much is it?
It's 1,000 yen per pack.
It's expensive.
Isn't it expensive?
But the time is the time.
That's why it's strange.
That's why I can't sell it.
If it's 10 packs, is it 10,000 yen per pack?
It's 10,000 yen per pack.
It's a little expensive.
Thank you very much.
It's sold out.
This is 10,000 yen.
I understand. Thank you very much.
I'm sorry.
No, no.
I'm sorry I sold it.
Good luck.
Thank you very much.
It's 1,000 yen.
It's sold out.
What are you going to do if you sell it?
I want to sell it at a very high speed.
I don't want to sell it.
It's fast.
It's dangerous in the park.
Please be careful.
Let's go.
What are you doing?
Good job.
That was good.
It's a wind.
Good job.
Wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
Bowling.
Round.
How about a bowling ball?
Bowling.
I'm sorry.
Why didn't you stop there?
Bowling.
I was there.
I told you not to stop here.
But I stopped here anyway.
I have to wait.
What are you selling?
Bowling.
It's not selling.
Who are you to say it's not selling?
That's a good thing.
It's not selling.
Did it sell?
There's no hole.
There's no hole?
You can raise it however you want.
It's like this.
How many kilograms is this?
It's impossible.
It's slippery.
It's impossible for an amateur.
It's not like that.
It's good to raise it little by little.
How much is this?
It's 5,000 yen.
It's expensive.
But it's a little expensive.
That's right.
But this is also a business.
I can't make a living if I'm just a comedian.
I think it's a bad product to go with this.
But you have to open the hole for yourself.
You don't know how it feels when you get a strike for the first time.
Try it once.
You'll get addicted to it.
You can raise it as many times as you want.
How many times do I have to raise it?
You can't stop it.
What should I do with the board?
Should I put it here?
That's right.
No matter how many times you raise it.
How many are left?
You have to sell two or three.
There's still a lot left.
Six?
I don't know.
It's 33,000 yen.
I don't know if it's expensive.
I can't think of anything.
If it was Yamazaki, it would be a great picture.
It's light.
Is it a plus driver?
It says so.
I don't think it's going to open.
I don't think it's a good picture.
How is it?
It's not over yet.
It's almost over.
That's right.
Mr. Ito, I'd like to buy this.
Really?
Yes, six.
Six?
It's 5,000 yen, right?
Yes.
That's it for today.
That's right.
It's gone.
Yes.
Thank you very much.
That's right.
Please make an opening.
Thank you very much.
It's 60,000 yen.
60,000 yen.
If you buy it, it's 30,000 yen.
Yes.
It's too early to go home.
Thank you very much.
It's not a rally.
It's a rally.
Come on.
OK.
It's amazing.
It's super good.
It's a Super Good.
I agree.
Really.
It's amazing.
Thank you very much.
Koshiba?
Yes.
This is Unfortunately.
Was it in the picture the heater with firewood?
It's a problem.
That's enough, Dao-san.
Please.
What is this ranking?
What is this?
What do you think?
It's a family photo.
What's wrong with this photo?
This is a collection of various things.
If you'd like, there's more.
Take a look.
There's a lot.
Can you sell this?
What is this?
What's wrong with not being your own family?
Who is this?
This is Machida-san.
Do you know him?
No, I don't know him.
Mino-san is sold out.
There's a lot.
What do you think of this?
This is taken by someone else.
That's right.
By the way, how much is this?
If it's around here, it's 10,000 yen.
There's a price tag, too.
15,000 yen.
That's a lot.
1,000 yen.
3,000 yen.
That one is really blue.
Oh, this one?
I like that one.
This is a little...
I can't sell this.
This is something I cherish.
Is this Itao's?
This is mine.
This is something I cherish.
This isn't for sale.
Thank you, but can you sell this?
I can sell it when I can, but I can't sell it today.
I don't know what to do.
I'll have to work a little harder.
I think I'll have to work harder.
Even if you work hard, you can sell it.
I'll do my best.
Even if you work hard, you can't sell it.
If this picture comes out at 5 o'clock, it'll be sold out.
Can you still sell it at 5 o'clock?
I can't be a target.
I can sell all of this.
Wait a minute.
There's a price tag.
There's a price tag of about 5,000 yen.
I'll give you a service.
This one.
I don't know anything.
I'll do it.
Really?
This is 5,000 yen.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me, this is a little rude.
Excuse me, I'll take it.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me, thank you very much.
Good luck.
Excuse me for disturbing you.
Thank you very much.
Excuse me.
Let's get our spirits back.
Let's go.
It's cold.
Go.
Thank you very much.
I'm blowing the whistle.
It's the same score again.
OK.
I'm counting on you.
Go.
OK.
Nice.
This one.
You're good.
It's a rally.
Good.
How was it?
What do you think of a young man who is 150 cm to 175 cm tall?
I can't stop there.
It's best to stop here.
What is this?
I don't know anything.
It's a young man.
What do you think of a young man?
Young man?
Young man of a comedian?
Young man of a staff?
What is it?
What do you think?
Is he young?
The youngest one.
Young man?
Yes.
This one.
No, he is young.
He looks older than me.
He is young.
Wait a minute.
Where are you looking?
This one is a young man of a camera.
Young man of a comedian?
Staff?
There are people like that.
Is he writing something?
Maybe.
What is he doing?
He is a comedian.
Are you surprised?
What is funny?
He is a comedian.
He is funny.
I don't know anything.
His reaction is funny.
He is funny.
Is it funny?
Can you do something?
He is a comedian.
I can do something.
Do you want to try something?
No.
You guys go to the front.
Thank you.
We are checking the cabbage.
This is cabbage.
Conte.
Watermelon.
Go to the front.
Go.
He is laughing.
He is slow.
He is like a cherry blossom.
He is like a cola.
He is funny.
How much is it?
It is 10,000 yen for a set.
It is 5,000 yen for a bottle.
You are a good guy.
Please.
He is funny.
He is laughing.
Come on!
There's no way I can do it!
If you can do it, sell it!
Hahaha!
Mr. Tsugawa!
Yes?
I'm sorry.
It's impossible to have a comedian in our show.
Isn't there anyone like Mr. AD?
Why is it written in such an ugly place?
I don't know what it says.
But he can do it, right?
He's a comedian, isn't he?
No, but...
Is it okay?
It's 5,000 yen.
I'll buy it or rent it.
Hahaha!
I think he can do something.
If you'd like, please watch the story.
It's 5,000 yen, right?
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Well, you're going to rent it, right?
Yes, I'm going to rent it.
I'm sorry.
Hey, Itao!
Yes?
It's really over here.
Are you doing badminton?
I told you earlier.
If you don't stop, you'll be in trouble.
I'm sorry.
Please.
Do your best.
Yes.
Are you okay?
I'll do my best.
It's starting today, isn't it?
I think I'll get a job right away.
Are you okay?
That woman doesn't laugh at all.
Hahaha!
Here we go!
All right!
Good luck!
That's good.
Wow!
Okay, okay, okay!
It's a wind.
Nice serve!
All right!
Oh, one more time.
It's good.
Itao, go ahead.
I'll continue.
No-ban-yaki-mo!
What?
It's stopped again.
Itao, don't stop there!
Dao-san!
Yes?
What's a no-ban-yaki-mo?
It's a no-ban-yaki-mo where you can watch a dance.
No-ban-shabu-shabu?
Yes.
I don't like it very much.
Well, I can't help it because it's work.
Imo is definitely delicious.
Yes.
What do you think?
It's just a no-ban-yaki-mo.
By the way, how much is a no-ban-yaki-mo?
1,500 yen.
Just one?
Well, it's a little more expensive than a normal no-ban-yaki-mo.
It's expensive, isn't it?
But, well, there's also the entertainment part.
Just one?
Well, if it's just one...
Well, if it's just one, you can see it.
You can see the entertainment part.
You can see who's going to buy one.
I'm sorry if it's like this, but I'm sorry if you don't get six of these.
9,000 yen?
9,500 yen?
Well, 10,000 yen is fine for six of us.
It's expensive.
It's 9,000 yen for 1,500 yen.
Well, 10,000 yen is fine for us.
It's 10,000 yen for six of us.
Is that so?
Thank you very much.
It's 40,000 yen.
Excuse me.
By the way, I'm not wearing underwear.
It's cold.
It's 6,000 yen.
I'm not wearing underwear under the jeepan.
It's a no-pass.
It's longer than I thought.
There's a variation.
There's a lot.
Thank you very much.
It doesn't matter if it's gold or not.
I can't see anything.
Where are you going?
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry.
Don't stay here.
I know.
I'm afraid of the habit.
I'll be careful.
Thank you very much.
The hand I'm holding is cold.
It's cold.
It's colder than usual.
I can't eat it.
It's colder than it is now.
That music is annoying.
I don't like that music.
I don't like it.
2 points.
America wins.
The final whistle will be blown.
The last whistle will be blown.
The final whistle was blown.
What is this?
What do you mean?
It's like cash.
There's no waste.
This is a waste collection vehicle.
What?
Hidao-san, what?
We're doing a waste collection.
What do you mean by waste collection?
We don't need it anymore.
Do you have a ball?
I have it already.
We're selling it.
How much will you give us?
Well...
It's complicated.
Maybe 500 yen each.
If that's the case,
we'll take family photos and ADs.
We'll take them all.
I don't want it anymore.
Let's go.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Thank you.
This is a waste collection vehicle.
It won't move.
What?
With your daughter?
My daughter and I are acting suspiciously.
He took it.
This is the worst.
Look at them.
My daughter is a waste.
The 2004 version of the waste collection vehicle has finally been completed.
One is an Asian Perfume.
The other is an Asian Perfume.
But my mother is the best.
The end.
This program was brought to you by the following sponsors.