I'm the manager of Dantan, Nakimokuro Okamoto Taku!
He's a new manager.
I can't just leave him like that.
We have to celebrate tonight.
We have to.
I'm going to kill Okamoto.
What?
I'm going to kill him.
You're going to kill him?
Team Zero isn't going to kill him either.
I met the manager the other day, Nitta.
Nitta is going to be a decoy today.
He's getting ready for it.
The three of us are going to step in.
We're going to go all out.
And after that, Team Zero.
We're going to have them do the celebration dance.
And we're going to have these two even more powerful dancers.
Here they come.
Where are they from?
They're from Hawaii.
Hawaii.
Hawaiian dancers.
Aloha.
First, we're going to have them do the celebration dance.
And then we're going to have them jump in.
That's the plan.
Let's go to Okamoto's house.
Hurry up.
It's already 4 o'clock.
Oh, Okamoto.
Good morning.
Oh, well, let's go in.
The manager is going to celebrate again.
Yes, yes, yes.
Come on in.
Good morning.
No, it's not good morning.
No, no, no.
What is this?
It's not dirty.
It's dirty.
Come here.
Where should I sit?
Oh, oh, I'm ready.
What are you looking at?
It's dirty.
What is this?
Oh.
That's Okamoto.
Yes, that's Okamoto.
Okamoto.
Yes.
Oh, you.
What are you doing here?
It's a celebration.
Are you here to celebrate?
No, this is what I always do.
I did it on the day.
This is a matter of course.
That's great.
Thank you very much.
There's one more group.
That's great.
That's great, Okamoto.
The symbol of peace, the pigeon.
The pigeon.
How was it?
Good job.
What?
Ladies and gentlemen.
Oh, I'm tired.
Are you tired?
I'm tired.
Why?
I don't know.
Let's take the time to eat.
I can't do it anymore.
I think I'll be dead in about five years.
I don't know.
What is that?
Life?
I don't know if it's life.
I don't think I'll die if it's life.
I think you'll be killed.
Who's going to kill me?
I don't know who it is.
A woman?
I don't know if it's a woman.
You're the one who got stabbed.
Oh, that's right.
I'm definitely going to be on the special edition.
Michael Tomioka is chewing gum.
Why are you chewing gum on TV?
Michael Tomioka's face is red.
It's unexpectedly stupid.
What?
It's on TV.
It's a guest.
I'm talking to a person, and he's chewing gum.
That's right.
You're wrong.
Michael Tomioka is wrong.
Michael is wrong.
That's right.
It's my win.
Michael, don't look at the gum.
But Nagoya, huh?
What kind of gum is that?
Michael, you know.
When I say that, the ratio of badness between Michael and you is about the same.
Why?
That's what happens.
Michael is already in the other side, so it doesn't matter.
At that time, you said something like a foreigner.
It's different from a foreigner.
Well, that's right.
No, that's not good.
If you're chewing gum, you'll know it's not good.
I don't know if he's half or something.
That's right.
But foreigners are kind of shy.
Because half of it is flowing.
Half like me.
Are you half?
I'm wearing a little Indian.
That's it.
Didn't you know that?
If you say that, I'll believe you.
I'm wearing a little Indian.
What are you talking about?
I have a Thai face, but you have a Filipino face.
Why are you wearing an Indian?
I'm wearing an Indian.
I've been with you since elementary school, but I've never heard of it.
I didn't want to say that much.
If you get along normally, you can say something a little bad.
Actually, I'm not wearing an Indian.
That's what friends say.
You've been deceiving me for decades.
Wait a minute.
Isn't it your first time being so mean?
If you've been so mean for a long time, I'd be like, huh?
It's my first time now.
Get out!
Sometimes it's fun to be stupid like this.
Well, that's fine.
I've never started, but I was a little angry when I got a good one.
What is it?
I'm just going to come out.
Then a guy came up to me and said,
You're so stupid.
Did you really say that?
I said, you're so stupid.
You're so stupid.
I've never started, but I'm angry.
I'm angry.
How should I walk?
I'm just walking the way I was taught by my mother.
Why are you doing that?
My mother doesn't teach me how to walk.
No, I'm aware of it.
Who said that?
I'm aware of it.
That's...
Don't say that.
You're the one who said it.
It's a woman.
I'm just walking normally.
Don't walk like this with a glass on your head.
Like this?
Like this.
Is this transparent?
It's transparent.
I'm transparent in a different way.
How can I forgive you if you walk like that?
I have a low back.
Like this.
Don't look at me.
That's why you're wearing a dandy.
No, no, no.
I'm wearing a dandy.
That's why you don't have a wide foot.
A comedian should have a wide foot.
What kind of comedy is this?
A woman should have a wide foot.
If you do that, no one will like it.
Don't say that.
No, I'm serious.
I don't know if you need a wave-like hand.
If you do that, you'll look like you're on TV.
I'm really angry.
Some people are smiling.
I'm angry.
You're angry, aren't you?
I almost got angry yesterday.
Why did you get angry?
I was eating at a lunch in Akasaka yesterday.
Why?
What do you mean?
I'm at home.
I was eating at a lunch in Akasaka.
Akasaka is my hometown.
It's different at this time.
I was born in Akasaka.
I was eating at a lunch in Akasaka.
Two students came in.
They looked at me.
They didn't look at me.
They looked at me while eating Chinese food.
Chinese food was delicious.
No, no, no.
Why are you looking at me?
I didn't make it.
If you made it, it would have looked good on you.
I'm angry.
What's wrong with you?
I'm really angry.
And that.
Shinkansen, Shinkansen.
I'm going to go to Tokyo Station soon.
Don't say it twice.
If you're next to me, say it once.
This is the third time.
I'm getting off.
I'm not getting off.
That's all for today.
Come on.
Do you speak properly?
I'll speak properly.
I'll never say anything strange again.
Speak properly.
I'll speak properly.
I'll get off at Shinkansen and wait in a place where I can get on in a minute.
It's so I can get off as soon as it opens.
Two brothers came.
He has a younger brother who is in kindergarten.
The rest of the elementary school students are like this.
I'm scared.
He doesn't keep them in his heart.
He calls them younger brothers.
I call my younger brother, Machan, Machan, and he goes back and says,
What should I do with this damn kid?
And while ignoring it, he sings a song.
He immediately turns it into a song.
He makes it on his own?
Machan, Machan, Machan.
He says it, he says it!
It's a pretty good song, isn't it?
That's...
Hello, hello, hello.
I'm a fan of the two of you, but I'm also a member of the Smapp fan club.
I'm the only girl.
Shut up!
Smapp is tough, isn't it?
What's wrong with you? Why do you all have the same hairstyle and laugh the same way?
It's usually the same guy that comes out from there.
While leaving behind the big-heartedness of Go Hiromi...
And the atmosphere of the match...
And while keeping the atmosphere of the match...
While making Mokkun shiver...
And while making Mokkun shiver...
Why is that?
What's wrong with you?
It's a strange band.
I heard human beings are born between the small number of fingers of the sand in the park.
Huh? Who?
Ah, The doctor.
Like everyday.
Is it true that humans were born with the size of the little finger of the sand of the sports field?
The size of the little finger of the sand?
The sand of the little finger of the sand, right?
It's written there, the size of the little finger of the sand.
But it's true.
But this is actually true.
Yes.
Don't you think so?
In the end, there is the sand of the wide sports field, right?
Yes, yes.
The probability of being born to humans is so small.
Yes, yes, that's right.
The possibility of being born to humans is really close to zero.
Yes, yes, yes.
Including us.
It was a coincidence or luck that I was born to humans.
I want to be with you again if everyone who is alive now is reborn.
It's stupid, isn't it?
I don't know if I can be born to humans first.
I can't be born first.
Is that so?
No, if I have a heart like a real boy and live with something bad, I can be born to humans.
But if I live a dirty life like you, I can't be born.
It's absolutely impossible for you.
Oh, me?
Yes.
Why?
If you are born next time, you may be born with a red cloth.
All at once?
First of all, you may not be born with a red cloth.
I'm sure.
You may be born with a red cloth.
But if you think it's better to be born with red nuts, you may face to be hit by red nuts.
Tell me about it...
How do you feel?
I thought you may be eaten at the moment of
Wait a second.
Hold on.
I'm sure.
You have to live well for life.
You can't say you're born with a red cloth.
Can you say that again? I can't sleep tonight.
How is it?
When you are born next time, it's going to be awesome.
You are going to be a GT scanner.
It's complicated.
It's close.
You are going to be born as a human.
If you have a pure heart like me, you are going to be a GT scanner.
I usually talk to a fairy.
You are going to die soon.
Why?
You are going to be a GT scanner.
I have never talked to a fairy.
You have never talked to a fairy.
What kind of fairy?
There are a lot of fairies.
What kind of fairy do you dress up as?
I usually dress up as a mini skirt.
Do you dress up as a woman?
No.
You are a man.
Do you wear a mini skirt?
I don't wear a mini skirt.
Ask me more questions.
No.
I often say that the dog's nose is a million times better than the human's.
But the dog is snorting because it's close to the poop.
Even if the nose is good, the dog doesn't smell.
Or is it stupid?
If you think about it, you can't sleep at night.
That's true.
It's natural that the dog doesn't smell.
If the dog is this close to the poop, it will smell.
But if you put the dog in the nose, it won't smell.
That's not true.
The dog blocks the nose that smells with poop.
It's a big deal.
Even if you put the dog in the nose, it's still smelly.
If you put the dog in the dog's eye, you can't see it.
Can't see it?
I can't see it if I have a shit in my eye.
It's the same as that.
Where is it?
Why?
I can't see it, but now I can see it.
It stinks.
It stinks until it comes here.
Even if it comes here, it stinks.
At first it stinks a little, but it's the heavy fin between here and here.
It stinks with the heavy fin up to here.
It's the heavy fin. It stinks with the heavy fin, but if it comes here, it doesn't stink anymore.
It stinks. It stinks. It stinks.
You've never done it, have you?
But it's definitely like that. I'm sure of it.
I can't poop, but if it stinks, I'll try it.
It stinks.
It's okay. It's okay.
Even if you put it in, it's about this much.
How is it?
It smells from here.
Beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep, beep.
The smell is when something mixed with air enters the nose and it starts to stink.
Even if your nose is stuffed, you can feel that it stinks.
I can feel it with my mouth. I can feel it with my sense of taste.
Is that true?
Yes, it's true.
I can't do that.
I'll do it.
What are you going to do? What are you going to do?
Are you going to poop?
It's true, isn't it?
But you have to poop.
Why?
I can do anything.
You guys don't use applause for such a trivial thing.
It's the most meaningless applause I've ever had.
Use it more when you watch an opera or something like that.
An opera is...
You're such a lousy singer.
You don't use applause for such a trivial thing.
It's okay. Let's use it here.
Oh, this.
One by one...
What?
You don't have to think about it. Just say it.
Why are you trying to twist it?
I want you to laugh at least once.
I know, but you don't have to say it quickly.
You can just say it normally.
One by one, from the Esper Kids.
Hey, you're slipping.
If you look at it closely, I'll hide it.
The message I sent you...
Just say it normally.
From the Esper Kids.
It's all over the country.
From the Sniper Kids.
Just say it normally.
It's coming more and more.
The other day, Machan said that he would write it when he saw a part of the old man's body.
So I tried it in the bus when I went to school in the morning.
I saw the old man's nose.
Then the old man sneezed.
Thank you very much.
It doesn't say thank you very much.
It's a lie.
It says that this is true.
There were a lot of pictures in other newspapers.
That's why it wasn't brought to me.
The staff was removed at Kitsuko.
Kitsuko?
What if I find it?
I'll be angry.
I'll be like this.
Are you doing it?
What?
I'm doing it.
Are you doing it?
Did you do it?
I didn't do it.
You didn't do it?
Send it to me more and more.
It's true.
There were a lot of people who didn't do it.
I'll gather a thousand people to say that I did it.
A thousand people will gather there.
A thousand people will gather in a circle and hit an old man in the middle.
A part of the old man.
If the old man is surrounded by a thousand people,
I'll be like this.