Chikichi's over-manager Fujiwara
I'm so sorry for that
Ken-sho
Good job Fujiwara
Do you wanna say something?
There was a word called Ka
I see
Over-manager
What is it?
You said it in the talk
You said it
Over-manager Fujiwara
When I went to work the other day
I wanted to take the expressway
But the expressway was closed due to snow
So I called the over-manager Fujiwara
I called him to ask him if he could send me the expressway
He said the expressway was closed due to snow
I said I'm so sorry
I didn't mean to call him like that
I said I'm going to the toilet
He said yes
I don't want you to think it's a joke
I didn't say anything
I went to the toilet
I said yes
You are the over-manager
Let's see the over-manager Fujiwara
This program is brought to you by these sponsors
Fujiwara doesn't know anything and keeps waiting for the guests
The over-manager Fujiwara is waiting in another place
The test for the over-manager Fujiwara is about to begin
There are four types of over-manager
The first type is the over-manager
The second type is the over-manager
If you don't know what the over-manager is
You will be sent to the front
I see
I don't know what the over-manager is
It's called the over-manager
If you talk to Fujiwara or Mr. Takasu
You will be able to communicate with them
I've done it before
You've done it before?
Have you seen this before?
I don't know this
Mr.Yanaka and I were talking and he asked me to give him the over-manager
Then
He asked Fujiwara to give him the over-manager
And then
You are so mean
That's how it is
He looks exactly like Fujiwara
He is so good
I'm sorry
And
Ideal type
He is so good
I'm working on the toilet
I have to go somewhere far
I don't know where it is
I'll do it
It's not like this
It's broken
I'll buy it
And
This
I'm a fool
And
I'll buy it
It's funny
It happens
Anyway
I have to go
He is on the monitor
Fujiwara is waiting for 2 hours
He is waiting for 2 hours
I'm sorry
I have to go
He says he is sorry
He is on the way
He calls Fujiwara
Will he apologize?
I'm sorry
Hello
Masumoto
I'm busy
I'm sorry
It's cold
I don't know
Why is it so cold?
I'm sorry
Tell me
I understand
I'm sorry
What are you doing?
If
It's cold
I'm sorry
The real test starts
First, he enters the venue in the order of Yamaizaki and Kogoriko
Then, 15 minutes later, Hamada arrives
Finally, he shows up
Fujiwara doesn't apologize
What kind of test will he do next?
I'm sorry
Good morning
Fujiwara
This cheese is too strong
Do you want to try it?
Fujiwara
Why are you laughing?
Fujiwara leaves the room to make a phone call
The writer, Takasu, follows him and approaches him
This is his specialty, arm wrestling
When are you free?
When are you going?
Really?
Let's go play
Let's go
Yamazaki
I heard that you are doing arm wrestling
What is it?
Next, he expresses himself
I'm sorry
What are you talking about?
This is strange
He said that he put his tongue out before, but it was a big failure
Finally, Matsumoto stands up for the toilet
The final test is the ultimate hand-pulling
Where is the toilet?
It's over there
Thank you
He keeps talking
He doesn't even look back
The final test
He doesn't look happy at all
He doesn't even look down
He did it
The final test
Everyone is trying their best and putting up a ccd
Why are you apologizing?
I'm sorry