Happy birthday to you, happy birthday dear An-chan, happy birthday to you.
Thank you.
Happy birthday.
Thank you very much.
It's so big.
It's like Katsura in Okinawa.
Thank you very much.
It's nothing.
You made a modified human.
That's right.
Everyone, look.
I made a modified human.
This is it, a modified human.
Let it sleep.
Let the human sleep.
I put something on it.
Yamazaki Hosei was reborn as a modified human.
Oh, he's awake.
What's going on?
It's making a sound.
Hello, excuse me.
It's not related at all.
Thank you very much for your birthday.
The person who is dressed as Power Man No. 2.
Hello.
Now, the fools are here.
The person who is dressed as Power Man No. 2.
Now, the main character appears.
Let's welcome him.
Power Man No. 2.
The person who is dressed as Power Man No. 2.
It's a mess.
Bring it on.
The person who is dressed as Power Man No. 2.
The children of P.A.R.S. have become fools.
Even though they are dressed like this.
Hello.
If you don't say hello to them, they won't buy it.
This is what an amateur should do.
I want your panel.
So many people came.
They came.
It's a good thing.
There is a rule.
You have to dress like Power Man.
That's right. It's a good thing.
They came.
Fujiko, Fujio, and A are very happy.
Thank you.
That's right.
First of all, the panel.
This is the panel that everyone is talking about.
Everyone, you've seen it on TV.
The real thing.
This is really like Mona Lisa.
It's very valuable.
From here?
How do you take it?
Hey!
I don't understand.
From below.
Strangely enough, there was a reaction when the number of people showed up.
It's a strange story.
This panel.
I'd like to give it to one person by lottery.
Then come here.
Please.
Thank you.
How many people came?
Two people.
Two people came.
Which part of Power Man do you like?
The cute part.
You're the same.
It's cute.
It's okay to talk like that.
Please draw one.
Let's open it.
It's a boy.
It's Mr. Banana.
He's eating bananas.
It's wrong.
Please draw one.
It's a child.
There's a part that looks like Kin-chan in Downtown.
It's wrong.
It's good.
Which is Power Man?
Number two.
Number two came.
There's no number two.
Parco.
Birdman.
It's Par.
I'm hungry.
What about you?
I like it.
I see.
Then you can go home with your nose in number two.
Let's open it.
It's good.
Parco, will you draw?
You did a good job.
I want you to win.
It's my first time.
Please draw.
Thank you.
Congratulations.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
I'll do my best.
Parco.
Thank you.
I took a taxi the other day.
I fell down.
I can't fall down sometimes.
I'm a driver with a side injury.
I can't stand sitting down.
I can't stand it.
Someone has experience.
You have to clean the car once a month.
It doesn't matter if you have a side injury.
It doesn't matter.
I can't stand it.
I want you to sit in the passenger seat.
I'll come like this.
I'll come here with the wind.
I want you to sit in the passenger seat.
I want you to run in the back seat.
I can't stand it.
First of all, you have to check if you have a side injury.
That's right.
It's a job where you get to know people.
You have to fix that.
There are two types of side injuries.
I...
What?
Don't say it like you're in a fight.
I have a side injury, Jin.
I don't have a side injury at all, Jin.
I'm afraid of people I don't know.
I don't know.
They are...
So you don't know the driver you're in a fight with?
I don't know.
I have a side injury.
You don't have a side injury at all, do you?
You'll be surprised.
The other day, I went to the theater.
For about three days.
There was a Kenyan dancer there.
A six-man dancer.
He had a side injury that couldn't be seen.
Come here.
He was surrounded by those guys in the elevator.
That's not a side injury.
That's a major injury.
It's a side injury.
He's a dancer.
He's not wearing a jacket.
It looks like straw pants.
It's a side injury.
He's not wearing any clothes.
No way.
His hair is covered with a transparent wig.
I don't know.
I don't know if he's wearing a wig.
I'll give you another example.
He was surrounded by those guys in the elevator.
That's not a side injury.
That's a major injury.
What?
That's not a side injury.
It looks like it's going to come off.
It's not like it's going to come off.
It's a smell I've never smelled before.
It's going to fill you up.
It's going to explode.
It was so smelly.
It became a hot topic among comedians.
I said, do something about it.
Then the director of the theater said,
When Japanese people go on stage,
we always have to dance to this.
So I gave him my Eto Four.
I said, oh, thank you.
They kept going.
But he didn't listen!
He didn't listen to Eto Four.
Eto Four
What?
What Eto Four?
Well, this class is higher than Eto Four.
You can't do it with a single line.
I can't do it.
It means that both of you need 10,000 yen.
I need 80,000 and 40,000 yen.
I can't do it.
This is how you dance.
How was the audience?
This is amazing.
Half of the audience was smelly.
Everyone wasn't enjoying it.
They weren't enjoying it at all.
They were looking at me like this.
But I heard that Charlie and Hama got 5 bad smells.
It was worse than usual.
That's the way it is.
It was smelly.
The stage and the audience.
That's right.
It was worse than usual.
Charlie didn't care.
The other day...
I couldn't stand Wada Akiko pulling and turning.
It was terrible.
You know the show,
Joushiki Hijoushiki?
We did it on Sunday, right?
It was a party.
I was at the very end.
I went to get a drink.
When I was at the very end,
the bingo started.
I got a lead.
I was happy.
I said,
Hey, let's go get a drink today.
That's what I said.
That's right.
Matsumoto, Matsumoto.
Hamada wants to go get a drink.
I didn't say anything.
You said that.
Then Roppongi grabbed Hamada.
And I grabbed him.
I couldn't stop.
I was waiting for the signal.
There were two girls in front of me.
I yelled at them.
You yelled?
That's amazing.
I was listening to you.
Suddenly,
I yelled.
I said,
It's rare for two people to be together.
You brought them here.
That's amazing.
I can't drink.
Izumi was there.
I told her to come back at 12.
I can't drink.
I was drinking a cup of wine.
I was drinking eight cups.
I was talking.
I was repeating the same thing.
I was singing karaoke.
I was singing one chorus.
I said, Stop.
Izumi sang four bars.
Stop.
That's amazing.
Shinsen came later.
Shinsen started singing.
We were singing together.
He was terrible at singing.
I said, I'm going home.
He said, You're leaving early tomorrow.
He said, I'll be home in 30 minutes.
Shinsuke put out a envelope.
He said, Write a contract.
He said, I'll be home in 30 minutes.
He was dragged in the middle of the road.
Poor Izumi.
Shinsuke said,
Let's go home.
Izumi was just laughing.
Izumi was laughing.
Izzumi was not laughing at all.
Let's go home.
Izzumi got beat up.
Izzumi was beaten up.
We had a lot of fun.
You said something at the end.
I had so much fun.
It was raining a lot.
Everyone went home.
Itsumi, Akiko-san, and the manager were here.
They all went home.
We were at the bottom of the store, on the stairs.
We said, hello.
They said, over there...
Hamada, we're here!
We have something to talk to you about!
What is this?
If you don't say anything, we'll leave.
That's right!
We don't know what to do.
No way!
What was that last word?
I wonder what it was.
It's scary.
But it was fun.
With you and...
That's right.
It was really fun.
Well, again...
I want to go.
Once every four years.
Please write it down.
That's enough.
Hello.
You don't have a resume today.
Yes.
Do you have a job?
Yes, I do.
What's your name?
My name is Mari Akiyama.
How old are you?
I'm 22.
What are you doing?
I'm working.
You're working?
Thank you very much.
By the way, I'm going to see a doctor I really hate.
The other day, when I was paying, I saw an eye on a cart in front of me.
On the cart, it said,
An unknown cart.
On that cart, there were more carts than any other cart.
I was surprised for a moment and made a reservation for the next time.
But I got scared and decided to buy it from another doctor.
Do you two have something like this?
The other day, I wanted to stay in Osaka for a while.
So I went to my house in Nitta.
I asked the doctor to look for a doctor near the main office.
There was one.
It was a local doctor, but he said,
Are you sure?
When I went there, I came to the front of the hospital.
When I saw the hospital, I couldn't stand it anymore.
It was all worn out.
I felt like I was in Shimura-ken.
If you wear something like this, it's Shimura-ken.
There was a place where I could get a doctor like that.
I was relieved and went home.
It's not a local doctor, but...
There was a scab here.
It's called ganglion.
Do you know?
I don't know what ganglion is.
That doctor has a bad tongue.
What's wrong?
It hurts.
It's a scab.
Ganglion.
What?
I thought it was a ganglion.
It's a bad tongue.
I've had a lot of blood.
I can say it now.
About half a year ago,
I had a pimple.
You were taking medicine.
Yes, I had a pimple.
I don't have a scab.
I met you in a dream.
I went between the birds.
You went between the birds.
There is a place like that.
I went to a bandage shop.
That's right.
Sorry.
I washed it in the drain next to the bandage shop.
I went out of the room.
I didn't notice.
What are you asking?
I'm worried about you.
It's your birthday, isn't it?
I don't need to hear that.
Mayonnaise.
It's true.
I don't like the way you say it.
I always say that you don't like fish.
What do you hate so much?
I hate fish, too.
What is that?
Do you like fish?
What is your favorite food?
I like this kind of food.
What do you like?
What?
What is the best food in the world?
It's a yellowtail teriyaki.
That's the worst.
If I had that, I would eat as much as I want.
You killed it, but you didn't cook it.
That's the cooking method.
It can't be helped.
That's a terrible story.
What is it?
I like Ace Cook's wonton noodles.
Isn't it?
I don't think it's good.
What kind of ramen do you like?
I like chicken ramen.
Why are you shaking?
I didn't know you liked chicken ramen.
Ace Cook's wonton noodles are better than chicken ramen.
I think it's good.
I've never thought Ace Cook's wonton noodles were good.
But chicken ramen became a cup.
What?
That's different.
Ace Cook's wonton noodles became a cup. That's different, too.
You can't do that.
You can't boil it in a pot.
But it's hard to throw away Hon Chuka.
I've been eating Sapporo Ichiban for a long time.
What does Sapporo Ichiban taste like?
It tastes like soy sauce.
I like miso ramen.
Japanese people don't like miso ramen.
Japanese people don't like it.
Egg rice is the best.
Egg rice is delicious.
I don't need egg rice and UFO.
I can't stand it.
I'm thinking of having dinner.
Egg rice and UFO.
Good evening.
This is the ending.
Next week, September 24th is the 100th anniversary of Gaki no Tsukai.
100th anniversary.
Let's broadcast live next week on September 24th.
We'll broadcast live from 1.40 to 2.10.
Actually, next week's live broadcast is the last episode of Gaki no Tsukai.
It's the last episode.
That's right.
The last episode of Gaki no Tsukai will be broadcast from 1.40.
And on October 20th, it will be broadcast on Sunday.
It will be a shocking TV box.
That's one reason.
Gaki no Tsukai will be broadcast from 11 o'clock.
That's right.
Will the title change?
Gaki no Tsukai will not be broadcast.
Gaki no Koshizukai will not be broadcast.
That's an adult video.
I can't watch it.
Next week is the last episode of Gaki no Tsukai.
And tonight is the last episode.
I'm looking forward to it. See you next week.
This program was provided by the sponsor you are watching.