It's a good thing I'm here.
I'm here!
Please, say something.
What is this costume?
What is this?
This is not what I was thinking.
Wait a minute.
This is weird.
The theme is...
Is this a 8th grade program?
What is this?
I have to play a game.
Today, we are going to do a program called,
Please, say something.
We are doing a program called,
This is cool.
This is weird.
What is this?
I really like this.
This is cool.
This is frustrating!
So,
I will be the first one to answer.
You will ask a question.
So, let's ask a question.
I will ask a question.
I will ask the first question.
There are 5 comedians that you hate.
If you can find 5 comedians in time,
you will be amazing.
Are you a comedian?
Start!
Here it comes!
Yasushi!
Mikaku!
Here it comes!
Sanshi!
Kosei Midori!
Marianne!
Here it comes!
Nozawa!
Monoko!
Here it comes!
Wait a minute.
Do you hate Mikako?
No, I don't hate her.
I think you hate her.
I don't hate her.
But there was a situation like this.
Let's say you are me.
I was at my debut.
I am Dantan Matsumoto.
There were only two of us in the hallway.
There was no one else.
And we met in the morning.
I am Mikaku.
I am Dantan Matsumoto.
There was a situation like this.
But I didn't hate her or anything like that.
But there was a situation like this.
That's all I wanted to say to everyone in the Kanto region.
All right.
How do you answer these questions?
What kind of matter is this...
Okay.
ashes throughout the farm never
smoke.
Hajimaru
Most of them are about the body
What?
Makijita
Miken Nishihara
What?
No
2 points
Isn't it easy?
Shitauchi
This is easy
Isn't it?
This guy's lower body is amazing
Normally, when you are hungry, you lower your body
This guy is different
Isn't it?
Let's go to the next one
The next question is
Matsumoto's favorite type of woman
Let's start
Kikuchi Momoko
Kuro Yuki
Stop talking
I'm talking about Kuroki Hitomi
What?
Towa Yuki
Who is it?
Morita
That's right
And...
Misako Konno
What?
Let's see
I know Misako
What's this?
Hinomi
One more
What's the last one?
Stop joking
This is my favorite type of woman
I'm talking about her
The last question
This is a question
What shows do you want to quit?
Regular, of course
Of course
What shows do you want to quit?
5?
You have 7 regular shows
In Osaka and Tokyo
It's almost 5
It's 5
Let's start
Dance, dance, dance
Let's see
What is it?
Yantan
Let's see
If it's not Yume
Iitomo
Gaki no Kikai
It's a show
What is it?
I don't know
It's the same as Izumi
Dance, dance, dance
That's right
Let's see
Dance, dance, dance
That's it
Let's see
Ladies and gentlemen
Thank you
Well
Hamada-kun is late today
The talent is to buy the clothes
If you like it, you can buy it
I really want it
Hamada-kun likes today's clothes
It's his fashion
Hamada-kun
It's cute
It's amazing
The sleeves are the same
Where is the ray gun?
No matter how cute it is, I want to be like this
The show is starting
It's a dress
It's quite expensive
Well, today
It's a great hat
How is it?
This is the hat I prepared because I thought you liked hats
What is this?
It opens like this
Oh
Is it okay?
It's the best
It's really the best
I can't stop
I'll do my best today
I'm a little dizzy
I'm not feeling well today
I'm doing well
Why?
I have a headache
I can't go on like this
I have to think of something
What do you mean?
If I work at this pace, I'll probably die
No
I'm not going to die
I'm doing it
It's not my problem
Monday
I'm doing well
Tuesday
Wednesday
I'm doing well
Thursday
Friday
I'm doing well
Saturday
Sunday
I'm doing well
Nothing
I can't go on
It's really tough
He is lazy
He is lazy on the Sunday
If you meet him in your dream on Saturday, you'll take a break on next week
So you take a break on Saturday, Sunday and Wednesday
Yes
Are you guys stupid?
If I ask you honestly, you would think that you have a lot of days off, right?
But you know, when you have a day off, you have a day off, and you like this, right?
That's...
That's your fault, isn't it?
Is it my fault? That I like this?
No, it's not.
If you spend your time and work hard for that, it can't be helped, right?
It can't be helped, isn't it? I have to do that, right?
It's hard because I work hard all day long.
I just said that I like this, and I don't do anything else.
That's because I shop for women, and I like that, so I say that I like this.
That's a lie.
Shopping is a lie.
Do you think that swapping is a lie?
On the other hand, don't you have anything for three days?
Well, if you get a special edition or something like that...
You always get something, don't you?
Well, I got something, so I don't have anything for three days.
That's a lie.
You don't travel, do you?
You can't stay in Tokyo all the time.
We travel from Osaka to Tokyo.
The calories and energy you use on a three-hour Shinkansen.
I don't use calories.
Even if I use energy.
That's a lie.
If you think about it like that, you'll get tired.
I think it's bad for your body to be on a fast train for three hours.
If you go back to the airport, you can go in an hour.
That's faster, so I can't go any faster.
But you can go in three hours in a short time.
I really think so.
I think it's bad for your body to be on a fast train for three hours.
Is that so?
That's definitely bad.
In the old days, people didn't do that.
They used to ride on a basket or something like that.
That's why they took a long breath.
It's better not to get on such a fast train.
Is that so?
If you think about it like that, you need to rest more.
I have a question.
How many days do you want to rest?
I want to rest five days a week.
That's how it is.
Three days out of five days.
And two days out of five days.
As you know, if it were me, I would be like this.
You can't do that.
You can't rest five days a week.
Why?
Do you want money that much?
That's a dirty way of thinking.
I don't want money.
If you sell 1,000 yen while walking, you'll get it, right?
I'll pick it up.
What? What?
Pick it up.
Pick it up?
I'll pick it up.
I'll pick it up. I'll pick it up.
Pick it up.
That's strange.
No, the intonation is strange.
It's still there, right?
I've been doing it all the time at home.
My wrist hurts.
Wrist?
If you say that, I won't say anything.
No, my wrist hurts.
Really?
My stomach hurts.
It's not good.
Is it good?
My stomach hurts.
Let's all use Osaka dialect.
Really, Osaka dialect is good.
It's like a market.
What do you say when you go shopping?
You say you're going to the supermarket, right?
You say you're going to the market, right?
Isn't that a market?
You say it's a market, right?
That's strange. It's a market.
I go home and say, hey, did you go to the market today?
I went to the supermarket, but I didn't go to the market.
I say that.
Why?
There's a market in this era, right?
There's a big market in the center.
That's a market, too.
It's a market, including everything.
It's a ghost.
My mother comes home from work and says,
I'm hungry. I'm going to make dinner soon.
Mom, I'm going to the market.
That's right.
That's a market.
You push it, right?
That's right.
That's not true.
You say it's not true, right?
I've been saying this for a long time.
What's unforgivable?
That's the most unforgivable thing.
That's the best.
What's that best?
Right.
You call it best.
That's right.
You guys can't do it.
You guys are cool.
Osaka is the center.
That's why I think that.
The people from Osaka and Tokyo get married a lot.
I think it's nice of you.
Everything will be mixed and it will be a good feeling.
I don't understand what you're saying.
Mixed and it will be a good feeling.
The Osaka dialect and the standard Japanese will be mixed and it will be a new word that will disappear.
I see.
I'm so tired today.
What are you talking about?
There will be no manga.
There will be no IKIMANGA today.
And the next step will be a new word.
What do you mean by the next step?
The Japanese will communicate with foreigners.
This is a pen dengana.
I'm so tired.
Let's go to the postcards.
There aren't many pictures of this kind of postcards.
Oh, it came out on its own.
Hello.
Please come to the middle.
Are you a model today as well?
What's your name?
I'm Yoshimura Michiko.
How old are you?
I'm 20 years old.
What about your hair?
I'm eating it.
You're eating your hair all the time.
Thank you very much.
Let me introduce you to the next person.
This person's pen name is Lulai Lulai.
Thank you very much.
Do you have any friends who would die for you?
He's so rude.
What's rude?
He thinks love is very important.
That's why he can protect his girlfriend and his partner.
It depends on the situation.
What?
If you're involved.
What kind of guy is involved?
Is there anyone who gets involved with me?
I'm the one who fights.
What kind of person are you?
For example, if you have a knife.
I've never thought I was afraid of knives.
If you have a girlfriend.
What?
He's talking about a knife.
Is that a knife?
It's a knife.
What are you going to do if you get stabbed?
What kind of knife is that?
If it's this back, it's already stabbed at this point.
If you ask me that, I can't tell you the truth.
It's about this.
I'll leave it at this for today.
But wait a minute.
You're talking without saying anything.
That's the funny guy.
It doesn't matter who it is.
This guy is really funny.
I'll wrap it up with love.
It's stuck to the root.
What are you going to do?
Wrap it up.
I can't wrap it up.
Why?
But I want to wrap up a poor kid like that.
What if it goes to the woman?
What?
That's the pattern.
You have to protect the woman.
What are you doing?
That's a big mistake.
What is this?
It's a festival.
It's a lie.
Leave it to me.
I'm really good at telling the truth.
You're starting to look like Yasukio.
What do you want?
Are you going to fall down?
I can't do that.
What?
I can do it.
Leave the knife.
What about the pistol?
The pistol is the easiest.
Die!
Bang!
What are you doing?
That's all for today.
That's all for today?
The show.
Oh, the show.
That's all for today.
I'll see you in the spring.
You'll see me in the spring?
Spring is coming.
Let's have another event for the show.
What?
Why not?
It's hard.
Let's do it.
You're always good.
That's enough.
What?
We're doing the punishment game together.
With the fans.
You're going to ask the young girls to play?
They're going to dig up the soil.
That's nice.
I'm going to do it.
And there's a talent like Mr. Ishii.
He wants to be on the show.
For example, someone like who?
If it's a big star, it's...
Mori Ogami.
Really?
You're lying.
I knew it.
Anyway, everyone, please come to the show.
I can't use the show, so I'll see you next time.
Goodbye.