I just briefly explain it...
When about to explain it briefly
If you go to Nishibori, Yasumoto Prof 맞agis's.
Who is the storage manager of the button
detachment
I'd like to talk to you
Cross from this Akasaka
azziand
Come on sales
This period of time we are chasing you in the hidden camera
I sent it to the person who set it up.
I sent it and tried a lot of things.
In the meantime, there were a lot of things going on.
Today, I would like you to go to Azabu Juba Onsen here for business.
You can go directly to the money gala.
The road is also crowded today, so I want you to walk all the way here.
Wear this jacket and go to the money gala.
It's just right, isn't it?
Is this good?
No, I want you to return it.
If you go over there, there is a manager named Sakurai.
I won't go.
If you go this year, there will be other jobs.
I'm happy.
Please.
Walk properly.
I don't have a taxi.
It's okay because you don't have a taxi.
I don't think he can get on a taxi.
Go to the hospital.
Where is TBS?
I don't know.
Go straight and turn left.
Turn left and go straight.
You should go.
I don't go.
I have a job.
I don't have a job.
I'm sorry.
I'll give you half of this.
That's a good guy.
If you go that way, you'll see me.
Thank you very much.
Be careful.
I'm sorry.
I'm scared.
I'm confused.
Turn right and leave.
I'm sorry.
Oh?
Oh, hello.
You're finally back.
I'm back.
Hello.
Hey.
Yes?
What?
Are you a comedian?
I don't know.
Hey, hey.
Do some comedy.
Yes.
See?
I'm doing it!
This is famous.
Our young man is a fan.
Yes.
Right?
I want to show you.
Hey, come play with us.
Yes.
No.
What should I do?
Come and play with us while I'm talking.
Yes.
Hey, come play with us while I'm talking.
No.
It's too hot.
I can't stand it.
Run away.
Hey, maybe you can teach me the theme song.
I don't know.
Oh, he ran away.
He ran away.
I don't know if it's because of the yakuza, but I'm being chased.
It's because you're running away.
I'm scared.
Just say you're going.
I don't know.
So many things happened and now I'm finally here.
I thought he ran away because he was followed by a lot of people.
I'm Jimmy Onishi. Nice to meet you.
Um, Kuro-san.
Sakurai-san.
Ah, Sakurai-san. I'm sorry.
Ah, I'm sorry. I'm the first Jimmy Onishi. Nice to meet you.
Everyone, yes. Is it okay?
Ah, everyone. Hello. I'm Jimmy Onishi.
Um, everyone knows me, right?
I did it! I did it!
Recently, it's getting hotter and hotter.
Really. If it was this hot in July and June, I wonder how hot it would be in December.
He's facing this way. He's facing this way.
Um, I'm the first Jimmy Onishi.
I'm the first Jimmy Onishi.
Excuse me, ma'am. Can you touch this for a moment?
Ah, it's a bit wet.
Why is it wet?
Really.
I don't know.
It's really wet.
Excuse me, ma'am.
I don't know if it's wet or not.
Ah, really. I don't know if it's wet or not.
Today, um, today, everyone's tour is over.
Um, we hope to see you again.
I'm not going home.
Thank you very much.
Ah, thank you very much.
It's really hot today.
Let's do it.
Yes.
I'll give you the gyara here.
It's a little heavy because there's a lot of food.
Yes.
Thank you.
My gyara is taiyaki.
He's frowning.
Thank you very much.
Is it good?
Yes.
Thank you very much.
I thought I'd get it if I was told to.
Um, Mr. Sakurai, please.
Yes.
Mr. Sakurai, please.
Ah, thank you very much for today.
Thank you.
Yes.
This way, please.
Ah, I'm really going home.
It's okay.
Yes.
Is that okay?
I'm really going home.
Yes.
This way, please.
Thank you very much.
Um, excuse me.
Um, I'm the manager.
Yes.
The gyara was given to me by Mr. Sakurai.
I heard that taiyaki is a gyara.
Is that true?
Isn't that a joke?
He noticed it.
I got taiyaki.
He got taiyaki.
I'm going to take it with me.
Where's the money?
He's still saying it.
It's Mr. Sakurai, right?
Yes.
Thank you for your hard work.
Yeah.
How was it?
It was really good.
Hey, didn't you get a shock?
You got a shock.
Did you get a shock?
I didn't get a shock.
That's not true.
You got a shock.
I didn't get a shock.
You did.
Be honest with me.
You got a shock.
Excuse me.
Look.
The microphone is on.
I'm the real one.
Why are you laughing?
I get excited when I see a star.
Don't say that.
That's right.
I say Hama-chan.
I just get excited and say it.
I can't stop myself.
I just can't stop myself.
Actually I don't remember saying Hama-chan.
You don't remember.
It was really...
You said it in my mouth.
You said it while looking at me.
I got excited and it came out.
I got excited and said Hama-chan.
That's what I'm saying.
That's scary!
That's right! I don't need that kind of thing!
It's scary, you know.
You come out like this, and you don't check anything.
It's not like you're doing a body check or anything.
You come in like this, and you're excited.
When you go to a fan meeting,
you want to be the only one there.
So what kind of behavior are you doing?
From around here, you go like this.
That's dangerous!
That's what I'm saying.
Why don't you blow your nose?
That's because I like it too much.
That's a very high probability.
You blow your nose from around there, and you stick your nose in here.
There might be people like that.
If you think about it, it's a scary world.
I don't think there's anything like that.
It's scary.
Well, it's fine.
There's no one who comes to a place like this.
No, no, no.
I don't know about my fans.
There are fans, too.
It's about the other day's incident, but I still can't give up.
What kind of incident is this?
It's a grudge.
It's really a grudge.
I said I baked a pancake.
You sent me a pancake as a tip.
You started with cold noodles.
When I gave you the butter, it stank.
It's a bad habit.
It's a nuisance.
What did I do?
I thought you'd want it, so I thought about it and sent it to you.
It's practical.
I've been saying it on TV all the time.
Yes, the sleeping bag of Robocop.
Transforming sleeping bag.
Don't say that.
I can't send it to you.
I had no choice but to get it.
I'm wearing it at home.
It's hot.
It's really hot.
I'm sweating.
But the mission I was given is...
What mission?
It's up to here.
Right?
That's fine.
It's like that.
The other day, the day before,
Yes.
It's rice.
It's on the street.
It's near my house.
I was told to bring it home.
I didn't bring it home that day.
It's you.
You threw it in the middle of the street.
In the middle of the street.
I was looking at my fans.
Wait!
Because...
Because I hate chocolate.
I hate it.
Don't say that.
Everyone is throwing it away.
Katsuno Hiroshi, too.
Why Katsuno Hiroshi?
Because something just came out.
The cash is going to get dirty.
That's it.
Yes.
It's hard.
The talent too.
If you're called Hamada,
Harutatsu will call you Romi-chan.
It depends on the person who said it.
Oh, really?
Yes.
What kind of person?
Someone who walks around like that.
Someone who looks like he's going to cry.
I don't know.
Oh, Hamada.
What?
But...
But you're Hamada.
I know.
That's right.
You're really Hamada.
That's why you're Hamada.
For example,
If you were called Deba-bouchou,
What are you talking about?
Shunputei Deba-bouchou.
It's definitely not going to sell.
Deba-bouchou.
But you're not angry, are you?
No.
I don't understand that.
No, no.
You're not angry.
It would have been nice if you had a stage name.
By the way,
If you're called a painful person,
A painful person,
A yakuza.
It's okay if you're called a yakuza.
That's not good.
The other day,
When I came to Tokyo from Oda,
I got off at the station,
And the back seat was full.
At first,
At first, they said,
Hey, Hamada.
I said,
Yakuza, that's enough.
They said,
Hey, Hamada.
I said,
Yes.
If you say something you like because women will be interested,
You're covering your face.
Trust.
What?
Trust you.
Trust.
If you say something you like,
I'll get my weekly review.
I'd like to ask you something.
In Yoshimoto Kogyo, there is a person called Hamane-san.
You don't know him, do you? Hamane Takashi.
I don't even know his full name.
You don't even know how soft he is.
Hamane-san's house is near my grandmother's house.
But Hamane-san doesn't come out on TV.
So I'm very worried about my grandmother who lives in the same area.
Where is Hamane-san and what is he doing?
I don't know.
Please use Hamane-san on TV with the power of Downtown.
But Hamane-kun is doing his best in Osaka now.
By myodo manzai.
Oh, is that so?
Yes, yes, yes.
I like the feeling of the gag.
The new gag is Hamane-kun's gag.
I'm surprised, I'm surprised, I'm surprised, I'm surprised.
When I saw this, I didn't think much, so I didn't feel bad.
Do you want me to call you?
What are you doing?
I'm surprised, I'm surprised, I'm surprised.
There are a lot of people in Osaka.
There are a lot of people who want to introduce them to you.
Look, look.
There was a person named Choichi-san, right?
Choichi-san.
He was doing magic with fire.
He was doing it like this, and the fire flew like this.
That person is Zura.
He was burning like this.
I don't even know this.
If it was a fire head, I wouldn't know.
If my head was burning.
But it's a wig, so it's not that hot, right?
The woman from the back was like,
Sensei, head, head.
Sensei, head.
Why?
Do your legs stink?
Are you stepping on something while a strange insect is sleeping?
Please tell me about that.
Most men have stinky feet, right?
Well, I guess so.
But I really have stinky feet.
But your feet are stinky.
It's more than I expected.
Wait.
Since you were born, I want to smell as much as you once.
Why?
Everyone is human.
I want to be bad.
I can't be bad.
Is it bad to be stinky?
Are you stupid?
I want to be bad.
Take off your shoes.
Wait, let me tell you.
I don't wear these shoes all the time.
These are the shoes that my stylist brought.
I'm wearing them now.
That means, after this program,
Don't say that.
Do you want to say that my feet stink in a short time?
These are the shoes that I used to wear all the time.
Don't say that.
Why?
Take off your shoes.
No.
Don't say that.
I can't see.
No.
I can't smell.
Explain.
You don't have to do that.
I can't smell.
Take off your shoes.
I won't run away.
What do you think?
Are you a reporter?
This is it.
That's right.
It looks good, doesn't it?
I see.
It took about an hour to make this.
An hour ago?
Yes.
I boiled it.
I see.
That's right.
Well then.
Thank you for the food.
You're welcome.
It stinks.
But it doesn't stink.
It only smells like leather.
I don't know.
I've been looking at you like this all the time.
It doesn't stink at all.
It only smells like leather.
So why does a guy like you smell like that?
That's why it doesn't stink.
No, no, no.
It stinks as much as your feet stink.
Who is it?
I've never smelled it.
It stinks as much as your teeth stink.
Who is it?
Number two?
No, it's number two.
It doesn't stink at all.
Look, look.
That's enough.
My socks.
It's okay.
Try it on.
I'm so confident.
I'll tell you this.
I've been wearing this since this morning.
I didn't change my clothes here.
Try it on.
It doesn't stink at all.
This is it.
This?
Yes, that's right.
Then...
It's soft.
I've been wearing it for a long time.
That's right.
It feels tight.
That's not true.
You'll get angry.
Then...
I'll try it on.
Here you go.