In the 6th episode of Gaki no Tsukaiya, let's play the original game of Chikijiki Gainin Kouan!
This is the 6th episode of Gaki no Tsukaiya.
Oh, it's already the 6th episode?
I like this kind of game.
Because I get involved with various young people.
I'm happy, but Hamada is getting more and more exposed.
What do you mean?
I don't like the atmosphere of OI.
It's not just Hamada.
That's right.
Because it's fashionable.
Don't worry about that person.
I'm just doing what the script says.
Did you have such a script?
Did you write it?
I'll take two pictures.
First of all, the first group.
Hello.
We are the Yacchanai Master.
My name is Suehiro Garisu.
Nice to meet you.
We are Tate Matsuri.
This is the game we brought.
Your voice is like an old man's voice.
I'm sorry.
Don't do that face.
You look like an old man on TV.
I'm sorry.
Don't laugh.
That's it.
What is the game that Suehiro Garisu brought?
This is the game.
There are many theaters in Omiya and Makuhari.
There is a writer called Higashiyama.
He is a young writer.
This game is very interesting.
I brought the most interesting game.
This is the acrylic docking painting.
What is it?
This is the game.
Five people will draw a picture on the acrylic board by dividing it into parts.
If you put the parts on the acrylic board and complete the picture, you win.
I see.
I understand.
I will give you an example.
For example, if the subject is a lion, I will divide it into parts.
One is the outline, one is the nose and beard, one is the mouth, one is the eye, and one is the vertical hair.
Divide it into parts and dock it at the end.
I think I can do it without Hamada.
I look forward to working with you.
Have you ever seen a motorcycle from above?
why?
I can't do that.
This is the perspective of a Kamen Rider.
This is the perspective when riding and crossing.
I thought you were a genius.
I look forward to working with you.
Let's start with the first question.
This is the first question.
My name is Mishima from SUEHIROGARIZU.
I will draw Mishima.
I will draw Mishima's face.
I will ask you to decide which part to draw.
The first is the outline, the second is the nose, the third is the mouth, the fourth is the eye, and the fifth is the hair.
Where is Hamada?
I will draw the mouth.
I will draw Tanaka's outline.
I will draw the outline.
I will draw ENDO's nose.
I will draw the hair.
I will draw the eyes.
What did I think?
I will draw Mishima's face.
I will draw Mishima's mouth.
You said it first.
I said yes.
This is good.
Please draw Mishima normally.
Everyone, please draw.
This is a face that is easy to draw.
This is simple.
This is not difficult.
Everyone has a sense of size, so if you draw differently, it will come out or be too small.
If you have common sense, you will be good at drawing.
This is easy to draw.
He closed the lid.
This is fast.
Hamada, please draw.
This is easy to draw.
He drew it.
I will draw the outline of Tanaka's face and ears.
I'm looking forward to it.
I think this is good.
Please draw.
Please draw the outline of Tanaka's face and ears.
Next is ENDO's nose.
This is easy to draw.
This is close to this place.
ENDO's nose is close.
Please draw it again.
Oh, but, yes, it's a little different, isn't it?
The touch has changed.
The touch is different.
Let's go to Matsumoto-san.
This is pretty good, isn't it?
It's amazing, isn't it?
I'm following the side side.
I should have drawn it here.
That's right.
It's doubled.
I see, I see.
It's hard to draw a person here.
This is the first time, so let's clear it.
I'm glad to hear that.
OK, OK.
It was as good as that.
I wanted to do that.
It's cute.
Let's move on to the next topic.
I can do it again.
Here it is.
The topic is Downtown Matsumoto-san.
Matsumoto-san.
Yes.
Do you like people?
Is it an animal?
I think animals are good.
I drew it on the back of the flip as you thought.
Thank you very much.
You have to divide the animal into five parts.
I see.
It's difficult.
It's still a normal old man's face.
It's a phenomenon.
It's Kinga Shinno.
I'm a little embarrassed.
Congratulations.
The topic is over here.
It's okay.
It's hard to divide the parts.
That's right.
This is an interesting idea.
It's an interesting idea.
It's a topic.
That's right.
How about this?
This is the topic.
This is a giraffe.
It's a giraffe.
Is that all?
It's the whole thing.
It's not a face.
I have no choice but to go that far.
Face.
Let's go from 1 to 5.
Neck.
Body.
I'm sorry.
I think it's okay.
Is it vertical?
Let's decide vertically.
It's vertical because it has a neck.
You're expecting it to come around here, aren't you?
That's right.
Please write it down.
The body is almost the same, isn't it?
I'm the legs and the tail.
That's right.
What do you mean?
It's fast.
I did it.
It's a game that Mr. Higashiyama came up with.
You're talking about Mr. Higashiyama.
It's like Mr. Higashiyama is bad.
I don't know that.
But if it goes well, it's okay.
If it goes well, it's okay.
The tail is bad.
Only the tail is bad.
That's right.
Tanaka, who draws the tail, is bad.
Tanaka doesn't have to draw that.
He didn't have to draw that.
If I say too much, I'll get a pie thrown at me.
I'm scared.
I'll transform into Tanaka.
Acrylic Docking Painting
A challenge to divide a giraffe into five parts.
Will it be a success?
If it goes well, it's okay.
I want you to draw well.
Please draw well, Tanaka.
That's great.
Let's go in order.
Where should I start?
Let's start with the face.
Please.
First of all, the face.
Will it work?
Let's add this.
The face came in the center.
That's bad.
I don't know which one is the center.
Is it this one?
That's right.
The center is strange.
Let's say the whole thing.
This way of thinking is strange.
I thought so.
No, no, no, no.
But even if you shift it, the picture is a little bad.
I'll do Acrylic Docking Painting.
Mr. Masumoto's neck.
Please draw the neck.
But it's like this.
It's not a problem.
But it wasn't bad.
It's a good position.
The position is perfect.
Mr. Hamada's torso.
It's thin.
Think about the thickness of the pen.
Please match the thickness of the pen.
Think about the TV.
What is this?
It's thin.
Why did you use a thinner one here?
Everyone is fat.
Please draw the legs and tail.
I don't think it's that off.
But if you match the face.
If you match the face, the rest is just.
Finally, the pattern.
Disgusting.
There are too many.
It's not even a pattern in the first place.
It's like a scale.
Please shift the face.
If you match the face a little more.
But what do you think?
If you ask me what this is.
The wrinkles on the pattern.
If you change this.
It's Tanaka.
It's bad.
That's right.
But if you ask me what this is.
I think it's Kirin.
It's okay.
I feel like I can do more.
This is a good topic.
It's not a face.
I think everyone who sees this will be able to play.
I'm thinking about a lot of things.
Acrylic is close by now.
I'd like you to use it.
Thank you very much.
Next, let's have the actors appear.
Here you go.
It's coming out like this.
I got it.
That's what I was doing.
I'm sorry.
I'm AOKI SAIZO SUYAMA.
I've never seen you before.
This is the fifth year of his acting career.
This is the game that AOKI SAIZO SUYAMA came up with.
I brought this.
I was excited when I was doing a drinking party with comedians.
Here it is.
It's a double minus one game.
Thank you.
Please prepare a card.
I'll have you draw only one card from your deck.
Please double the number written there.
I'd like you to draw one more.
The person who says the number the fastest will get the card.
I see.
It's a little confusing to draw one over two.
That's right.
The person who said the number wrong or the person who said the number wrong will get the card.
It's just me.
I got it.
The Joker is also confiscated.
The person who answers the question next can take the card.
It's a game where you can turn the tables at once.
That's the kind of dream I had.
I'm doing it right now.
You're doing it right now?
Thank you.
Are you talking about your dream?
No, I'm not.
I'd like to do it with you from now on.
Do you have the right to refuse?
I don't.
Then you have no choice but to do it.
Then please.
Yes, please.
All right, I did it.
When you draw one card, you have to say it's two times minus one game.
I see.
The number that comes out wins.
I just have to put it here, right?
That's right.
I'd like you to start with me.
I'll do it.
Here we go.
Two times minus one game.
What is this?
Since Joker came out, it will be confiscated.
It's not funny at all.
No, it's not.
I think I'm the biggest victim.
Can I get Joker back in there?
I think you should eat it.
Can I?
Please.
It's an elephant.
Please say it's an elephant.
Say it's Seyama.
It's Seyama.
Is Seyama your real name?
That's right.
Is it the same for you?
No, it's not.
It's not?
How long have you been eating?
Let's go.
Did you get it right?
Yes.
Are you nervous?
Two times minus one game.
Twenty-five.
Twenty-five is the correct answer.
It's fast.
What?
Really?
You're not that strong.
Why? It's easy.
It was really fast.
I didn't think 13 would come out of the blue.
I panicked.
Really?
Let's go.
You can calculate everything.
Two times minus one game.
17.
17 was the fastest for Hosei.
It was fast.
We said it.
By the way, I'm participating, so I'll answer the numbers.
Go ahead.
Can I answer before Hosei?
I know you're participating, but you got it first.
I'm sorry.
You got it first.
I got it first.
Did you get it?
I got it.
I didn't edit it.
Wait a minute.
What? It's really fast.
You didn't say it clearly.
Two times minus one game.
11.
No.
Hasegawa was faster.
Really?
Yes.
Hasegawa was faster than Hasegawa.
I was definitely faster than Matsumoto.
Hasegawa was faster than Matsumoto.
Yes.
Really?
Hasegawa was slow.
I'm the judge, so I'll answer the numbers.
You're participating.
You're participating, but you're the judge.
That's right.
It's my role, so let me play the game master.
You can do whatever you want.
I'll ask Hosei.
Here we go.
One, two.
Two times minus one game.
13.
It's Hosei.
Wait a minute.
It was fast.
I was pretty fast, too.
I said it, too.
It was pretty fast, so I said it, too.
It's Hosei.
It's because you're next to me.
That's right.
Listen to the whole thing.
I'm saying it at the same time.
Then I'll spread it out more.
Two times minus one game.
25.
It's me.
It's not me.
It's two times minus two games.
Say it's minus three when you do it.
Let's do that.
Let's change it.
I'll play all the games.
You don't have to judge.
It's a rule book.
I'll do it.
Next.
Please press minus two.
I'll do it.
Two times.
You should have said that from there.
You should have said that from the song, too.
For example, I'll do it.
Five times minus nine games.
Who can do this?
55.
46.
Two times is the same.
I'll ask you what to draw with two times.
You have to think about how many to draw.
I got it.
I'll do that.
Two times minus two games.
It's Mr. Hose.
I was fast.
I'll ask you.
Let's go.
Two times minus three games.
It's very fast.
I did it again.
You.
Not at all.
I'm doing this because it's a TV show.
I'm going home if I do it at home.
Thank you for your hard work.
Let's have the next entertainer appear.
Who is it?
Hello, I'm Blue Ready.
I'm the prince of the first current HANRYU idol entertainer in history.
I'm very angry.
I'm really sorry.
I was angry when we met, but it's completely different.
I'm sorry.
I've been looking forward to it.
There's nothing behind him.
He's a trainee.
I'm Sano.
Nice to meet you.
He's a trainee.
It's been eight years since I've been an entertainer.
What is the game that Blue Ready came up with?
This is the game I played when I went to Korea to work as a HANRYU idol.
It's hard for me to speak Korean, so I couldn't do it.
At first, I was having a lot of fun communicating with the locals.
This is the game.
It's a greeting game connected to the world.
I'll tell you the rules.
Can Sano explain the rules?
That's about it.
I'm a trainee, so I'll tell you the rules.
Does Sano have upper teeth?
I have it.
It's coming out.
What is it?
I'll tell you a little bit.
It's a game that you play according to the rhythm.
First, tell me about the country and region.
It's a greeting that goes along with that.
If it's Osaka, it's Maido.
If it's Okinawa, it's Haisai.
If it's Korea, it's Anyohaseyo.
If it's America, it's Hello.
If it's China, it's Nihao.
If it's Thailand, it's Sawadika.
I've never heard of it before.
I'll give you a hint.
If you're stabbed by a young man,
It doesn't matter who stabbed you.
Everyone, please stand up and say,
Please stand up and say,
If you don't say this, you're out.
I'll give you a little bit of an example.
First of all, a successful example.
Greeting game.
Korea.
Anyohaseyo.
This is a problem.
It's a wrong pattern.
Greeting game.
Korea.
Sawadika.
This is a wrong pattern.
Sano's way of getting up is unusual.
What's wrong, Sano?
Is that how you do it?
I'm not nervous at all.
Are you ready for YOKARUBI?
It's YOKARUBI.
Here we go.
Let's connect to the world from the prince.
Greeting game.
Yeah.
One, two, three.
Osaka.
Maido.
America.
Hello.
China.
Nihao.
Okinawa.
Haishai.
Korea.
Anyohaseyo.
China.
It's a little wrong.
It's a wrong pattern.
It's a wrong pattern that doesn't get excited.
I'm very sorry.
Just say it.
If you're going to fall, just fall.
I thought you were going to fall.
I was nervous.
I was nervous, so I calmed down.
Here we go.
Let's connect to the world from the prince.
Greeting game.
Yeah.
One, two, three.
Wakamono.
Yes.
Thai.
Sawadee krap.
Wakamono.
Yes.
Thai.
Sawadee krap.
Wakamono.
Yes.
Sawadee krap.
What's wrong with Sawadee krap?
It's too bright.
It's the other way around.
Let's get started.
GENINI KOWAN ORIGINAL GAME KOUHAISEN
Matsumoto is confused by the new KOUAN game.
Nakanishi Nasu is excited by the new KOUAN game.
He is also moved by the moment.
I'm about to cry.
Here it comes.
Wait a minute.
I'm going to wear it.
This game is available exclusively on Hulu.