Ladies and gentlemen
How long are you going to do this?
Today is a special day
Is that so?
There is no useless talk today
Why?
I think everyone knows
But I bet on it and the result came out
I bet on it
I bet on it, you bet on it
Yes
I lost the bet
As expected
Well
If I lose?
If I lose, I will do skydiving
But I already did it
I did it
I will show you everything today
That's great
The people who came today are already lucky
Let's take a look at the monitor
Do you want to take a picture?
Have you all seen it?
Right?
Until the end?
Yes
What?
Have you all seen it?
This is the first time I have seen a baseball game like this
Let's take a look
Everyone, please look at the monitor
Yes
Here you go
It's hot
It's dark because it's night
It's dark
It came out
It's okay to shake your hand in front of the cameraman
I want to fly
I can't stand it
It's so scary
I will go home
It's scary
What are you talking about?
I don't know what you are talking about
I'm going to turn it
I will turn it
Turn it
How many rounds are you going to aim for?
I won't do it.
What?
Did you take any medicine last night?
No, I didn't.
Do you have anything to say to your child?
Even if I don't have a father,
I want him to grow up healthily.
At first, I took off from the plane,
and before the parachute opened,
I took off at a free fall.
At a speed of about 200 to 250 kilometers per hour,
I took off at a speed of about 40 seconds per hour.
Did you take off at a speed of about 40 seconds per hour?
Why did you do that?
Please open the parachute.
I took off at a speed of about 40 seconds per hour.
Now, the camera is in the middle of the face.
How are you doing?
This is a small gift from the staff.
This is a hand-carrying bag.
I don't need this.
I'm called the lady plaster.
Thank you very much
It looks like he is under construction.
It looks like he is a beauty contest 일반大學這所
Wait, what the heck…
Ok, ready?
So that's the whole story.
Up to the first half
You and I went on the Setsuna together, right?
Yes, yes
Even just that, it was pretty scary
Eh?
Of course it was scary to jump off
But I experienced about 4 out of 5 of your fear
I didn't, I didn't
That's too much, but I was scared of 1 out of 10
I couldn't say anything
It was scary, because it was a sudden Setsuna
So I said to Maachan to get on too
So I got on
I was floating up there
At that time, I counted my head, and there were 10 people on it
Eh? I thought
Everyone was carrying parachutes, so it was heavy
That's why it was scary
Eh?
I thought it was pretty scary, but I was told it was about 1,000 meters
But 1,000 meters was the scariest
If I went any higher, I wouldn't know what was going on
You wouldn't know what was going on
Yes, yes
It was pretty scary after that
I was moved
I don't know if I'll be able to cry today
It's about 1,000 meters high
Eh?
It's about 4,000 meters high
It's still 1 out of 4
It's the worst
It's really scary
Well
If
If I say that I'm going to quit
I won't stop
I'll say that's right
You don't have to fly
If this is a joke
It's really scary
It's 3,500 meters high
It's cold and scary
My body won't move
Can I take off my jacket?
Yes
What are you doing?
It's about time
I'm going
It's scary
I'm about to cry
It's funny
I can't stand it
I'm about to cry
I can't stand the speed
I can't stand it anymore
It's scary
This music
I don't know this song
I was really excited
I'm going down
Hamada
Do you understand?
I'm waving my hand
Hamada
I'm going down
I can hear the voice
I'm waving my hand
Hamada
I'm going down
I'm Hamada
I'm Ozora
Can I land safely with both feet?
Landing is the problem
I'm going down
I'm going to take it off
I can't express it in words
Thank you
I'm fine
Please come
I'm moved
Did you open your eyes from the beginning to the end?
I opened my eyes
I'm moved
Thank you
I can't express it in words
I can do it again
I landed
Thank you
I really
I don't know if I should praise you
It was amazing
I almost cried
I was scared
I was shaking when I landed
I couldn't control it
Don't say that
I was scared
The face of a pilot
I can't forget the scene when I landed from the top
It was amazing
I've never seen anything like that
I can't express it in words
I can't control it
It was amazing
That's all
But you don't look nervous
When you went up, you opened your mouth
I opened my mouth
The picture we took on the way was taken by the person who put the camera on the helmet
He took a picture of us and came back later
I was shaking and he was right in front of me
We took pictures with our heads together
That was amazing
Everyone was shaking
I couldn't control it
I was scared
It was amazing
At first, I was scared that I would die if I didn't open my mouth
But when I opened my mouth, I couldn't breathe
I couldn't control it
When everyone looked at me, my mouth was closed
I couldn't feel the excitement on the screen
It's the same when you look at it from above
When the old man and the young woman took the picture, I couldn't control it
I was like, what are you doing?
I was scared
It was really fast
It was creepy
I couldn't control it
I thought I would die if I looked at it from above
But I couldn't control it
I couldn't see it on the screen
The old man was coming to me
When the staff went to the top and came to 3000 meters
The old man said, this is my present
I was like, what are you doing?
I was scared
But I was told that it was my present
I was like, what are you doing?
You didn't do anything
I couldn't control it
It was the worst
I was moved
I was like, what are you doing?
I couldn't control it
It was really fast
I was embarrassed
I was scared
I couldn't control it
I was like, what are you doing?
Why did the person who was
I don't know what you're talking about
If it was in slow motion, it would be cool
It was in slow motion!
Are you stupid?
At that time, the music was like
What is this?
I don't know what to say
I want to ride on the orchestra
I want to do that kind of thing again
But after this, we are waiting for you
If I say something good, I might be able to impress you
This time, let's go to the main battle
So, today...
You watched the punishment game
The content was very good
It costs 2-3 million to fly that
That's right
This program costs money
Even though the set is like this
At that time, I really thought that the staff didn't want to pay
At first, I ate pilaf, and then napolitan
I was very impressed today
I did it
But I didn't do it to impress you
I was very impressed
I don't know if I will do the punishment game again
I will do that
If you do that, you will do something more than that
I don't know if I can do that
I don't know if I will do it again
Why do you have to be punished while doing the program?
I have a little question
If you don't enjoy it, you won't be able to do it
I don't know if I will do it again
I don't do anything for the event
And also
I want to do the punishment game with you
I had something
Is that so?
I have something
I had something
I don't have something that is not
Let's go to the main battle this time
That's right
Let's go to see you
Really?
Yes, really.
But I don't want to talk to you if I get caught.
Hmm...
I don't know what you're talking about.
At that time, I didn't have the guts.
I want to go to the main battle.
I'm looking for your ideas.
Yes.
You can write a lot of things.
I'm looking for your ideas.
And...
I told you to put only male characters.
I'm looking for your ideas.
I want to do it with only male characters.
Basically, you can put only male characters.
That's right.
I want to do it with only male characters.