I like Honjyamaka more than this! Switch on!
In the first episode of Gaki no Tsukai, Chikishiki! Downtown Hoteishiki! What are you doing?
This is a strange feeling.
This is the first time that young people other than us are sitting on the stage of Gaki.
Today, we are going to do a survey.
Let's see what it is.
I want to explain a little.
It's a little confusing to explain.
Well, everyone.
There is a formula like this here.
This is for famous entertainers.
Well, there are people who are not so famous.
You can paste it here.
For example, the first problem is a multiple.
It's 02.
You have to be careful.
If it's a multiple...
I'll do it.
Make it easy to understand.
From now on, let's see.
For example.
A very famous entertainer.
My favorite, Mutsugoro.
And the person I admire, Izumi Pinko.
The person you admire is the same sex, isn't it?
For example.
I want to be hugged.
You want to be hugged by Mutsugoro?
Izumi Pinko?
I want to be bullied.
I'll write it like this.
Now it's your turn.
Are you ready?
First of all.
The person who wants to be hugged by Mutsugoro.
The person who wants to be hugged.
Switch on.
I won't show this number.
No, no, no.
This number is different.
I'll collect it from behind.
I won't show it.
The person who wants to be bullied by Izumi Pinko.
These two numbers should be zero.
That's why I wrote this.
Is this zero?
It's zero.
You can't do this.
Well, well, well.
The person who wants to be bullied.
If you get bullied, you'll be in trouble.
Right?
What are you talking about?
Wait a minute.
Now, let's look at the answers of the two numbers.
Let's look at the answers.
Ready, go.
What?
What are you thinking?
That means.
Which one is it?
Do you want to be hugged by Mutsugoro?
Let's go to the right place.
I'm sorry.
Let's go to this one.
Good.
Right?
Let's go to this one.
My name is Masatoshi.
I see.
This is easy.
Do you want to be hugged by Masatoshi Nagamura?
Do you want to be hugged by Watabe?
I see.
I want to be hugged.
No, there are quite a few.
There are fifty of them.
This is Iyayaki.
I don't want to be hugged.
What?
Wait a minute.
If it's something like that, it's a great number.
You said it, so I wrote it down.
What are you talking about?
I don't want to be hugged by Masatoshi Nagamura.
If it's something like that, I can understand.
I don't want to be hugged.
Watabe is a bad person.
That's not true.
That's just how he looks.
Everyone thinks he's a bad person.
So, I don't want to be hugged.
I want to be hugged.
Isn't that right?
That's right.
Now, let's look at the total.
Let's see the total.
Twenty-seven.
I can't hold this side.
Ah, it's dirty.
As expected, he brought me here.
I'm more shakure than Makisei Rio.
Kiku.
I'm more shakure than Inoki.
Now, let's look at the answer.
Tenshin.
Minus eight.
What does that mean?
There are many people who are not as shakure as Inoki.
That's too much.
That's right.
No matter how you think about it, that's right.
He's not shakure.
This is difficult.
I need my head.
Now, let's take a look at this.
This is difficult.
This one is quite big.
That's right.
In that sense, it's this one, isn't it?
It's getting more and more interesting.
It's getting more and more Matsumoto.
What does this mean?
It's a simple story.
I want to be hugged.
You want to be hugged, too?
That's right.
Because it's me, it's three times as much.
I'm very interested.
The closer I get to the answer, the more frustrated I get.
Let's just take a look at the picture.
Let's take a look at the picture.
0.6
What does 0.6 mean?
Does that mean there's a lot of Matsumoto?
That's good.
Ladies and gentlemen.
It's not an old-fashioned story, but it's very interesting.
Don't apologize to the guest today.
Why?
The guest today is really tired, but he's still up today.
Really?
Yes.
It's a new guest.
It's not a new guest.
It's finally a postcard.
If you're glad you got it, you're not going to get it.
Come back.
And the next week, come back.
I don't know that.
I feel sorry for you.
I don't feel sorry for you.
Why don't you make a cream bread?
You're really...
You seem to be making a lot of money.
There's only a few words that are different from you.
Down town, the two of you together, down town, please take care of me.
Don't be so cocky.
I've been talking a lot since I came out.
Now, please take care of me.
Please take care of me.
I've come to this program.
There's only a difference of 220,000 yen.
Where do you put that difference of 220,000 yen?
Cream bread.
I don't like cream bread with this much money.
I don't like it.
Why not?
Because the two of you are here.
It's really bad to make a difference in money.
It's really bad to make a difference of 220,000 yen.
No, no, that's you.
And then, I'm sorry, Matsumoto.
Put 110,000 yen in the envelope.
I'm really sorry.
Why are you sorry?
Don't say that.
That's not true.
Then, you should calculate the difference.
You're right.
Taxes are not good for you.
Because you have a family who doesn't need it.
But still, the two of us are in the office.
We're making it equal.
The money that goes into the office.
You usually write down your expectations in magazines.
Your expectations from taxes.
Your income.
In my case, I'm told a lot more than my expectations.
In his case, he earns more.
Wait a minute.
You're saying that the same amount of money is coming in, aren't you?
You're saying that you're making it equal, aren't you?
Don't take it off.
It's only natural for me to spend 100,000 or 200,000 yen a year.
I'm amazing.
I'm different.
I'm all-rounder.
I know that.
I know that expression.
I'm amazing.
I only eat avocados.
You only eat avocados?
That's true for me.
I eat watermelon in the winter.
I have money.
You can pull it out.
I can pull it out.
I want to eat watermelon.
What are you talking about?
I have money.
My house is like a Persian carpet.
I saw it on TV.
I thought I'd seen it once.
I was wondering if I'd be so moved by it.
It was a happy yellow handkerchief.
Oh, you were doing it.
Why would I be moved by it?
The guy who plays the role of Sakakura Ken is a bad guy.
Is that so?
He's a bad guy.
He's full of arrogance.
Is that so?
That guy is called Takeda Tetsuya.
He met Momoi Kaori.
They went on a drive.
They bought a new family car and went on a drive to Hokkaido.
That's why I was wondering if I'd be so moved by it.
I asked him to push the shutter.
That's how I met him.
I asked him if he wanted to get in the car.
It was like a greeting.
He said, sure.
He's a bad guy.
He got in the car.
Takeda Tetsuya was polite to Sakakura Ken.
He got in the car and stayed at the ryokan that night.
Takeda Tetsuya approached Momoi Kaori.
Momoi Kaori didn't like it.
He started to cry.
He was in the car all day long.
Momoi Kaori was in the car all day long.
He got in the car.
The next day, I thought he was going to take the train, but he was right behind me again.
That's not good.
He's a bad guy.
I don't know about that.
Is that so?
That's right.
I sent him to the station.
It took about 2 hours for the train to come.
And a crab came here.
A crab came here.
And he came back.
He came back like a crab.
That's because of Momoi Kaori.
When I woke up, I saw Takakura Gen with a crab.
Momoi Kaori and Takenashi were having a good time.
They were having a good time until the morning.
I thought, can't I get in the car anymore?
That's not how you say it.
I'm telling you, they were having a good time until the morning.
I saw it. I know that.
In the end, he stopped the train and got on the train again.
Can I tell you something?
I want to see if my wife is wearing a red handkerchief.
Red?
You don't look like her.
I want to see if she has a yellow handkerchief.
Don't just say that.
If you do that, Momoi Kaori is a good person.
Let's go.
Hey, Yu-san.
Listen.
Listen to what?
I'm going to the house in the car.
On the way, stop the train.
That's not how you say it.
Stop the train.
Everyone is scared.
That's not true. You should see it.
You'll be relieved.
I'm talking to you, but you don't listen to me.
What?
I called her, but she didn't answer.
I saw a yellow handkerchief.
I saw it.
Then,
I went up to her and told her to drink tea.
I left her alone.
Then,
I didn't even thank her.
I didn't do anything.
That's not true.
I asked her why she was in prison.
She said she was drunk.
She grabbed a drunk man's head and hit him with a rock.
She killed him.
Then she went to prison.
She regrets killing him.
When she was on the train,
Tako Hachiro appeared.
Tako Hachiro hit him.
Tako Hachiro grabbed his head and hit him.
He didn't regret it.
He hit him with the same handkerchief.
There are a lot of people talking about Yutaka Ozaki.
I think he and Hitachi Matsumoto are a couple.
Who is Hitachi?
Is his name different from yours?
He seems to be sharp and naive.
He seems to be ready for a joke.
If Ozaki is a teenager,
Hitachi Matsumoto is a bad hero.
He is skinnier than he was in Osaka.
Hitachi Matsumoto will disappear soon.
I don't feel alive just because I think I can't hear his jokes.
Did you do a thorough examination?
No, I didn't.
Then...
I don't want to die of illness.
I want to die at the age of 40.
You want to die at the age of 40?
Yes, I want to die at the age of 40.
On the other hand, I did everything I wanted to do.
Really?
You did it quickly.
I wrote a song that remains in everyone's heart.
Where is it?
I wrote it for everyone.
Who wrote it?
I wrote it.
What did you write?
I...
You had a bass on Japanese TV.
I wrote a song.
It's not a song.
It's not bad for everyone to burn out in their 40 years of life.
You're still burning out.
I did everything.
I played guitar in America.
I was really into Mick Jagger and Rolling Stone.
That's the only name I know.
Are you a fool? Tell me.
I don't know.
Tell me the members of Rolling Stone.
Don't be so cool.
Tell me.
It's Mick Jagger.
I'm a vocalist. Do you know?
I know.
Why?
What should I say?
Members.
The vocalist is Mick Jagger.
Mick Jagger.
Tell me the other members.
I should say the members other than Mick Jagger?
Yes.
What do you say to the other members?
I'll study here. Tell me.
I'll say the names of the other members other than Mick Jagger.
You should say.
You should check. If you're wrong, you're wrong.
Yes.
That's fine.
There's no mistake.
I'll wipe my ass.
I don't listen to Rolling Stone.
Wait.
The first album is like this.
What's the title?
Well.
Nice to meet you.
Rolling Stone.
Yes.
I don't listen to it.
I love Hama-chan.
I want to ask you this.
What?
What's that string on the corner of the bed?
I want to ask you this.
Well.
How can I explain it?
If there's no string.
The string is the string, isn't it?
The string is the string.
It's not the string.
You said the string.
If it's not the string, what is it?
What are you going out for?
Why do I have to get out of here?
That's to eat you.
You can't laugh like that.
I don't want you to think that I can't get out of here.
Then, please say it.
Everyone is waiting.
Are you waiting?
What?
You can change the way you say it.
I'm waiting.
What?
Are you waiting?
I'm not a fool.
To be honest,
the reason why it's hard for me to answer.
It's because the question itself is wrong.
No, it's not wrong.
You said you thought it was the string that came out of here, didn't you?
It's not the string, is it?
It's not.
Then, what is it?
It's Zabuton.
What?
Do you know Zabuton?
It's Zabuton.
This is...
This is Zabuton.
You're making me scared.
I'm scared.
That's what it is.
That's why I was wondering what you were talking about.
You!
There's one thing I want you to know.
It's about the long necktie of the referee in the ring.
What are you wearing it for?
It's not for that.
I have to turn it over.
That's...
Why?
You know what?
You two are excited, right?
At that time, you don't have to break it.
Yes, yes, yes.
It's called the long necktie.