I'm going to put this flag up so you can see it.
Today, I came all the way here to take off my jacket.
We're here!
Well, the weather isn't too bad, but...
It's a bit cloudy.
Let's go!
If you close the trunk, you'll have to open it again.
That was 5 months ago.
Hamada played a 4-on-1 handicap golf match with Matsumoto, Yamazaki, and Kokoriko.
However, when he opened the lid, there were too many rules.
On top of that, the Matsumoto team had a surprising victory, and Hamada had a hard time.
In the end, the Matsumoto team won.
Hamada ended up losing without doing anything.
So!
Hamachan, you're out!
The worst penalty game ever given to the loser, Hamada, is...
...Titanic with Matsumoto.
After this, Hamada came up with a new idea.
I'm sorry, but...
How about we do it again?
Sure!
I don't care about the timing, but...
Let's change the rules again.
You're going to change the rules?
I have to change that?
And so, Hamada's revenge begins.
Morning!
You're so energetic!
What do you think, loser?
What do you mean, loser?
What do you think you're wearing today?
I came here to return this jacket to you.
You have a bad taste.
European style.
It's not that hot today.
You have to come.
But you're wearing a nice green jacket.
Green jacket?
Let's go with a rough one today.
Let's go with a rough one.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
The biggest game of this century!
Hamada vs. Matsumoto vs. Kogoriko!
The dream golf tournament!
Kogoriko vs. Matsumoto
Why is it Hamada vs. Matsumoto vs. Kogoriko?
Don't say that.
It's the opposite!
No, it's not like that.
Tell us!
What kind of ability do you have?
I have the ability to act.
That's right!
That's how it is.
Kogoriko has the ability to act.
What was that reaction?
Well, that's how it is.
It's a tie.
I lost the last time.
I'm here to punish you.
It's a tie this time.
Can you tell us the rules again?
The rules are a little different from the last time.
In the previous game, the score was 1-1.
That doesn't change.
But when you hit the green line,
When you make a putter,
If you make a putter, it's 1-1.
If the next person makes a putter, it's 2-2.
If one person makes a putter, it's 1-1.
Let's play normal golf.
When you hit the green line, it's normal golf.
Matsumoto's team's score is multiplied by 1.
Hamada's score is 4 times as much as the green line.
The next putter is a normal 1-3.
If Hamada wins at least once out of the three holes,
Hamada wins.
You drank a little.
No, I didn't drink at all.
It's not natural to drink this much.
We don't want to win.
I'm holding back a little.
I've been bleeding before today.
I've been bleeding a lot.
First of all, there's a long hole in the fairway.
The right side is OB.
It takes a lot of time to put it on the green line.
It's a disadvantage for Hamada.
Matsumoto's team will hit in the order of Matsumoto, Tanaka, Endo, and Yamazaki.
Let's go.
Let's start the game with Hamada's opening shot.
I'm under a lot of pressure.
All right.
It went to the left.
I can't say it's a nice shot.
It's a little bent.
What do you think?
Let's go.
Next is Matsumoto's tee shot.
Right, right, right, right, right, right.
Mr. Kaji.
What was that?
It's on the right.
Is it an OB?
Since Matsumoto's shot is not confirmed, Tanaka is going to shoot a penalty shot.
Tanaka, Tanaka.
Tanaka is going to shoot.
I'm scared.
It's a nice shot.
It went in.
All right.
Is it OK?
It went in.
You hit it well.
Excuse me.
When are we going to play golf?
Can we start?
Is the first shot safe?
It's safe.
You did it.
OK, OK.
Matsumoto's shot is safe.
The first shot is to the second point.
One, two.
Tanaka.
I'll do my best.
You've already decided.
Let's go.
OK.
It's a nice shot.
Amazing.
OK, OK.
If you can go forward with this, you can win.
You can do it.
This is tough.
It's tough.
I'm sure I'll win.
It's impossible if you don't shoot a super shot.
It's easy.
I'm sure you'll hit the tree and go somewhere.
What?
I've always admired him.
It went in.
But I'm sure I'll win.
It's true.
I'll do it.
Hamada continues with the third shot.
Really?
Amazing.
This is good.
What was that?
What?
Really?
This is good.
What was that?
It's a warp.
Warp.
After this, En-dou from the Mazamoto team hits it.
But it doesn't reach Hamada's ball.
And Yamazaki hits it next.
Oh no.
It's a warp.
Mazamoto.
This is the first one.
Zaku-san.
It's better than going to a strange place.
Let's focus on teamwork.
We can't aim.
We have to aim.
That's right.
Teamwork.
Let's aim, Mazamoto-san.
Let's aim.
I'm counting on you.
Let's go.
Aim for the cup.
OK.
OK, change.
That's amazing.
Oh no.
OK.
It's the sixth hit from the Mazamoto team, Tanaka.
Nice shot.
The seventh hit is En-dou.
Oh no.
It's a bunker.
Next is me.
Finally, Hamada is in the same position.
OK.
Hamada is in the fourth hit.
He wants to hit the green.
I think so.
Green.
I got it.
Hamada, nice on.
But, he got on the fourth hit.
He got on the fourth hit.
You're really good.
I'm scared.
It's OK.
Oh no.
You should go home.
Hey.
You're a campaigner.
Look carefully.
If Matsumoto hits the green, it will be advantageous for him.
OK.
Nice.
Good.
From now on, it's one hit at a time.
He can't let his guard down.
I think he will hit the green.
But, if he doesn't pay attention, the next hit will be dangerous.
It's dangerous.
It's definitely dangerous.
Hey.
Don't come.
Why did you come today?
Take a rest.
I will come.
Nice on.
He's strong.
He's a campaigner.
I don't know how strong he is.
He's weak.
He's strong.
Hey.
It's dangerous.
OK.
It's OK.
It's dangerous.
OK.
In the end, Hamada hit a bogey.
But, he hit 18 in the middle.
I hit a little.
Oh.
OK.
It's OK.
Don't do unnecessary things.
I know.
It's OK.
You can approach slowly.
Wait a minute.
You don't have to do that.
You can approach quickly.
OK.
He did it.
First, they won 14 to 18.
But, they have only 4 hits.
Next, they hit a bogey on the right side.
The left side is OB.
It's shorter than the first hole.
If they can make a two-on, Hamada has a chance to win.
Hamada is the first one.
It's dangerous.
What is this?
I think it's OK.
What?
I don't know.
I aimed too much.
Did you make a mistake?
No.
Safe.
OK.
It's dangerous.
Matsumoto's ball is taken to the left and it's OB.
It's OB.
What is this?
Don't say what is this.
You look scary.
No, no, no.
It looks like Shime.
It's Tanaka.
It's Tanaka, isn't it?
He rolled the ball.
It's a one-touch.
It's not a one-touch.
It's light.
It's this one.
Here I go.
Tanaka is at his best.
Nice shot.
OK.
It's a miracle shot that goes over 250 yards.
It didn't stop.
What was that?
It was a nice shot.
You're lucky today.
Really?
He put the ball in the tee.
I see.
You mean he put the ball in the tee?
He put the ball in the cap.
You're really good at English.
Hamada is in the second hole from the same place as the first hole.
I'm scared.
OK.
I hit it.
Good.
I'm glad.
Oh, no.
That was a waste.
After this, Hamada and Yamazaki's ball goes to the bunker together.
The fate of the game is in the bunker shot.
Nice out.
Wow.
First of all, Matomoto gets a nice out.
Should I take a protest?
And Hamada.
OK.
Nice out.
That's right.
He finally got a nice out after three shots.
He got a green on.
But he got 24 shots out of 6 shots.
I think I can get in from here.
Really?
Matsumoto's team, Tanaka, is in the seventh hole.
Hamada's team has a lot of space.
I'll aim.
Nice.
Nice shot.
It's long.
What?
That's right.
Wow.
You're not good at that.
I'm not good at it.
Nice.
This hole is 26 to 9.
Matomoto's team wins again.
The last hole is a short hole with a lot of bunkers around the green.
If he can get a green on in the first hole,
Hamada has a chance to win.
This is a set up.
Really?
To be honest.
It's bad.
Is it set up?
You have to put a lot of effort into it.
If it's not set up...
This is bad.
Will Hamada get a one-on?
No way.
Hey.
Where did it go?
What's wrong?
It's in front of me.
This is bad.
That was close.
This is definitely a par.
How big is this?
It's about three bounce.
It's big.
How big?
Was it 160?
It's 170.
It's 170, right?
What did you say, Hamada?
I can't tell you that.
I can't teach you golf.
No way.
Why not?
I can't teach you.
It's dirty.
It's the Chinese mafia.
Why can't you teach me how to bounce?
It's Matomoto's first try.
I told you.
It's coming out.
Here I go.
It's Tanaka's second try.
Will he catch up to Hamada?
Hey.
Good.
It's a bunker.
I'm sorry.
I won't break the direction.
OK.
It's Endo's third try.
It's a twist.
It's Kimu's turn.
What are you doing?
It's coming out.
It's a bunker.
Are you kidding me?
Yamazaki.
Yes?
If you change the bunker again, I'll hit you.
I don't like it.
This is important.
Don't put it on.
That's right. Don't put it on.
The club.
I didn't put it on.
Are you Kanpi?
You're like Kanpi Fujiyama.
Next.
I'm counting on you.
It's coming out.
I'm in trouble.
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
Matsumoto regains his composure and challenges the bunker shot.
Don't put it on.
I was going to put it on for a moment.
Hamada.
Huh?
Hamada can't put it down.
I don't care.
You're not paying attention.
The Matsumoto team finally escapes from the bunker hell.
But the situation is in a pinch.
The Matsumoto team is careful because there is a possibility of losing for the first time.
Strong.
I think it's strong.
But I don't think I can hit the green.
Really?
No.
Don't do that.
Please hit the green.
I'll do it.
Strong.
One more time.
More?
I don't know why it's like that.
Strong.
The last one.
You're talking like a fool.
It's really scary.
I think I'm going to miss.
It's out.
I said it's out.
It's strong.
Endo continues to put it on the green.
It's not bad.
If Hamada puts this second hit, it will be eight on four times.
It's weak.
OK.
It's a little bit.
This is a little bit.
Hamada, hit it a little bit.
It's a little bit in the back.
From now on, it's a pad game for each hit.
The Mazamoto team is seven on.
Hamada is eight on.
There is a good chance of losing.
Yamazaki, who hits the pad next, will be under a lot of pressure.
What's going on?
Good.
OK.
If Hamada puts this, it will be nine on four times.
You guys are noisy.
Why are you guys so close?
What are you going to eat today?
I don't know.
Take it off.
Good.
Let's go.
In the end, Hamada was out of the hole in ten hits.
Take it off.
Good.
The Mazamoto team will lose if they don't put it in two more hits.
OK.
Even if you take it off, you have to take it off at this point.
You have to take it off.
But let me tell you.
This is a downtown match.
That's right.
Downtown.
It's a downtown match.
You've never won a downtown match.
That's why the rules are like this.
I'm being honest.
Let's win.
If you win, I'll do it with a sash.
It's okay to fail, but that's the way to fail.
That's right.
If you think you're going to make it this far, Tanaka will be next.
If you come this far, it's impossible.
Tanaka doesn't even know how strong he is.
What's the order?
I'm so nervous.
I'm going.
I did it.
Good.
This is okay, right?
If you take this off, you'll lose.
All right.
It's okay.
I'll break my teeth.
I can do this.
It's definitely okay.
If you take this off, you'll lose.
Tanaka's last pad.
I'm scared.
It's okay.
All right.
So, this time we won.
Hamada's punishment game.
I can't win with four people.
Hamada's punishment game is decided again.
Hamada's punishment game has made a lot of history.
At one time, Hamada's punishment game was skydiving in the sky.
At another time, Hamada went to the mountains of France to collect avians.
At another time, Hamada went to the place where Sakamoto Ryuichi lives in New York to get Matsumoto's forgotten mechanical pencil.
And the ultimate, Matsumoto's Okanta's Titanic love scene.
All of them remain as wonderful memories in our hearts.
What kind of memories will Hamada give us this time?
And Tanaka-kun will take part in the protest.
It's decided.
I'll do my best.