Police mill
Let me konk aerial report.
Please enter the prosecutor's office.
Defendant, please take your seat.
Your Honor.
Yes.
Let's begin the trial of Akiko Wada, who was a man.
Before we begin the trial,
I'd like to ask Professor Matsumoto, who is said to have obtained a large amount of evidence, to come in and verify it.
Professor Matsumoto, please come in.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
I was very surprised this time.
That's right. I was surprised too.
Yes.
That's why I asked the professor.
Yes, yes, yes.
As expected, that's right.
That's right.
After the investigation, it turned out that he was a really strange man.
This program is brought to you by the sponsor you are watching.
Let's take a look at the evidence photo.
Evidence photo?
Wada, you bastard, look at this bastard.
I'm going to rip off your monster face today.
Let's take a look at it for now.
This is the photo of the pilot Wada.
If you look at it like this, it's not much different from the Wada we usually see.
That's right.
And I used a computer to get a closer look at the camera.
It's closer, isn't it?
Yes, it's closer.
Then it looks like this.
Even with this, you can't tell the difference.
Is that so?
You can't tell the difference.
You've been deceiving the world for over 20 years, haven't you?
That's right.
I got even closer.
Then I found out something terrible.
You bastard!
That's what I thought!
You look like a bandit.
Professor.
Yes.
You look like a bandit.
No, no, no.
This is the first evidence.
Even with this, it's enough.
You look like an old man.
Let's take a look at the photos of the pilot.
For example.
What?
Can't you defend yourself?
That's fine.
Wait a minute.
What is this photo?
What is this bulge?
Don't do that!
You're a man!
You can't shake your butt.
That's right.
This is unthinkable.
Moreover, the side of this old man is not good.
But.
Are you sure?
Even women don't work at such a place these days.
I don't think this is evidence at all.
If you look at the next one.
You can see that he is a man.
Is that so?
This is it.
He's in a sauna.
This bulging bulge.
It's natural.
It's very natural.
He's a regular customer.
It's natural.
However.
He looks a little young, but his body is very thin.
I guess it's like this.
And.
He is a witness.
That's right.
I'm not the only one.
I have a video of the evidence.
Please take a look at it.
Why do you have a manager?
I think it was about 10 years ago when I became a manager.
I went to Asahikawa for a singing show.
After the show.
I came to a nearby izakaya to drink.
On the way home.
He said he really wanted to go to the bathroom.
I was wondering if I should do it here.
Is it okay?
I don't know if I'm going to talk about it or not.
I asked Omomoro to stand up.
I thought it was like that.
This is my manager.
What are you talking about?
From that day on, I was able to date both men.
Omomoro.
I have something to say.
Wait a minute.
What is it?
This is strange.
What's strange?
The police are forcing me to say this.
What are you talking about?
I'm sorry.
Let me say one more thing.
He is also him.
You are also you.
He is the manager of our site.
I don't know what time the meeting will start.
When I go to a meeting, you don't go to a meeting either.
That's it.
Please take your seat.
You said it.
I couldn't hear you. Please say it again.
Please take your seat.
All right.
The judge is weak.
So far, it's just my testimony and the video.
I think it's better to listen to the live voice.
Is that so?
All right.
I'll call the witness.
This way.
Witness, please come in.
You don't have to lie.
Please be honest.
We are in the same agency as Mr. Wadawaki.
He invited me to a meal.
He took me to a bar.
He took you to a bar?
He has helped me a lot.
I often get a phone call from my house.
The other day, I got a phone call from my house.
We were on the loose.
There was a message on the loose.
I brought the tape.
I see.
Let's listen to it.
Hello, this is KUDO brothers.
I'm out now.
Please send me a message.
Hello.
Are you there?
I'm at the school.
I was introduced to you.
You were very nice.
I'm glad I met you.
I'll call you.
I'll call you for a while.
Introduce me to a nice girl.
Huh?
What?
I see.
What do you think of his voice?
He is obviously an old man.
The woman I introduced to you was very nice.
I think it was similar to your voice.
He is a strange man.
What are you talking about?
I understand.
Thank you, KUDO brothers.
Thank you.
KUDO brothers.
Yes.
If you give us enough evidence, he won't say anything.
There is a lot.
Is there anything else you want to say?
I have another great video.
Really?
Yes.
Please watch it.
It will be a great decision.
I understand.
Please watch it.
I think it was when I cried last year.
What are you talking about?
I was a little drunk.
He took me to the hospital.
I was seen three or four times.
He was more manly than I saw on TV.
I can go home at least three times.
It's a decision.
Is that a woman?
That's a woman.
You know nothing.
It can't be helped.
I developed a chart-based diagnosis method.
This shows the gender.
I will take it off.
I hate dogs.
He doesn't hate them now.
But he doesn't like them.
So it's a yes.
Yes.
Is that okay?
He is short.
Which one?
It's a no.
Yes.
He is from Osaka.
Answer it.
It's a yes.
Excuse me.
Stop it.
Other than the fact that he hates dogs, he can only answer yes.
What else?
Excuse me.
Shut up.
Judge, please give the verdict.
The defendant, please come to the center.
What are you talking about?
Come to the center.
The verdict.
The defendant, Wada Akiho.
Wada Akiho?
Yes.
The verdict.
Come out.
It's a no.
What has changed recently?
Oh, that's it.
What?
It seems that you've gained weight.
I've gained weight.
I'm sorry.
Did you cry this time?
I didn't cry last time, but I didn't cry this time either.
I was so moved that I cried when I went skydiving.
I was so moved that I cried that time.
It's been a long time since I did a rerun.
The blonde one.
It's no good, but I'm going to cry.
No matter how many times I watch it, it's no good.
I've never seen blonde before.
Don't you see that?
There's a lot of crying.
I'm doing a lot of dramas right now, but I can't win against blonde.
Because you have a great graduation ceremony.
Adada was never a good student.
What are you talking about?
Calm down.
You're a good student.
I'm telling you the last lesson.
You guys were never a good student.
Don't say that.
Don't say that on the last episode.
At the end.
Don't say that on the last episode, blonde.
Don't say that.
Don't make me feel like I've been betrayed.
Don't be impatient.
Don't worry.
This time, I'm going to love you guys.
No, no, no.
No matter how many times I watch it, it's no good.
I don't think so.
It's really good.
The last one.
The one with domestic violence.
The one with Kato Masaru.
You can't even put him in a car.
Before you get in.
You can't say that.
You can't say that on the song of Miyuki Nagajima.
Don't say that.
I don't watch it at all.
I said I don't watch it.
I said I don't watch it at first.
I don't watch it.
I go to the factory and broadcast it.
Then go.
Apologize.
What are you doing?
You can't do that.
What do you mean?
You'll be released.
I have a gold под when I get in.
I'll look at you and hold you.
You're our..
You are wrong.
You are my students.
You have to do it again.
You don't have to do it again.
I'm like, don't forget it!
I'm crying so much.
I don't know anything about you.
I'm not looking at you!
Alright!
Where did Kato Masaru get a job?
You want to know?
Why did you have to ask me such a cult question with a blonde hair?
You should remember the Bokutou Kogyo!
The last one.
Well, I don't think that's true.
Whose hair is that?
It's a blonde hair!
I don't think that's true.
It's a blonde hair now?
If there's someone who wants to become a politician,
They'll say,
Give me 10,000 yen!
Give me a lot of money!
If there's someone who wants to work at a beauty salon,
They'll say,
Lend me some money until I'm tired.
I'm crying right now.
Why?
And if there's someone who wants to become a school teacher,
They'll say,
What's that word?
I'm already broke.
That's correct.
You remember?
Alright.
Where did Kato Masaru get a job?
I don't know.
I don't remember.
You just said it!
I just said it.
I don't know what to say.
I'll talk to you.
I'll talk to you for two weeks.
Two weeks?
Why two weeks?
No, really.
Let's be more moved.
Of course, I'm moved.
There are a lot of people who're moved all over the world.
You have to be more sensitive.
Ah, really?
That's right.
No matter what you see,
no matter what you see,
there are moments when you think,
Right?
Yeah, sometimes.
There are times when the washing machine goes like this.
You're doing your best!
It's work.
There are times when it goes like this.
It's worse if you put it in.
Lately, my impersonation has been polished again.
No, no.
The previous impersonation hasn't been polished at all.
Who's that?
That's Hibari.
Hama-chan.
I know that.
Anyone can do it.
Ussi-ssi-ssi.
Ah, Kyo-san?
Well, it's fine.
Go ahead.
You don't need a follow-up?
This is amazing.
Hama-chan's impersonation in Machikado.
I've done it before.
Someone introduced it before.
This is amazing.
It's similar.
It's not similar.
It's a picture of a school trip.
I took it.
Now, you're trying hard to look stylish.
You're trying hard to look stylish.
If you don't work hard, you'll be like this.
You'll be like this.
Now, Japan is having a problem because of water shortage.
Why is the sea water not decreasing?
That's the point.
That's what happened before.
This kind of story is usually told in fairy tales or old fairy tales.
Is that so?
It's usually like that.
Isn't it the same for all fairy tales?
What does Urashima Taro want to say?
He doesn't want to bully the turtle.
It's the same.
It's the same for all fairy tales.
What does Momotaro want to say?
Momotaro wants to say that we should pick up the big peach.
Why is the sea water not decreasing?
It's also in fairy tales.
What kind of story is it?
It's about a rabbit and a turtle.
It's called a rabbit and a turtle.
The rabbit wants to compete with the turtle.
Alright.
The turtle was slow.
Taro can win.
And there is a enterprisingeedkid.
When it starts the turtle is slow so it ran away.
The turtle was bored.
They slowly, slowly, one step at a time,
Yes, yes, yes.
They overtook the sleeping rabbit,
That's right.
And won.
Yes, yes, yes.
After that, the sea water turned into salt.
Yes, that's the end of the commercial.
Continue to the next part.
Foreigners often have a broken jaw.
Yes, there are.
Do you have a way to use it?
No, I don't.
Yes, there are.
Something is stuck.
Yes, yes, yes.
When I was told to line up in the center,
I didn't know how to match it.
In the center?
Do you match it with that?
If it's broken, you can line it up straight.
You don't have to line it up in front.
Why? How do you line it up?
What?
How do you line it up straight?
What are you talking about?
No, no, no.
Why are you so angry?
Who is that?
If you were told to line up here,
You can match your jaw with this hand.
Why?
If you have something to say, say it.
Come on, I'll answer you.
Jump in more.
If you jump in, you'll definitely get it back.
Who?
Me.
Americans are amazing.
Do you know?
I don't.
The other day, at McDonald's,
You know the coffee you bring home, right?
When you open it, you have to make a mistake.
It was really hot.
I see.
I suffered for six weeks.
Yes.
And I complained to McDonald's.
And that old lady bought it.
At the court?
McDonald's gave that old lady
250 million yen.
You paid for it?
I had to pay for it.
I told her to give me a lot of money.
It would be nice if you could use the minestrone.
That's right.
At the airport.
If I could use the minestrone, I wouldn't have to pay a single cent.
I was sitting here.
I was sitting on a macaroni.
I laughed a little.
Macaroni is like that.
It's a little stiff macaroni.
It's like a pirate ship.
I got it.
It's like a handle macaroni.
That's why I'm sitting here.
Even now, when I'm angry, it comes out.
Thank you for watching.