Getsu! Getsu! Getsu!
Thank you for your hard work this year as well. Today is the end of the year special project. We will be giving away the opening VTR best 10 of the 2003 Gaki no Tsukai.
This year, the former downtown manager, Fujiwara Hiroshi, has been chosen as the host for 6 consecutive years. His name is Dandy Fujiwara.
Getsu! Getsu! Getsu! Getsu! Getsu! Getsu!
This is all-star, isn't it? This is all-star, isn't it?
It's almost the end of the year, but this year, to celebrate, Tanaka-san got married, and Endo-san gave birth to a child.
I'll leave the first part to you. Why? Wait a minute. Stop it! Right? It's still Yama-chan's birthday. It's cold. Stop it!
I'm the one who's suffering the most. I'll do the things that aren't done in advance.
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
As an entertainer, even when he's drunk, he has to run on stage to perform a sudden attack on Momotaro while drinking. However...
Isn't that water? I can't stand this guy. I think the people who watch Yama-chan on TV are cold. They act like they're not drunk, but they're drunk.
I've seen it many times. It's cold in Yamazaki.
Grandma! Grandma! Who was it? Was it Masuda-san? Then I'll do it too.
I'm the one who's drunk. I'll do it next time.
Since the drama was so bad, he changed his role and tried again. But his appearance was so bad that he couldn't be called a play.
This is our child, Momotaro.
Then let's open this Kimi Dango.
Momotaro, bring the dog.
I don't remember my grandma doing it.
The 9th place is this project that Hamada went to the radio stock with a punishment game.
I don't like this.
What is it?
Hey, how long have you been waiting?
You're so noisy.
I don't know because I was told to come here.
You're the one who told me to come here.
You said you were going to beat Rajimel.
You're so noisy.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I don't know because I was told to come here.
The 9th place is the entertainment fishing competition held once a year.
Just like every year, a hot fishing battle has been held with a luxurious crowd.
This time, the two of them are close friends and did not catch a single fish.
Who will be the winner?
The winner is...
Tamayama Tenryu!
The winner is Tamayama Tenryu!
The 7th place is Shogeki Kokuhaku Omoide Byokan.
The person who turns the cards and hits the person who is talking has to confess the topic as their own experience group.
That's right!
My memories are good, right?
Why did you do that?
It's not easy.
You know, I...
I covered my face with ice hockey.
Who?
Me, me, me.
When you were a kid?
When I was a kid, yes.
But recently...
Recently?
Why?
I was so excited.
I covered my face with ice hockey and then with my eyes like this...
I killed him.
You shouldn't do that.
You're a pervert.
Who? Who?
The guy who was there.
I don't like that.
That was last month...
I mean, on Friday, the 13th.
You did it?
Yes.
There was a new one.
I was surprised.
Momotaro.
Yes?
You were sleeping when you met your grandma, right?
Who is this guy?
Was it really me?
You don't remember that?
You didn't move at all.
You didn't talk.
I really want to go home.
I want to do it again.
It was delicious.
Thank you.
Anyone can come on Friday the 13th.
I don't want to talk about the past.
It's hard to talk about the past.
Right?
Yes.
Get it!
I thought this was going to be delicious.
This project was made by the five of them.
All of them will eat what they made.
Yamasaki made a meal with yogurt, banana, and nata de coco.
I'm going to eat it.
What is this?
I'm not going to eat this.
I'll eat it.
It's hot.
Why is it so hot?
What kind of comment is that?
Tell me the taste.
It's so hot.
It's not burnt.
Eat the soft part.
Really?
Is it bad?
What kind of comment is that?
It's hell.
Hell?
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
It's like Ultraman when you hate it and want to go home.
This happened while the five of them were eating delicious ramen.
I'm going to eat it.
What are you doing?
I hate it.
You hate it?
What kind of comment is that?
You're a rude woman.
He regained his mind and went to another ramen shop.
But...
I'm sorry.
Can you stop the car?
Why?
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
He's running.
What are you doing?
Thank you.
He's running.
Stop it.
Because it's dangerous for an adult to fight on his own,
Matsumoto's suggestion is to exercise hard with a rune runner,
and then play against Nyu-san.
The result will be decided by the Nyu-san battle.
Matsumoto vs. Nyu-san
I hate it.
Don't let your guard down.
That's right.
Matsumoto vs. Nyu-san
The high-speed rotating group was defeated last year,
and this year a new one has been released.
The first opponent is the strong opponent, the Ota professional team.
Matsumoto vs. Nyu-san
Go, go, go.
This is the real deal.
Seriously.
Everyone, try it.
This is the real deal.
You think it's a joke, don't you?
You're wrong.
Matsumoto vs. Nyu-san
The strong opponent is Hamada, who has defeated the strong opponent.
Will he be able to win?
If you do it 38 times, you win.
I see.
If you do it 37 times, you get the same score.
I'm already at the limit of 50.
Let's do it.
Ready.
Start.
Yes.
I'm counting on you.
Let's win.
One.
I don't know at all.
I don't know what to do.
I'm going to do it.
What?
60.
I'm not going to do it anymore.
Yes, yes, yes.
I can speak.
What?
This is great.
I'm at the limit of 50.
I just kept going.
The counter...
I can't do it.
I'll go this way.
I can do it.
It's fast!
This is amazing.
It's really fast.
It's fast!
That's cheating!
Amazing!
Even if you fight against any team, you can win.
I can definitely win.
As long as Hamagawa-san is there.
As long as he's there.
He can definitely win.
Even if it's 500 times, he can win.
No, it can't be 500 times.
It's not 100 times, so it's the same.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, it can't be.
It can't be.
It's really good.
This is the project Hamada happened to see in the newspaper.
He went to catch a huge anago in the Tokyo Bay.
There's a big one in the middle.
But it wasn't easy to catch it because the opponent was there.
How many minutes have passed since you dropped it?
The anxiety of the five began to creep in.
At that time.
I think it's coming.
Not yet.
It's coming.
Put it here.
It's not coming.
It's coming.
Go, go, go.
Hurry up and lose.
My head hurts.
It's big.
Wait a minute.
You're good.
It's coming.
It's big.
It's amazing.
It's still a baby.
As the sun went down, huge anago came one after another.
It's heavy.
That's why I went.
That's the end.
Is that so?
It's amazing.
It's hard.
It's dry.
I can't get the rice out.
How did you eat this?
It's heavy.
That's why I went.
There is a festival in the book.
Women's festival.
I'm not laughing.
What?
What are you looking at?
I'm not laughing.
Please get a hold of yourself.
Ok?
Well...
I know!
I'm so sorry!
I tried to fix it many times.
I failed many times.
Well...
The gross man like you,
It was prepared by Hamada-san.
What the fuck are you?
You're so...
Please sum it up. I'll wait for one more time.
Hamada-san is really...
He's going to beat Kitahanki.
Anyway, the show is ready.
This is it.
Yamasaki.
I can't do it.
Itacho wants to say hello, is that okay?
Itacho.
I can't do it.
Yamasaki is out.
If there is anything you want to say about the show, please say it.
This is...
What should I say?
I don't know.
Say something.
Just once.
Don't get angry just because I used the eraser.
It's because you used the eraser.
Yamasaki is out.
Tonight is Yamada.
It's funny no matter where you film it.
Yamada is always so stubborn.
He always says that he won't laugh.
He's always like that.
If he gets proposed to, he'll say yes.
2003.
We can't talk about this guy without him.
Heikou, the main character of Gaki no Tsukai.
He's back on the scene this year.
For the third time, Heikou was exposed to the fear of the haunted house.
I'm not a ghost.
He was sentenced to death by the human breaker.
I'm scared.
Someone help me.
Peppo.
He's not here.
I'm sorry.
Where are you?
This happened when Yamada came to drink beer at the Hiroshima Carp next year.
I feel like I'm going to drown.
What are you doing?
I didn't do anything to anyone.
What is Peppo going to do next year?
Peppo is number one.
What do you think?
How old are you?
I'm going to be 50 this year.
I'm scared of ghosts, so please forgive me.
What do you think of Peppo?
I'm scared, so I can't help it.
I don't think it's a good idea.
I think it's natural.
It's natural to be on TV.
It's hard.
It feels like the 4th generation of the NAC.