Eh?
Congratulations!
This is from the staff.
It's from the heart.
Thank you very much.
Ah! Stop it!
It's still going to take some time.
Next time, at the Gaki no Tsukai Arai,
Chikichiki's new gym,
let's dance with Hiroko-chan!
Now...
The pain in the butt hurts.
What are you doing?
What do you know?
Today's opening is...
I'm going to do some new exercises.
Are you okay?
You haven't been using your body too much lately.
Sometimes it's good.
Today, I'm going to use my little finger.
Let's introduce him right away.
It's Hiroko Yamazaki-san!
Hello.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
You seem to be light.
What?
Ah, you're saying I'm thin?
Yes, you're saying you're going to be able to do it soon.
You're saying I'm light from the back of your mouth.
That's the only thing I can think of.
What do you mean I'm light?
You're really light, right?
Yes, I'm really light.
You idiot.
You're a fairy.
You've been teaching people how to do it for the first time, haven't you?
The other day, I did it with Ucchan-Nanchan's Sharara.
Please write it down.
I did it.
You were really good at it.
I'm really good at it.
That's right.
Comedians are really good at it.
Really?
They have a good head.
Like this.
Really, really.
I can't do it at all.
I'll teach you.
Yes.
First of all, I'll teach you the key points.
I'll show you how to do it.
That was a fierce attack.
Where are you going?
Hold on.
That's amazing.
I went to the Olympics.
It hurts.
What are the key points of the ball?
There are two difficult points.
The first is a big jump.
A big jump?
A big jump.
You have to step forward with your left foot.
Raise your right foot forward and leave your left foot behind.
That's Kin-chan.
That's right.
A wide balance.
Not yet.
A big jump.
I can't do it at all.
I'll show you how to do it.
The ball is difficult.
It's really difficult.
What would you score if you won the Olympics?
I can't do it.
I can't do it at all.
It's like a white butterfly floating on the water.
Hiroko-chan.
Yes.
Please show me how to throw it.
This?
This is impossible.
It's a little difficult.
Is that so?
For an amateur...
Don't make fun of me.
It's not high.
There's something like this.
Throw it over there.
I can't see it.
It's coming back.
This is amazing.
This is it.
Please show me how to throw it.
That's right.
I don't have time to change it.
Do your best.
More.
That's right.
Don't bend your legs.
It's difficult.
How was it?
Compared to Uchiyama Nan-chan.
It's not just physical training.
Practice is the first.
I'll give you this.
Let's have a confrontation next time.
Are you going to throw it?
I'll judge you.
That's a good idea.
Uchiyama-sensei.
I'll practice at home.
The people below are angry.
The clothes have changed.
I've been studying a lot lately.
What are you talking about?
You touch it.
Men touch it a lot.
They touch it a lot.
It's different from feeling.
It's meaningless.
It's meaningless to touch it.
It's a religious story.
You have to touch it.
I see.
I've been doing a lot of research lately.
I want you to listen to my research.
Why is the world so self-conscious?
It's a mass of self-consciousness.
Women are especially self-conscious.
Really?
Why?
Women used to walk on the street at night.
They don't have any intention.
But they want to be popular.
They want to be popular.
That's self-consciousness.
But there are people who are actually doing that.
I don't think so.
If I run away, I'll be angry.
If you run away, you'll be angry.
I'll sleep.
I sometimes think that men will be angry and do it.
If you do that, you'll be angry.
There are definitely women who get angry because of that.
There are 520,000 women in this summer.
Why?
520,000 women?
What is that?
That's a lot of women.
That's self-consciousness.
Even animals are self-conscious.
When I was in junior high school, I was a newspaper writer.
I wanted to put a newspaper in the newspaper.
Self-consciousness.
You didn't do anything.
That's not good.
That's self-consciousness.
What is self-consciousness?
A pigeon.
It doesn't eat.
I don't think so.
There are people who have been eaten.
That's not good.
That's self-consciousness.
Even children are self-conscious.
Children are like that.
Children come out.
I press the brake.
This hand is self-consciousness.
My car can't stop with your hand.
A cat is self-consciousness.
I'll hide it.
No one will see it.
Cats like to be beautiful.
I'll hide it.
No one will see your poop.
I'll take it.
There is no such thing as self-consciousness.
There are people who run.
I can't wait as much as you think.
What are you talking about?
If you say that, you can't do anything.
You are also self-conscious.
What are you talking about?
Everyone is self-conscious.
I'm just sitting.
That's wrong.
There is no such thing as self-consciousness.
Why is everyone self-conscious?
Who?
This?
Self-conscious.
Why?
This is self-consciousness.
You are thinking while saying.
I'm not thinking.
Why?
I don't need it.
Your hand is holding it.
I don't care.
Why?
I can't see it as much as you're trying.
You can see it.
It's in front of you.
Your hat is also self-conscious.
Why?
I don't want to see your head.
You're wearing it because you don't want to see it.
Why is the cameraman self-conscious?
It's self-conscious.
Why?
I don't need it.
Tell me right away.
Why?
What?
Tell me right away.
Why?
I don't want to see the color of your polo shirt.
It doesn't matter.
What?
Everyone says so.
This is Tokyo ramen.
Really?
I don't understand.
I will continue my research.
There is no research.
It's self-conscious.
It's not self-conscious.
Why?
What?
Everyone says so.
There is a woman.
She is a good woman.
But she wants me.
There is a woman who wants you.
I want you.
Don't say that.
I didn't say that.
I don't want you.
What kind of woman do you want me to be?
There is a woman who wants to hug you.
I don't know.
I am old now.
I'm old.
There is an old woman.
I am a dirty old woman.
I don't see you.
I open my legs and see you.
What is this?
This is dirty.
No, it's just that I can't find the right position.
It's strange, isn't it?
If you don't live carefully, I'll be watching you.
I don't have a blind spot.
Even if you're watching, there are only a few people.
There's no way everyone will be watching.
You're just watching because you don't want to.
You think it's a skier lover, don't you?
It's not like that.
It's like a woman riding a car with a woman.
That's enough.
It's a highway.
I said, let's go to my room.
You said, huh?
You're asking me to go see a doctor.
Why are you saying, huh?
I know you're a human being, so why are you saying, huh?
You've already taken one step into the room.
You're always like that, huh?
You're not going to do anything when I give you a room like that, are you?
You're lying, huh?
If I ask her if she can help me with my knowledge, she doesn't listen to me
If that's the case, I'll go!
Isn't that a bit too much?
You're talking and then you close the door and start talking
It's not like that, but I'll do it
Hagi!
Where was I hiding?
You never show your staff
Today you're dressed like this
Hello
Let me introduce you
Hey!
That's dirty!
Did you really just come out?
When you went like this, you looked like a capsule
I said before that I was going to go
Even then, when you went like this, you looked like a capsule
Capsule?
There are times when you look like a grain
What's white?
Fuji-kun, Nao-chan
Go ahead
It's okay, I'm saying it in front of you
She's 20 years old
She read the book
Eiken 39
Tekondo 59
You're lying!
Did you refuse to train?
You said you didn't want to train
Is there something wrong with your body?
Is there something wrong with your stomach?
I forgot, it's cool
There's a hole here
Is there something cool about it?
Do you want it?
I don't care
It's starting to stand out
It's not me!
Thank you
I heard you released a photo book
What is it?
Did it sell well?
My friend is looking for it in a bookstore
I heard it wasn't in a certain country
I don't think you'll find it
Tell her to give up
I saw it in Osaka the other day
It's still selling well in Osaka
How much did it sell?
It's amazing
I think it sold well
The page in the middle
I can't see the two of them
They were in a state similar to Zenra
It felt good
Even though it was a joke
They were doing well
They were over 5
Let's talk about this
This is 18-year-old Minako from Saitama
Have you two had a scary experience?
Please tell us
The other day, I saw a ghost-like thing
with the left half of Mach-chan and the right half of Hama-chan
It's scary
I saw a dream where I was chased and ran away crying
You ran away
It's scary
It's not that scary
It's not scary
It's just a sad story
I've never seen it
There are times when I feel like something is going to happen
When you hear a sound
Even if you're in a room
Like a sound
Why does it sound like that?
It's like a rap
It's proof that it came out
Like a click
No, no
It's not like that
It's like that
Why does it sound like that?
It's not like that
It's like a click
The click is old
It's not like that
It's like a floor
What is that?
I don't think it's a rap
Why does it sound like that?
When there's nothing in the middle of the night
That's a rap
What does that mean?
It came out
I can't see it
You can see it
It came out
Why?
It's a rap
Don't ask me that
I get it
Rap
Why does it sound like that?
What are you talking about?
Isn't it strange?
Isn't there a time when you sing?
I don't know
You're scary
You don't feel like it
You don't know
Ah
If you say that
I'm scared
Ah
I don't know
Whose ghost is it?
I'm scared
For example, if I die
If I die
If I come out, are you scared?
I'm scared
In a different sense
I don't know what to do
That's not it
Are you scared?
If I come out, are you scared?
I don't do anything
I just come out
I'm sleeping
Are you scared?
I don't know
I'm scared
I can only see you
I can't see anyone else
I'm always there during the day
When I die
I come out
I can only see you
I'm always there during the day
You can see me
Yes
I don't come out
I can't see anyone else
I can't come out
I'm always there
Ah
That's amazing
Hey
Today, we did the opening
We did
It was difficult
You watched it
I think it was good
My body is getting better
That's right
My body
I don't play
What do you think about
the battle with
Uchiyama?
Ah
If he
does it according to
my schedule
If he does it
according to my schedule
I don't care
He's busy
Uchiyama?
Yes
Masaki
has a lot of work
Then
I can't refuse him
Well
If it's according to
my schedule
I can do it
And
Next week
I'll do the
child's play
I'll do it
All the guests
are men
I don't know
Please look forward to it
And
send me more costumes
Well
I don't care
about you
Well
I don't care
There's a limit to what we can do
Well
There are fans
and fans
Please send me
all the costumes
Thank you
And
I'll do the child's play
Hey
I don't know
I don't care