Kotonohottan was in the middle of recording last week's talk.
You know the one you open the bottom of the kitchen?
And you put a bowl or something on it?
I have one like this.
You can put four of them with the tape.
But this is...
This is definitely not good!
This is life!
I know that.
You open it, right?
You put it on, right?
You put it on the bottom, right?
You're crazy!
Matsumoto, who can't control his anger, began to draw more details after the show.
I think I did four of them.
And then...
Like this.
What the hell is this angle?
And then...
Bang!
What was I supposed to look for?
Let's look for this.
He decided to look for the problem.
But Hamada, his partner, doesn't care at all.
How do I look for it?
Like this.
Like this?
I don't need to look for it.
Does the Otamakake family, who has such a mediocre look, really exist in this world?
With his sharp sense of observation and unrivaled insight, Mr. Matsumoto challenges the root of evil that lurks in modern society.
Mr. Matsumoto, Cutting off Society.
Otamakake's Review.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
Suddenly, downtown went to look for Otamakake's problem.
Mr. Matsumoto, isn't it around here?
There's a hook like this.
It's not like this.
It's like this.
It's down here.
Around here.
This is...
This is Otamakake.
This...
This is terrible.
This hook.
The color is different, but the angle is close to mine.
It's like this, isn't it?
It's close, isn't it?
It's not like this, is it?
Look at this.
If it's like this...
This is good, too.
If it's like this, there's no problem at all.
It's straight.
Let's try this.
This?
Yes, let's try it.
What's that?
It's gas.
Let's do an experiment with Otamakake.
The shape is a little different, but the angle is close.
It's almost close.
What is this?
It's an unbeatable angle.
Let's try it.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Let's go.
We're going to do a commercial here, aren't we?
Let's do it.
Let's go.
I can't do it.
Two out of three have fallen.
But I can't help it.
You know, when you're cooking, you want to do it well.
At that time, you can do it like this.
I'm in a hurry.
What are you doing with this?
This is a little different.
But I can't help it.
It's okay.
Right?
Yes.
I've been saying this all the time.
Why do I say this so strongly?
This is a matter of life and death.
You're kidding me.
This has fallen in the kitchen.
This has nothing to do with people.
What are you looking at?
I got it.
Let's buy something like this.
This is the real deal.
What?
This is a disaster.
This is the real deal.
Let's go.
Where are we going?
I'll show you the horror of Otamakake.
Let's go.
Why does this Otamakake have to do with people?
The car is going to a certain place with Hamada on it.
Mr. Machan.
We've come to such a place.
Isn't it okay?
I'll show you the shocking video from the back.
I'm not going to shock you.
It's just going to fall.
I'll show you again.
It's all going to fall.
Why is this so small?
Let's zoom in on this shocking video.
This is what happens when you zoom in.
Let's shake the camera.
Here you go.
This is what happens.
Are you two idiots?
I'm here with Jimmy today.
Why are you here with Jimmy?
I want you to experience it with your body.
This is what was faithfully reproduced until the end of Otamakake.
This is a disaster.
This is impossible.
I want you to see what's going on.
I'll choose two people who don't have numbers.
I'm a talent.
If you use a talent with numbers, it will go in a different direction.
This is not a punishment game.
I see.
This is an experiment.
Let's open it.
I can't stop it.
What are you doing?
You look happy.
It's 40 and 33.
Is that so?
It's 41.
Let's reproduce it.
I'll press this button.
Let's go.
Switch on.
You fell.
You fell on your face.
Hurry up.
This is dangerous.
I saw the camera.
This is a disaster.
You have to raise the angle of Otamakake Hook.
Look at this.
This is what happened.
I wanted to say this after two weeks.
Say it in the talk.
Everyone was listening to the joke.
The staff of Gaki no Tsukai are being carried.
You did it.
After this, there was an unexpected development for Matsumoto.
Matsumoto.
I found out one thing.
What is it?
Look at this.
This is a new truth.
I wanted to surprise you.
This is the hook I bought at the store.
Look at this.
The hook of this angle is attached to the back of the door.
The hook you are talking about is attached here.
The hook you are talking about is attached to the back of the door.
He said something good.
What does this mean?
This is the wrong place to attach the hook.
If you have any questions, please come to the show.
We will solve it.
Do you have any questions?
There is a parking lot at KO Plaza Hotel.
I can't park my car there.
I see.
Do you know where to park your car?
I don't know.
I thought it was attached to the back of the car.
When I parked my car, I went to the wall.
Let's go to KO Plaza Hotel.
There are many people today.
There are many people.
I'm scared.
Today is not a very interesting day.
I'm stupid.
Today is not a good day.
What are you talking about?
I heard that GAKIMIZU is selling well.
As expected, my strategy is correct.
I'm scared.
I'm selling well.
I can't sell well.
Is it bad?
It's not good.
I have a cold coat.
I think you have one or two.
I failed.
Do you have one?
I have one.
I don't have one.
Does it have anything to do with us?
You are a bad person.
Don't say that.
Do you like money so much?
Why?
You like money so much.
Don't say that.
If there is a 500 yen coin in a high place, you will climb it.
It's hard to find it.
I don't like high places.
If there is money, you will climb it.
You will definitely climb it.
I said it in the opening.
KO Plaza.
Why did you go there?
It's a conference.
It's nothing.
It's not a conference.
It's like a conference.
Why did you go to a conference?
I went to a conference when I was in junior high school.
I didn't go there.
Hamada went to a conference.
I went to a conference after a long time.
I didn't go there.
Don't laugh.
I went to a conference after a long time.
I didn't go there.
It's my story.
Can you see it?
If you go there, the parking lot is strange.
Look, it's wide, right?
It's wide and
where the cars bump into each other
there's a proper car stop.
That's right.
Like this.
Everyone is there.
The wall is open, so
on the wall,
like this,
Wait, wait!
Keio brother, look at this.
Jonathan, look at this.
Bunta!
He's the closest!
So,
I wonder if I can go like this.
I wonder if I can stop.
I'm bumping into the wall.
There's no car stop.
So, this is...
My car's rear is
damaged.
I can't help it.
It's a driver's mistake.
What?
It's a driver's mistake?
I'm being called a driver's mistake.
But, that's a driver's mistake.
What?
This is strange.
But,
you have to check it.
Normally,
it's narrow and dark.
It's narrow and dark.
But, when you open the door,
you can't go back like this.
What?
You can't do this.
When you open the door,
you can't go back like this.
So, you have to go like this.
There's a wall, right?
You have to go like this.
This is
really strange.
Kei-Pla's fault.
I'm amazing, aren't I?
That was interesting.
Thank you.
Thank you, Kei-Pla.
Kei-Pla.
Mr. Matsumoto,
from the top,
you're 84, 58, and 85.
It's a nice proportion.
What's the secret of your beauty?
Do you know where my office is?
I'm a yellow cab.
A huge army.
I'm...
A yellow cab?
I'm a yellow cab.
Oh, really?
I really am.
But you don't really look at swimsuits.
That's because
I'm 32.
I think I'm getting old.
In the past,
I was amazing.
Oh, really?
I was already
very popular around here.
I was already very popular
with everyone around here.
That's interesting.
Do you know what I mean?
Don't say that.
No, no.
I'm getting old.
Did you use silicone?
I didn't use it.
I'm getting old.
I was a boccon.
I was a boccon girl.
That was my catchphrase.
Well,
I can't do it anymore.
You can't do it.
It's strange that you're still here.
There's nothing here.
That's not true.
Do you want me to tell you?
I was a boccon.
I was.
Ever since then,
my tongue was
boccon.
It was like this.
It was dented.
So,
it was drooping and coming back.
That's gross.
So,
my boccon
was like this
on a sculpture.
I understand.
I was a boccon girl
from the land of the stars.
Why did you say that?
You should have said that
from the land of the stars.
That's fine.
I don't want to talk about that.
So,
84, 58, 85.
I think
this is just my
proportion,
isn't it?
This is
my point.
I bought it
when I was a boccon.
A boccon?
I bought it.
Yes.
Why did you buy it?
So,
80, 58, 85.
My opponent
is 83, 50...
What number is that?
Your opponent is...
What are you doing?
This is my final point.
I understand.
What did you do?
So,
I bought it.
I made up my mind.
What?
So,
let me borrow your pen.
Why?
I made up my mind
so it's 85.
You made up your mind
so what did you do?
That's why I bought it.
You bought it.
I bought it in a three set match.
Three set match?
I bought it.
So,
what kind of game is this?
What kind of game is this?
What did you do
to make it 85?
That's not a problem now.
I bought it.
It doesn't matter
if I won this.
I played a cross game.
I didn't lose.
So,
you played an A.C.I.
what did you do?
In the end,
it was around here.
So,
I somehow won.
But,
I didn't do it on purpose.
So,
I was around here
and the opponent was here.
A cross game?
So,
I won because
the opponent was at the end
and I won because
the opponent was at the end.
What?
Why did you win?
It's a strange story.
If you win,
it won't be 85.
You don't know anything
about the game at all.
If you win,
it's a minus point.
That's why
I'm telling you
to teach me.
What is it?
So,
are you running?
Running?
I don't run.
If I run,
I'll lose.
I'll be eliminated.
What?
Eliminated?
Yes, I'll be eliminated.
Where do you do it?
What do you mean?
Where is the place?
Pool, pool.
Pool,
poolside.
Look,
I'll tell you a good place.
Do you do it
at such a small place?
No.
You shouldn't run.
Well,
it's a poolside.
You'll be scolded.
You'll be eliminated.
You shouldn't run.
You shouldn't be eliminated.
So,
Chaya,
you don't know anything.
Are you okay?
In the end,
I'm fine.
Let me win.
In the end,
I won at 184, 58, 85.
I know that.
I won at Kokutai.
Why do you praise me for that?
No,
it's not like that.
My memories from when I was 29.
Why do you try to make it sepia-colored?
I don't know.
I didn't mean that.
So,
I want to say congratulations on winning.
tell me how you won.
I finally said congratulations.
No,
no, no.
You should have said it.
I didn't mean it.
No, no, no.
What did you say?
I wanted to say that.
You changed your mind.
When you were in your early twenties,
you were the AD of a TV station in Osaka.
Yes.
It seems that there was a legendary
legendary ball game.
That's right.
Please show us the magic trick
once again.
What kind of game did you play?
Well,
I played Adribland.
You played it every day.
I played Ikanimosuminyo.
I played it every day.
What?
I was called the pawn of the day.
My AD taught me that.
Your AD is no good.
I don't know why.
You know why.
I don't have the motivation
to play the real game.
You mean that?
Yes, yes.
Can you show me?
A normal AD.
It's okay.
4, 3, 2, 9.
I don't know where to start.
You can say 9.
9.
4, 3, 2.
No, no.
It's hard to understand.
It's annoying.
Why?
No, no.
It makes me angry.
I was like this.
I can't move right away.
Your hands are like this.
Like this.
I can move right away no matter what I do.
I can't move.
Why?
I can move right away.
Your legs.
Why?
I can't move.
I can move.
What?
I can't move.
It's annoying.
Why can't you move?
You can move from here.
I can't move.
I'm stretching my legs.
That's not good.
Why?
And then like this.
When did you do that?
When I was watching the show.
A round of applause.
A sign of applause.
It's harder for the audience to understand.
The audience will clap like this.
It's weird if you do this.
You don't know what to do.
No, no.
If you do this.
I can't do it.
What should I do?
Like this.
I'm doing it on my own.
It's an imaginary ball.
I forgot.
I'm glad you forgot.
Like this.
Can I?
I can't stretch my legs.
You said it was a ball.
Why can't you stretch your legs?
It's always like this.
I hate it.
I can't stretch my legs.
Like this.
Five seconds.
Four.
Three.
Hurry up.
I'm coming.
I can't do it.