No.3
I didn't see that coming.
Happy New Year.
Today we have a special project for the new year.
We will give you the best VTR of 2002.
This year, we have chosen the former downtown manager,
the current producer of Lumineda Yoshimoto,
Hiroshi Fujiwara.
I will call him by his first name.
Nice to meet you.
You have nothing to do with this program.
Why do you only do this?
Thank you.
Really, please.
How was last year?
You watched it, right?
Yes, I watched it.
You were active.
Except for Yama-chan.
Wait a minute.
You watched it, right?
Yes, I watched it.
And Yamazaki-san too.
Is that so?
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
First of all, the best VTR of 2002.
From 10th to 7th place.
VTR Kuru-Kuru-Kuru.
It's strange that Azarashi is in the center.
Don't call him Azarashi.
It's Tama-chan.
That's no good.
Based on the information we received,
we went to see Tama-chan, who caused a big fever this summer.
Come here.
Who?
It's Tama-chan.
Look, look.
It's not.
It's Tama-chan.
Shut up.
One, two.
Tama-chan.
It's embarrassing.
Let's go home.
That's good.
What's wrong?
What's this?
It's Tama-chan.
It's Pride Day.
I'll do it like a role-playing.
One, two.
Tama-chan.
It's Tama-chan.
It's amazing.
It's good that we saw a lot.
Hey.
What's wrong?
What?
Hey.
One, two.
Tama-chan.
It's looking.
It's looking that way.
In order to get rid of his daily work, Chidou came to Odaiba with the help of Producer Suga.
For some reason, this project has become a battle between ordinary people and menchi.
It's not working at all.
I've never cut menchi before.
I'm sorry.
Hey, Miko-san.
What are you doing?
I'm sorry.
You're a friend, aren't you?
It's a good idea.
I was really scared.
Let's see the car.
Is it there?
Yes.
Let's see.
This is...
This is impossible.
Hey, give me a break.
You're a friend, aren't you?
Even though you're big.
The annual big event, the entertainment fishing competition.
This time, the first time that Asano Torobu has participated.
The gorgeous Kaobure has gathered in Kaguchiko and has had a hot fishing battle.
I'm so sad.
So the winner is...
The winner is...
I see.
Matsumoto, who lost in the Japanese series, is throwing the pie.
But Matsumoto doesn't react at all.
No reaction pie hell.
It's time for the big one.
It's hard, isn't it?
I'm going to throw up.
He dropped the towel.
Wait a minute.
I'm going to die.
The 7th place is like this.
This is the most recent punishment game.
This is...
I've been told many times.
You've been told.
That it's hard.
I want to have a match with someone else and do it.
This is the most popular punishment game.
Yes, we did it.
It's the first time that Aroha-chan did it.
It's your debut, isn't it?
Yes, it's my debut.
I said I was going to do it twice, but I'm going to do it once.
The opponent is...
Who is it?
Kijime Shiro.
Thank you.
You dropped it.
Why did you drop it?
I don't know.
Kijime Shiro, the guest, suddenly fell into a pitfall.
The man-to-man cooking battle started unexpectedly.
I can't do it today.
I don't think you should say that.
Do you know what I was doing?
I don't know.
I'll sell more money.
I don't want to do it.
Kijime, who was completely upset by this incident, went home.
However, Ichidou managed to persuade Kijime to continue recording.
The first episode of Gaginotsukai Yaraen.
The man-to-man cooking battle in the entertainment world.
The second episode of Gaginotsukai Yaraen.
Today's guest is Kijime Shiro.
This is a cooking battle.
Let's start.
I'm sorry.
What do you mean you're sorry?
I only have money.
Thank you.
Ouch.
What is it?
I can't move.
Yamasaki, who is expected to record suddenly.
Then, Suga.
Wait a minute.
Let's go.
Yamasaki.
Yamasaki, wait a minute.
I'm sorry.
I can't take a picture.
I did it.
Right after this, Hamada and Tanaka are down.
Hamada.
Well.
I'm sorry.
What happened?
Match.
Match?
Yes.
Let's cooking.
Somehow, the members who came back to the studio immediately started the cooking battle.
But here, Endo.
Ouch.
What's wrong, Endo?
Are you okay, Endo?
Suga.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
How about Endo?
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
Are you feeling down?
What?
I'm feeling down.
I need to cheer up.
Endo, what's wrong?
Do you want to put your finger in?
I don't have enough time.
And after this, Matsumoto is also down.
Ah.
Are you okay?
I'm worried.
I'll do my best.
OSU! Ikidomebu is aiming to be the number one in the entertainment industry.
The first opponent is the strong opponent, the team from the north of OSU.
First, Hamada appears.
The opponent is Taka Gadarukana.
The 50-second wall.
One minute left.
Wow.
I wanted to go for one minute.
Ready.
Start.
I'm counting on you.
Okay, it's done.
45 seconds.
Okay.
Okay, it's done.
It's really amazing.
It's just a half-cut.
And finally, it's the final battle.
Matsumoto is going for the victory.
Start.
Okay.
Don't use the oil.
It's okay.
You're coming back.
It's done.
30 seconds.
Wow.
Ready.
Start.
He's being cornered.
Okay.
He looks like a bad guy.
Why are you doing that?
30 seconds have passed.
He's coming back.
Yama-chan is coming back.
Look.
He's coming back.
Wait.
So close.
Only 5 seconds left.
This is the last round.
The first round.
How many times have you done this?
Only 2 times.
But you haven't done it once.
No.
That's right.
9 seconds is terrible.
It's terrible.
Really?
Yes.
That's not good.
If you say it like that, we can't say anything.
What should we do?
It's scary.
You don't have a lot of life force.
Matsumoto lost to the Hamada team in a race.
The 5 members of the family will make an interview.
The action show will be broadcast live for 5 minutes in the morning.
Are you okay?
Matsumoto family is having fun with the family for the first time in a long time.
It's just 2 legs.
But the fried chicken is delicious.
You put a lot of salmon in the rice.
It's strange.
I didn't put rice in it.
Have you ever put chicken in it?
The fried chicken is delicious.
Why didn't you sell it?
I haven't eaten it for 10 years.
The fried chicken is delicious.
And finally the real show.
I'm waiting for my dad.
I thought it was about time.
Someone help me.
Help me.
I don't know anyone.
I'm going to faint from here.
What is this?
This is a broadcast.
I didn't see it.
I don't remember the sound.
It's nice to have a family.
Everyone, take care of your family.
Bye bye.
I don't remember anyone.
It's a commercial.
I'm number two.
One day, the person who was called by Yamazaki stepped into the mystery world.
Are you still using Korn?
That's why I gave you a chance to use Korn.
In this mystery world, the 16th century is France.
There are four gold coins.
If you can find it, I'll give you a great treasure.
This is how the treasure hunt began.
But after this, Yamazaki World was waiting.
Everyone, did you understand?
I've been working for Gilbert for 25 years.
My name is Audrey.
I work for Gilbert.
Because Gilbert is cool.
Your adventure will continue.
Yamazaki wants the four of them to go to the haunted house.
Hamada and Endo will enter the house.
I'm scared.
Let's go together.
Why?
I don't want to.
Shut up.
I'm scared.
I don't want to.
Shut up.
And as if they finally reached the goal, they found the wonderful treasure.
I'm scared.
Everyone, let's go.
1, 2, 3.
It's a waste.
It's really a waste.
It's going up.
It's over.
It's coming out.
Hello.
This is what Yamazaki wanted to do.
This is 2.
This is...
This is not what I wanted.
I think Komu put it in.
Komu really likes Yamazaki.
When he was doing that, he kept laughing.
He likes it.
It's terrible.
It's so noisy.
He panicked.
I don't know why it's open on Wednesdays.
Hello.
This is a popular snack in Japan.
Are you okay?
You drank too much.
Why is this my friend?
Sit down.
I can't stand it.
Wait a little.
Wait.
Amazing.
He can't help it.
He can't win.
Do you have more?
He's good.
He's doing it until the end.
This is the first time in four years.
That's right.
It's the 10th place.
I hope you will do your best this year.
I want to see Yamada.
Yamada, what do you think?
This is Yamada.
This program is provided by the sponsor you see.