Next, Matsumoto Yamasaki vs. Kokoriko.
The budget is 1000 yen.
The Gekuman Cooking Contest!
As the title says, today we are a team.
We are divided into two teams.
Cooking Contest.
The title is 1000 yen.
1000 yen!
The budget is 1000 yen.
Now, we will be having a competition in this shopping district.
And at the end, you cook for me.
And I eat.
And you say, it's good!
It's good!
I'll eat this one too!
I'll be in trouble if I keep warming up.
Oh, really?
I'll be like, let's do this, let's do this.
That's fine anytime.
It's not like a school.
I'll be like, should I go crazy?
I'll be like, go crazy.
You won't lose, right?
I'll never lose.
This is omurice.
Oh.
Omurice.
I can't say anything anymore.
I already said it.
You're an idiot.
I can't say anything.
This program was provided by the sponsors you see.
I'm weak.
I can't say anything.
Then, let's go.
Alright.
Let's go.
Well, I can't say anything about this omurice.
I don't know if I'll go home or not.
I'll keep it a secret.
Just the two of us.
Look, look.
There's no way he's hungry.
That's because of the ingredients.
I see, I see.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
What?
What's wrong?
I have a stomachache.
A stomachache?
What?
You have a stomachache?
Are you okay?
I don't know what's going on.
I'm sorry.
I have a stomachache.
That's right.
Really?
Can you wait a bit?
I'll take you.
Are you sure?
I can't do it if you don't do that.
What's with you?
You looked fine earlier.
Please give me a little time. I'll do something.
What?
Yes, I'll do something.
Tanaka is fine too.
Really?
Let's continue.
Where do we start?
Let's start from where we left off.
So, we're going to start with the first team.
What are you going to make?
I'm going to make rice omelette.
Rice omelette is the best.
I'll decide what I want to make.
What about Tanaka?
We haven't decided yet.
What is it?
Can I ask you to do something?
I'm going to buy some soup.
You're going to buy soup?
What is this?
I bought it!
The team that bought it first bought tofu!
I see.
What about the team that bought it last?
We definitely need this.
What? What? What?
Chicken.
Ah, chicken!
That's right.
We have something to buy too.
Really?
I'll take it.
Then, the Kogoriko team too.
85 yen.
It's cheap.
The chicken is really cheap.
You're really good.
You're from a normal team.
Stop it.
I'll go look for a pork team.
I've been looking for it for a long time.
It's really cheap.
The Kogoriko team.
There it is.
The cheapest one?
The cheapest one.
It's not like the taste of the stomach.
It's different.
Did you find the ¥114?
This is fine.
Ok, I found it. ¥114 is cheap.
It's like a hidden taste.
It's a big voice.
It's good.
It's a hidden taste.
Really? Hidden taste?
I'll go with the sweet one.
Okay, I'll go with the sweet one.
What should we do?
There's a cheap one.
But we don't need you.
No, it's fine.
It's me.
Hey, Yama-chan.
Here it is.
What's wrong?
What is it?
I can't move.
What?
I did it.
I'm surprised.
You want it?
Really?
Really, really, really.
It's still a wine.
I'm sorry.
You are not good at it.
I was bad at it.
You were bad at it.
You hurt a little in the previous match.
I have a habit of it.
Really?
It hurts?
It hurts.
I can't move.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Samu-san.
Zaki-san, are you okay?
I bought wine.
I'm sorry.
Sorry.
Are you okay?
I'm sorry.
What?
Zaki-san, are you okay?
Like the other day?
No, no, no.
Excuse me, wait.
Ouch, ouch, ouch, ouch.
Take him away.
Hey, hey, hey.
Hurry up and come here.
Zaki-san.
Zaki-san, are you okay?
Soga-chan, what are you going to do?
I'm in trouble.
Please give me a little time. I'll do something.
Really?
Yes. Please wait a moment.
Let's go.
Yamazaki! Yamazaki!
Please wait a moment.
Yamazaki, it's okay.
Let's go.
You're being filmed by the product, right?
The 3 of us.
Is it okay?
You're using the hidden camera properly?
Yes, I'm using the hidden camera.
I did it!
Our team...
I want to buy it at the drugstore.
Really?
Let's go to Yaoya next time.
Yaoya, yes.
What was it?
Yaoya...
Ah, there it is.
Then I'll go there.
Let's go.
Welcome!
Ah, I see.
I haven't eaten yet.
Yes, yes, yes.
What did you eat?
Ah, onion and...
What?
Masuo-san.
I'll go there.
Onion and...
Yes.
I'll go there.
Onion, onion.
Ah...
I feel sick.
Are you okay?
Yes.
What?
I'm fine.
It's hard.
It's a break-up.
Please give me a little time. I'll do something.
I'll do something.
I'll buy eggs.
Tanaka, Tanaka, Tanaka, Tanaka.
Right, right, right, right.
Ah, there it is.
It's an egg.
I don't need a teacher like you.
Ah, I don't need one.
This is Yamanagi Achiya.
Ah, sorry.
Then, I'll go with this.
Onion and egg.
Sorry.
Hamada.
Already, that one.
Yes.
Already, I'm almost done.
Already, here.
Yes.
Ah, really.
It's about time.
Hurry up.
Yes.
Oh, good morning.
Good morning.
What's up?
I'm here.
You're here.
Yamazaki?
Yamazaki.
Oh, excuse me.
Excuse me.
You should have bought more.
Oh, really, you're so rude.
Are you paying properly?
Yes, I am.
How much do you have?
Do you have enough?
Yes, I do.
I have about 250 yen left.
I have.
Oh, excuse me.
Oh.
I've bought everything.
Really?
What do you want?
It's over.
What?
I'm fine with omurice.
Are you sure?
Yes.
Then both teams are fine.
Then go back to the studio.
Yes.
The game of rock-paper-scissors.
Are you sure?
You need to get more fired up.
I'm Tanaka.
Get fired up.
Don't say that now.
The game of rock-paper-scissors.
Let's go.
Yes.
Hey.
Sorry, sorry.
Hamada-san will get angry.
Sorry, Hamada-san.
So, the Ryo team is here.
Today, we will be making the omurice.
We have already said it.
The omurice is ready.
Are you ready?
Yes, I'm ready.
Hamada-san hasn't said it yet, but we will be making it.
We'll eat it after it's done.
Please judge.
I'll eat it.
Please.
What's wrong?
Your face...
Your face is not good.
Your eyes are not good?
A little.
You don't seem to be calm.
You're not confident as usual?
I'm not confident.
Yes.
Then, let's start the cooking competition.
DETSURI COOKING!
Then, Yamada-san.
I'll cut the meat.
You are basically a person who eats things.
Yamazaki.
Yes, I'm sorry.
Why are you sorry?
What's wrong with you?
No, I'm sorry.
Ouch!
What's wrong, Endo?
Are you okay, Endo?
Hey, Sugachan.
Sugachan, Endo, can you go to the bathroom?
Sugachan, can you go to the bathroom?
Let's go.
Let's go to the bathroom.
Sugachan, please.
Are you okay?
Are you okay, Endo?
Sorry.
What's wrong, Sugai-chan?
Then, give me a little time.
Alright.
How's the performance?
It's fine.
I've changed.
You've changed?
Really?
You're good at cooking.
I've changed.
Really?
Your tension has dropped, hasn't it?
Huh?
My tension is low.
Tension up more.
What's wrong, Endo?
Your finger hurts?
That's a little different.
You need to get more excited.
More, Endo.
I want to cheer for you.
Yes.
You understand?
You still have to watch the enemy's moves.
I'm sorry.
Endo, this is too much.
Endo, Endo.
Hey, it's done!
Matsumoto!
What's wrong?
Matsumoto, are you okay?
Are you okay?
What's wrong, Matsumoto?
Matsumoto, are you okay?
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
Are you okay?
Hey, Sugashira!
Yes, yes, yes.
Hey, you're here again.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Sugashira.
Are you okay?
Matsumoto, are you really okay?
I'm okay.
Everything but my heart hurts.
Everything but your heart hurts?
Everyone, come here.
Hey, Mr. Okada, please end this.
Are you okay?
What?
I'm sorry.
Why did you ask me if I'm okay?
I'm okay.
Please give me some time. I'll do something.
Is Matsumoto okay?
I'm worried.
Matsumoto!
Matsumoto, are you okay?
I'm worried.
Are you okay?
Matsumoto.
I'll do it properly.
Yes, yes, yes. I'm sorry.
Matsumoto!
You're suddenly getting a beard.
Matsumoto is big.
I've gotten a little bigger.
I'm sorry.
I'm done!
The end is okay, right?
Okay, okay.
I'll roll it up.
I'll put this on.
Please put it on my face.
I can't move.
Matsumoto, do it more.
Do it more.
I'm sorry.
Matsumoto, what are you doing today?
Now, the dish is ready.
I'm going to eat it.
It's delicious.
It's delicious, Yamazaki!
Hamada, this is really good.
Eat it.
It's definitely good.
Look, it's really good.
Yes, yes, yes.
Excuse me.
This is really good.
Really good.
D.R.
I failed.
Good evening.
This is a sad story, isn't it?
You didn't do anything on TV, and you're still laughing.
That's a lousy story, isn't it?
You can't laugh about that.
No, no, really, you can't laugh about that.
That's true.
Well, well, well, how was it?
Recently?
There are things that you've shown your face to, but...
I don't show my face at all.
You don't show at all?
Yes, yes.
Oh, really? That's not funny.
What is?
I'm not, either.
Really, there's nothing.
It's not funny.
You'll crash when you get home.
I'll never crash.
Why do you say that?
I can avoid it.
You may think it's a joke, but I'm probably the best driver in the world.
Do you know what a possible driving is?
What?
A possible driving.
Everyone, please remember this.
It's a secret.
I don't care.
Let's keep the word, maybe, in our mind.
What?
Let's put it on a sheet.
Let's put it on a drive.
Let's save it on a radiator.
Save it on a radiator?
Maybe!
Shut up!
I knew it.
If you say something like this, you might get hit.
You know,
you can't push it at the police station.
Yes.
It's possible that they'll come.
Yes, it's possible.
Everyone knows that. Everyone who has a license knows that.
But everyone's possibility is quite high.
The society is very generous.
What?
Well then, well then, well then.
Get on.
I don't want to be ignored.
Then what kind of possibility are you thinking about?
Hey.
What?
Is there any way to know if someone will suddenly appear from the side?
Say it properly with the word, maybe.
There is no such thing as maybe.
There are many elderly people.
They may appear from the side.
Say it more, maybe.
Say it faster!
There may be elderly people appearing from the side!
That is the problem.
Why?
What is that? It may be the elderly.
Is it okay to end it at that point?
It may be the old man.
It may be the old lady.
People are people.
What is the way you drive the old lady?
It may be the old lady.
Of course, it may be all of me.
It may be possible to get a wiper.
What did you do?
This is not a security problem.
Let's make it a pattern.
Right? This is a signal.
You should think about the signal.
It may not be limited to three colors.
You can see it.
But there is the fourth color of the heart.
This is amazing.
What do you mean by the fourth color of the heart?
What?
I think that the gorilla came now.
I always think about the gorilla.
OK.
There is another reason for the possibility.
There is a jinx.
If you think that there may be something like this, it will not be so.
Do you understand?
For that reason, by thinking ahead,
It will be made to be nothing.
That's right.
Everyone, think about the possibility a little more.
Everyone who is riding a car is thinking and driving.
It's okay.
What's with that annoying feeling?
Everyone wants to go to Kyoshu.
I know that.
I don't know if you know, but if you do it like that,
Right?
There's still a chance.
Maybe.
Next week, next week.
Ah, that's right.
I'm just saying that I'll continue.
But, there is next week.
So, if you make me look so weak.
If this week I am so weak, what will happen next week?
A question for Mr. Matsumoto.
Please tell us the correct reaction when you received the Macadamia nuts as a souvenir from your friend in Hawaii.
This will be the situation where I will receive something from now on.
I'm angry!
Academia Nuts
But you are right.
I'm not good at it.
I have a problem.
I need a reaction to improve the relationship.
I need it.
I'm a comedian.
Who is a comedian?
I'm not alone.
When you get something, you feel nervous, right?
In the end, it's not just the laugh, but also the emotion.
It's the tension and the feeling.
When you tear the bag, you feel the tension.
Whatever you do here, it probably won't work.
I see.
The opponent thinks, let me cry here.
But when you open it up, it closes once.
Ehhhhhhhhh!
It's a mess.
But you can use this.
The longer this period is, the longer it is.
But if you don't know the story, there might be some people who just say it.
I'm totally fine with 5 minutes.
That mark.
After opening and closing, after opening and closing, 5 minutes.
It doesn't have to be longer.
After closing, Yu-san will get a gift from the previous owner.
I don't know.
That's right.
See, in the past, that kid was always saying something.
This is a question for Mr. Matsumoto, who has been through many rough times.
I heard that even if you meet a bear in the mountains and pretend to be dead, you will eventually be attacked.
Is that so?
Ah, yes. That's the wrong answer.
If you meet a bear in the mountains, what kind of acting will help you?
Ah, I think that you will meet bears 7 or 8 times in the future.
I don't know.
It's the easiest.
You can do it right away.
It's a lot of trouble.
What?
I'm saying it's a lot of trouble.
No, no.
People who are not good at it say,
Ah, that's the way.
It's easy.
Then, please play the bear.
What?
Please play the bear.
Ah, then I'll play the bear.
Where?
On the mountain road, right?
It's Hakkoda-san.
Yes, it's Hakkoda-san.
Yes, yes.
And then?
Ah, so it's Hakkoda-san.
No, there's a
There is, there is definitely a reason for that.
First, things that cannot be drawn.
Aaaaaaaaaaaah!
You're fast!
It's going to end soon!
You're really close!
You really scared me a little.
Please, give me a sign.
What?
Should I appear like this?
Yes, yes.
Yes, yes. When I do the four legs, I'm like a kotatsu.
Is that okay?
Ah, it's so bright here.
The air is so good.
Okay, let's have lunch.
Okay.
Oh, it's a sandwich.
I love sandwiches.
I have to watch it for a long time.
Well, then, can you say something like, wow?
OK.
I love sandwiches!
You know, your bear is weird.
It's a final blow.
It's definitely trying to kill me.
I can't run away even if I'm on a train.
Because it's aiming at me.
It's fine if you're just acting.
You're the one who did it!
It's a problem.
So, it's like a party.
That means, VS vs.
It means that it's no good if it's VS.
So, it's no good if it's like this.
See, it's VS.
You can see V and S like this.
See, it's ready go!
You can't win if it's like this.
That's why it's no good.
So when the bear goes,
BAM!
The bear becomes a pair.
But I don't know...
No one remembers.
BAM!
I'll go get some water.
This program was brought to you by the following sponsors.