Hey, look at this. It's Udon because it's cold.
Don't mess with me!
And where is this place? Look at this, everyone.
I'm alone in a place like this.
It's a temple. In a cemetery.
My staff was cold earlier.
When this is over, they say that something is reflected in the bag.
I thought, where did they all come from?
If my staff feels bad in a cold place, they all come in a T-shirt.
Next week, everyone will be in a T-shirt for the opening.
Otherwise, I can't go from next week.
This is JR's Higurezato Station.
Let's go!
This is Nippori Station.
Everyone, here we are.
Sunny Hall. It says, Nippori Sunny Hall.
This is a school building.
Oh, there's someone eating lunch over there.
Please stand by the camera.
This is strange.
Was there only one person in downtown?
Good evening.
What is it?
How is it?
It's ready.
Where did you come from?
This shitty staff.
How is it?
It's good.
It's good, isn't it?
Why are you eating lunch here?
What is it?
From now on, all the staff in the location will come in a T-shirt.
Even if it's a T-shirt, it's like a 24-hour TV show.
Everyone will be there.
That's it.
Nippori Sunny Hall will be opening tonight.
Nippori Sunny Hall
This program is brought to you by Sunlux,
Oyama International Products,
and the following sponsors.
My name is Jean-Paul Delmont.
I just arrived in Japan, but I'm a student from America.
But my curiosity is amazing.
I don't understand Japanese at all, but I came to Japan alone.
Papa, mama, this is my sister's extro-noodle.
This is Japan.
It's still me!
Why are you looking at me like that?
What are you looking at?
What is this Japanese doing?
If I don't apologize, if I don't do something,
I can't speak Japanese at all.
Sushi.
What?
Don't you say sorry when you bump into someone?
Mi-Mifune.
Say sorry!
What?
I'm sorry.
Say sorry!
I'm sorry!
Nissan.
What is that?
Toyota.
Toyota!
What are you talking about?
You only know Japanese words.
Say sorry.
Say sorry!
I'm sorry!
Say sorry when you bump into someone.
Don't you understand?
Did you see it?
Do you understand?
Yes.
Say sorry at the end.
No!
Then I was in a panic.
I studied Japanese with a sense of shame.
Wait a minute.
I like Kengo more than you do.
Say it.
Look up.
No!
What?
Say sorry at the end.
What is it today?
There were a lot of good things.
Yes.
It was a little bad.
Why are you dressed like this?
I won.
It's better to wear this.
You look like a bully.
I just had a haircut yesterday.
It doesn't matter.
I'm wearing this because it's short.
I lost.
I can't accept it.
It's been a long time since this program started.
It's a beautiful hall.
I've never seen it before.
I think it's the first time you've seen it.
I don't know.
I think it's always like this.
There was a place like that.
There was a place like a octopus room.
There was a baby crying.
What is this place?
I don't like children very much.
Why?
But if a small child comes here, I can't do it.
I like dogs.
You don't look good.
Really.
I'll do this if I'm in trouble today.
I can laugh for sure.
I shouldn't have shown it so early.
I'll show it again next time.
I really like dogs.
I don't like children.
Children are stupid.
That's why I hate children.
I think I was stupid when I was a child.
I know that I was stupid when I was a child.
Children really don't care about the distinction of things.
I can't help it.
I'm serious.
I don't know the difference between an old man and a young man.
How old are you?
I was born in the first year of elementary school.
I don't care.
It's normal that you don't know.
If you knew the difference between an old man and a young man in the first year of elementary school.
I didn't know the difference between an old man and a young man.
I was a child.
I thought that I would be punished.
I didn't know the difference between an old man and a young man.
I was a child.
I have a young aunt.
I didn't know the difference between an old man and a young man.
You've seen it from the old man's perspective.
Also, he thinks about what he is being seen as.
Ah, he's a coward.
He's a coward. That's true.
He's a coward.
He's being told that he's cute and he thinks he's cute.
Yes, yes, yes.
He thinks about it.
He's a sukebe.
That's why he says that children are really innocent.
All of it is a lie, right?
All of it is a lie.
When I was a child, I was single.
Even now, I'm like this.
Where is it?
I don't know.
Aren't you Kurikuri?
I'm not Kurikuri.
When I came in front of a beautiful lady, I was like this.
I wanted to be Kurikuri.
I thought so.
After all, there are two types of people, cute and ugly.
Men and children.
Ah, since you were a child?
Yes, if you're in front of a cute person, you're like this.
You're like this.
You're so sad.
After all, if you see an ugly person, you're like this.
I don't know.
Today, I asked for your autograph.
My mother said that too.
Did your mother give you an autograph?
Yes.
Right?
My daughter gave me a letter.
She gave you a letter?
She gave me a letter.
What?
I should have read it.
Oh my.
When I read it, your mother looked like an old man.
It's not like that.
Your mother is very fashionable.
There are old men, women and old men.
Today, I don't have an assistant.
You don't have one?
I only have an autograph.
Yes.
I'll take the address again.
A lot of people came today.
I'd like to introduce them.
A little while ago, I was talking about your fans.
People around me are like this.
They are just people around me.
The first fan is my fan.
He has big eyes.
He has long hair.
He is over 160 cm tall.
He has a good style.
He can wear a skirt or jeans.
He has thin legs.
He has good taste.
He is my fan.
The second fan is Hamada's fan.
He has thin eyes.
He has oily hair.
He is short.
He is fat.
He has a bad taste.
He has thick legs.
You are annoying.
This is true.
It's not true.
I'm a fan of Matsumoto.
You are a liar.
I'm from Yokohama.
My name is Ryoko Toda.
You are a fool.
Toda.
Next.
This is...
When did you two meet?
How did you know each other?
Please tell us a funny story of your childhood.
I don't know if it's a funny story.
I met you for the first time.
When I was in elementary school.
When I was in elementary school...
I knew your father better than you.
The green uncle.
Yes, the green uncle.
When I was in elementary school, I had a land sale.
Wait.
Right?
I was raised with that money.
Don't make fun of me.
But it was hard for your parents.
The most impressive thing was when I was in 4th or 5th grade.
Elementary school students usually have land sales for 6 years.
But they don't dress up like that.
This guy is really over the top.
He is a skip school kid.
He was a skip school kid.
He was wearing a perm when he was in elementary school.
He was wearing a perm.
He was wearing a blazer.
He was wearing a white jacket.
He was wearing a long jacket.
He had no choice but to have a land sale.
He was wearing a bag that looked like a bag from the movie.
When I was doing a land sale, I had a bag like this.
He was wearing a baggy.
It was called a pantalon.
I was shocked when I saw it for the first time.
It was called a culture shock.
I was shocked.
Who is this guy?
We became friends in 12th grade.
12th grade?
Yes, we did a lot of things at other people's houses.
We did a lot of bad things.
When I was in 12th grade,
I don't know if there are people who know this,
but it was a foreign underwear incident.
It was amazing.
There was a friend's apartment.
A foreign woman lived next to it.
She put a washing machine at the entrance.
I don't know why,
but she wanted to go to take off her underwear.
She didn't want to imitate a child watching TV.
The two of us were in the washing machine.
When I opened the washing machine and grabbed it,
she said,
Don't take off your underwear.
The foreign woman said,
Don't open the washing machine.
I was scared.
When I opened the washing machine,
she said,
Don't open the washing machine.
It was scary.
There are many foreigners in Tokyo now.
There weren't many foreigners in Japan at that time.
It was a suburb town like us.
I thought it was an international problem.
I was excited to go home.
We did a lot of bad things.
Today is the last day.
Osaka dialect?
Yes.
My head is a jingle.
I don't know what a jingle is.
Konbaba.
You know this, don't you?
Answer me.
Don't you know what a konbaba is?
Just as it is.
Konbaba.
Konjoubaba.
You don't know what a konjoubaba is, do you?
There is no konjou.
That's a baba.
Konjou is bad or dirty.
Baba means poop in Osaka dialect.
Konjou is like poop.
Dirty.
Baba means dirty.
Konjoubaba.
Sarapin.
Do you know this?
What?
For example, there is shampoo in the bathroom.
This is sarapin.
Freshly washed?
Yes, yes, yes.
You don't say it's freshly washed.
Yes, it's fresh.
You don't have to wear it.
What is it?
I don't know.
Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah.
Ah, dog.
Do you say dog today?
Yes.
In Osaka dialect, we say kairu.
If you say kairu, you say dog.
What's wrong with that?
It's true.
What about Ichiogami?
Ah, now.
I'm doing it on TV.
It's a voice that makes you cry.
I'm hungry.
It's hard.
You can go home.
I'm the type of person who falls down while looking at the castle.
I'm scared.
I'm dying.
I can't do anything.
I want you to get out of here.
I don't want to.
I'm the type who gets in the bus on my way to school.
I don't sit on the window sill.
There are women I love.
Who does that?
I can't.
I'm thinking about sleeping.
I can't sleep.
I can't think about twisted things.
Don't think about that.
I thought about it and thought about it and thought it.
Tempura or something?
Croquette or something?
It's the worst.
I thought, it's not oily.
I thought about it and thought about it, but I couldn't.
I couldn't stand it anymore.
I opened the window and said, I don't know if it's like this.
I opened the window and said,
Boo!
You're in that world.
I want to spit out.
That's how it goes.
Boo!
But
You know, there's a saying,
Even if you're seen by a real woman, you can't spit it out with one shot.
But I'm a Full Moon.
It's the power与r love.
Boo!
What do you think of this?
Sensei, something is sleeping in my moistment.
It smells like water!
Masumoto-kun!
Yes, I'm coming!
The teacher is sitting in the auxiliary chair.
Wait a minute!
Masumoto-kun, are you okay?
Yes, yes.
That's right.
When I thought about it, everyone was like,
No, no, no!
That's right.
I don't like it.
That's the type, right?
That's the type.
This guy used to be a bad guy.
There was a time when the two of us worked part-time at Snack.
In this world?
In this world.
It was a full-time job.
We worked part-time at Snack.
I was a night watchman.
I worked part-time at Snack.
There were a lot of night watches.
There was no train going home.
My mother would tell me to go home in a taxi.
I took a taxi and went.
I still have the feeling.
I'm on the bus, so I can't do it anymore.
I can't do it anymore.
I opened the window and went straight.
I was about to start talking, but I was like this.
I was like this.
I couldn't stand it, so I got on the bus.
I opened the door.
At that time, I couldn't do it anymore.
I got off the bus.
The driver came out.
Are you all right?
I opened the door.
It's funny.
I had to step on his back.
I was scared while doing the lots of things.
I was scared.
I was laughing at him from the side.
I'll have to do my best as a partner.
I have to do my best as a partner.
In the meantime, I was doing the lots of things.
I laughed.
I laughed because he was so funny.
I was laughing because I was laughing.
Because he was laughing.
I was like this.
Ha ha ha ha!
Well, well, well, well
I won't imitate the kid on TV
No, no!
Well, so what is today?
Bebe!
Maybe not bebe
Let's go with dog
So, say, I say!
What do you call it?
Well, let me do one like this.
Here you go.
If you say, grenades go-ahead.
Let's practice this one.
Now, goods go-ahead!
What is this?
This girl is probably called Patrick.
But at least don't go in yourert.
That's all for tonight. Thank you very much.
See you next week!
I thought a lot about what to do next week.
I don't really like it.
I don't really like this kind of stuff.
But I want to do something special.
You speak so clearly.
Something special?
I want to see this.
What do you want to see?
I have to do this.
I have to talk about this.
What is it?
Rolling Thunder Man.
I'm really looking forward to the opening.
The camera, lighting, everything.
In a yellow T-shirts.
Love is to save the world.
I'll do this cover.
What do I do?
I told Nirvana.
It's cool.
Have Unchained come.
Do it!
And, the last one, will come to L.A.
And L.A. will be our home.
The location is also important.
Do it like this.
Like this.
Turn it around.
That's how you do it.
Thank you.