You've been wearing a suit for a long time, haven't you?
Yes, I've been wearing a suit for a long time.
You were like that last week, too.
Really?
Yes.
Why?
Because I'm a talent.
If I don't wear a suit, I can't do it.
Should I talk?
Yes.
Let's talk more and more.
Excuse me, I've got some information.
I've found a place where I can get a lot of information.
Let's go.
How can you find it?
I've got some information.
Tell me.
Who told you?
I can't tell you, but I've got some information.
You can't tell me.
I can't tell you.
That's it.
You don't want to play, do you?
Tell me who it is.
Who is it?
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
This is the worst location.
Excuse me.
Where should we go?
Let's go.
This way.
Where is this?
You're not reacting.
This way.
That's why I can't do it.
Is it here?
Yes.
This is something.
What is it?
I don't know.
Let's do it.
Let's look for it.
There must be something on the floor.
Let's go.
What is it?
It's a secret.
It's a golden half.
Wait a minute.
I know this.
Who is this?
What is a golden half?
I don't know what a golden half is.
Is this a foreigner?
Everyone has a half.
A half?
A golden half.
It's Eva.
Eva?
No.
Agnes Lambda?
It depends on the person.
Wait a minute.
That's right.
It's not nostalgic, is it?
I only remember this part.
It's funny.
I only know this part.
Wait a minute.
I think it will be in the show.
Something came out.
What is it?
What is this?
It's a book.
It's Yoshimi Iwasaki.
The cover.
It's you.
This is nostalgic.
This is Aki Mizusawa's book.
I know this.
This is nostalgic.
This is Yoshiko Iwasaki.
This is you.
I remember this picture.
Really?
Look at this.
This is amazing.
Yoshiko Iwasaki.
This is cute.
This is it.
What is this?
Lineback.
Not here.
It's nostalgic.
This is the only baseball player that I know.
Linebackers of Linebacker.
Linebackers.
You remember.
Specone.
Home run.
March.
His name is Ma.
Tom.
Your name is Ma.
That's right.
That's why he won the championship.
Let's dig this up.
It's nostalgic.
It came out right away.
What is this?
This is still a record.
Romantam?
I know it.
I don't even know Romantam.
I think only I know it.
It's Romantam.
Did you put your heart into it?
It's not broken at all.
Why did you throw it away?
I'm not Japanese.
I don't know if it was written.
I don't know what kind of voice it was.
Romantam.
There was a program called the Japan Championship.
You can become a professional if you practice it.
I think that's where Yashiro Aki comes out.
It's really hard to practice.
Yashiro Aki is amazing.
Romantam.
I don't know the song at all.
I don't know a Thai singer yet.
It's Indonesian style.
It's amazing.
I know Romantam.
I don't know Romantam.
I don't know a Thai singer yet.
Where are you?
What...
Video.
I want to see it.
We take it here, so it's quite nostalgic.
It's been a long time since I've seen it.
It's been a long time.
There it is.
Let's get bigger.
Is it Marudai?
It's Marudai.
There it is.
It's been a long time.
I know it's a commercial, but it's Marudai Hamburg.
I forgot that.
What's coming out?
It's a good one.
What's that?
What's this?
It's a thing.
There it is.
There's something inside.
It's a pencil case.
It's from the Rokumen Pocket.
It's been a long time.
I know what this is.
It's a key.
There it is.
This is probably from my generation.
This is from my generation.
There's a separate place to put the eraser.
Put the eraser separately.
What's this?
This is...
You can use the back as well.
It's double.
You can put a ruler here.
What's this?
You can put the eraser again.
You can put a lot of them.
You can put the eraser inside.
There it is.
It's a calendar.
There's a calendar.
You don't know what this is?
It's from my generation.
This is a key.
You can't open it without this.
You can't open it.
You don't know what this is?
It's such a big key.
I can't help it.
I forgot about it when I was young.
It's been a long time.
What's this?
There it is.
It's from Ichi-ni.
I don't know.
There it is.
It's from Ichi-ni.
It's from Kontarou.
Who is it?
The author?
Kontarou.
There it is.
It's from Ichi-ni.
You really don't know?
You don't know?
You've already read third volume.
It's still manga.
There it is!
Toilet paper.
It's from Toilet.
This is a dream.
You don't know?
I don't know.
What's your dream?
It's from Torii Kazuyoshi.
Torii Kazuyoshi.
You don't know?
Not at all.
I don't know.
What is Matanki?
Do you know Mr. Tsunami?
Who is Mr. Tsunami?
Ichiro Otomo?
I don't know.
What is this?
Toilet paper.
I'll play a video.
Please.
Let's go.
Here it comes.
It's a video.
It's fun.
This is very old.
We are old.
What is this?
I don't know.
This is a video.
I don't like this commercial.
I didn't know this.
This is more than me.
Right?
This is about 50 years old.
This is a nostalgic video.
Here it comes.
This is big.
Wow.
This is very old.
A mustard bean.
This is a belt.
That is a car horn.
It was so simple.
Oh, I got it.
This is nostalgic.
Let's open it.
It's a little blurry, but it's very nostalgic.
Look.
I don't know.
It's a fishing line game.
Why don't you know the fishing line game?
This is nostalgic.
You can play with this.
You can put your own ship on it.
Please try it.
I'll set the ball here.
This is the other ship.
Look.
It's completely off.
It's a big explosion in each process.
It's funny.
It's impossible.
There's only one left.
What is this?
This is a video game.
I got it.
I got a video.
This is the last video.
I got it.
This is a nostalgic video.
I want to cry.
That's right.
This is nostalgic.
Is this all over the country?
Is this only in Kansai?
This is not only in Kansai.
People in Tokyo don't know this.
This is the most exciting video.
When I close my eyes, I remember.
Everything I saw was fresh.
It was the youth of Haruka Sepiairo.
And I did my best to do everything.
I did everything I could to do something stupid.
It was a youthful time that was blue and powerful.
Time is slow.
But we have grown up.
The nostalgic people who bring back the sweet and sour memories of that time.
Thank you.
I will never forget it.
Until the day we meet again.
It's very exciting.
There is a fool.
I went to Tsutaya.
Did you go to Tsutaya?
I was choosing what to borrow.
There were two men.
Look at this.
I will definitely cry.
I won't cry.
Idiot.
I will definitely cry.
I won't cry.
You will definitely cry.
Shut up.
Even if you say something different.
You will definitely cry.
I won't cry.
Idiot.
Shut up.
You were crying because you were tired.
You're such an idiot.
Really.
I went to the hot spring with my juniors.
I'm such an idiot.
It was a hot spring.
Everyone was in a yukata.
Of course.
We had dinner in a yukata.
There was a hot spring bath.
The next day, we had breakfast.
We went to the hot spring.
We had breakfast in a yukata.
What?
I don't understand.
I'm sorry.
Everyone was having fun in a yukata.
It was in the morning.
It was reset in the morning.
In the morning?
Wait a minute.
You went to the hot spring bath.
You changed into your uniform.
You said,
I'm sorry.
I don't understand.
Why did you go to the yukata?
I couldn't go to the yukata.
I couldn't help it.
The food was so good.
I'm getting old.
You should go there.
I didn't say anything.
What did you say?
Your juniors...
You didn't say anything.
I didn't say anything.
That's strange.
I don't know if it's strange.
What are you doing?
When your juniors say something,
what are you doing?
What are you doing?
This is Ebisu's face.
That's strange.
What are you doing?
Do you know that?
It's a high-speed train.
It's a central high-speed train.
You're driving a car, aren't you?
It's in front of the curve.
It's going fast.
It's not going too fast.
It's a central high-speed tunnel.
That's strange.
What are you doing?
Do you know that?
You're driving a car.
It's going fast.
Do you know that?
That's amazing.
Why didn't you say that?
That's probably because you're wearing a sleeping cap.
Is that so?
Yes.
I think that's amazing.
You're a genius.
Are you ready?
Yes.
Why did you say that?
That's amazing.
It's amazing.
Why can't you be more impressed?
Why?
You shouldn't let it go.
What are you talking about?
If we're driving a car, we'll know.
It's four wheels.
What's going on?
Can I say that?
It's like Hayashiya's Sanpei.
Why did you say that?
It's the same thing.
That's amazing.
I get it.
This is a question for Matsumoto-san, an astronaut.
Matsumoto-san has had sex with an astronaut.
How did you feel when you had sex with him?
Did you feel good?
Where did you meet him?
An astronaut?
Yes.
Harappa.
Harappa?
A nameless Harappa.
He was in Harappa?
He was in Harappa.
He was taking a walk.
He was wearing a belt.
A dirty belt.
Who's dirty?
He was a student.
That's a lie.
He was a university student.
That's enough.
He was wearing a belt.
He was wearing a belt?
And?
And then?
He was sticking out his tongue.
Up a bit to the left.
All the way.
It would be nice if he walk
in front of me like he's telling me to show him to a friend.
How did you do it?
That's strange, too.
There are times when a flower blooms out of love.
So the other person is like...
And I'm like...
And Perumon is like...
I didn't need that.
In short, it's sex in the head.
Like, oh, so that's how it came to be.
How does it come to be?
If you look at it from the skin, it's just floating in the air.
What's going on in your head?
In my head, I'm like...
I took off my bra.
I'm like, oh, so you came to take off your bra.
I'm like, oh, you're rubbing it hard.
I'm like, oh, don't touch the left side.
I'm like, oh, I touched the right side too.
I'm sweating all over.
Oh, you're so nice.
You too.
Do it more.
Do it.
I don't hate it.
He's a middle schooler.
When JR was still called the National Railway,
there was a question for Mr. Matsumoto, who was called the leader of the shadows.
Yes, I was called that.
There is a rumor that the linear motor car,
which has been experimented with in Yamanashi for many years,
has not yet been practicalized.
There is a reason why people can't say.
Do you know, Mr. Matsumoto?
Why hasn't it been practicalized yet?
I've been doing it for decades.
That's what it is.
In short,
it's too fast.
It's possible to go fast.
I see.
It's going to be fast,
but I can't stand that speed.
You've come to understand that you can't stand it.
I can't stand it.
What can't I stand?
The window.
I'm going to ride it.
Do it quickly.
This will come off immediately.
What is that?
Why is it so dirty?
Is that a window?
I'm trying to get caught.
This is like this.
So,
do it quickly.
Don't do it with your fingers.
Do it quickly.
Then you can't talk.
I can't do that.
It's like this next to me.
But the president is like this again.
Why is it like this?
The window of the Imiyama Otaku
opens like this.
That's right.
That's amazing.
You have to think about it from there.
You can't open a window like this.
You can't open a window with a hook like this.
Then how do you change it?
You can change the window to a normal Shinkansen.
You don't have to open the window.
You've done that before.
You have to open it.
That's strange.
You can do it like this.
What I said is...
Coffee, tea,
and the Udon.
You don't know what it is.
You can't open the window?
The linear motor car.
You can't open the window.
That's strange.
Why?
How do you drive if you can't see anything?
Where do you go?
You don't have a window.
Which window can you break?
You can't break it.
The driver's seat.
What?
It's not what everyone thought.
Really?
You thought it was horizontal?
It's horizontal.
The front is like this.
The driver's seat is in the back.
You have to open it.
Can I have it in the back?
I put two in.
I don't have to open it.
It's amazing.
The curtain is like this.
The race is like this.
It's amazing.
This program was brought to you by five sponsors.