Fight! Fight!
Give up! Give up!
No! No! No!
No! No!
Never give up!
Fight! Fight!
No!
Give up!
Fight! Fight!
Give up! Give up!
No! Answer!
Stop!
Yes.
There are 5 people.
What?
1,2,3,4,5. There are 5 people.
What? Why?
Why?
What do you mean?
There are 5 people.
No, I'm the judge.
There are 4 people.
There are 6 people.
Is that so?
What are you doing?
This is strange.
What do you mean?
Why?
Why are there 5 people?
Let's do it properly.
It's strange that there are no 4 people.
It's strange.
Let's check.
Let's take a picture.
Who are you?
What?
Tanaka.
Hey, hey.
Who are you?
Hey, Enno.
This is strange.
Come here.
Who are you?
This is me.
Look.
Yama.
Hey, Enno.
Good morning.
Enno.
This is strange.
Who are you?
Hey, Enno.
Good morning.
You are so slow.
I can't understand why you are so slow.
Hey, Enno.
Good morning, Enno.
Good morning.
What's wrong?
Eh? The wind is coming!
Wait, wait!
What are you doing?
Good morning!
Who is it?
Shoei?
You called me!
Shoei, what's wrong?
What's wrong?
Well, you see
It's painful.
Lend me your glasses.
Hey, if you pass by...
It's Shohei-san.
Oh, Shohei-san. Good morning.
Good morning.
What's the matter?
What are you doing?
What am I doing? You're a pro-wrestler.
I'm not a pro-wrestler.
This is a 100,000 yen deal.
I'm doing it on a regular basis.
What are you doing?
I'm just passing by.
I'm having fun.
You're in.
I'm not a pro-wrestler.
What?
That's not what a pro-wrestler is.
You're not a regular, are you?
I'm doing it on a regular basis.
I don't know how to use it.
I'm doing it for 100,000 yen.
100,000 yen and prize money are fine.
I'm not doing it for the prize money.
Why are you doing it?
I'm doing it on a regular basis.
But that's a bit of a problem.
Please go home.
Why?
You're in the way.
I'm not doing it this far.
You're the one who bought it.
I'm not a pro-wrestler.
I'm a senior.
I'm not a senior.
I have something to do after this.
I don't think you have anything to do after this.
I have something to do.
I'm doing it on a regular basis.
You're not doing it on a regular basis.
I'm doing it because it looks fun.
You're a baby bird.
I don't know what you mean.
Please explain.
You don't read the atmosphere.
I'm not doing it for you.
I'm a senior.
I'm not a senior.
I'm not doing it on a regular basis.
Please go home.
I'm sorry.
I'm not doing it because I'm a senior.
I don't know.
What are you talking about?
I don't agree what you're saying.
I'm not doing it because I'm a senior.
That's right.
I don't have any seniors.
It's strange, isn't it?
If you look into it, you're only half a year older than us.
That's normal.
You know that I don't have any eyes on DORORESU, right?
You knew that, right?
I'm famous in the industry.
I'm in it every now and then.
I don't have any eyes on DORORESU.
You know that, right?
I'll try not to do it next time.
Really?
You're my senior.
You're a scumbag.
I'll tell you later.
I'm counting on you.
I'll go to the next job.
Excuse me.
I've never seen a man with such a sharp nose.
You have a kind image.
Thank you for your hard work.
I'm sorry, but let's do it again.
Let's do it until someone gets 100,000 yen.
I'll do my best.
Let's do it again.
This program is provided by the following sponsors.
Oh, my God.
Stop, stop, stop.
There's another one.
One, two, three, four, five.
There are five people.
Four people started earlier.
Two people are back.
Yes, yes, yes.
Stop.
There are five people.
Let's do it.
It's funny because there are five people.
Who is this?
Come on.
What are you doing?
Thank you for your hard work.
Let's do it again.
Mr. Suga.
Stop that old man.
What's wrong?
Let's do it.
What is Mr. Ise?
What?
I'm on the show right now.
I'm playing Doro.
This is a TV show.
That's right.
I was doing it when I passed by.
I love Doro.
It's a problem if you don't come in.
Four people are doing it.
It looks fun.
This isn't a TV show, is it?
It's not a TV show.
There are a lot of cameras.
Aren't you playing?
No.
You're not friends, are you?
What?
Mr. Doro.
You're lying.
I saw it in 30 seconds in Shinjuku.
I don't know the skinship of soccer.
Let's do it.
Who's the one who's going to do it?
I'm sorry.
There's something I want to talk to you about.
What is it?
I'm going to do it.
I'm sorry.
Let's talk.
I'm getting a call.
Let's do it.
It's a recording, so I'm sorry.
It's better than our seniors.
Take him.
I'll introduce you to a good camera.
It's a shame.
It's our first time.
I don't know who it is.
You're good at it.
I'm back.
What is it?
What's up with the entertainment world these days?
It's like this.
Everyone is here.
It's impossible for me to have a meal.
You have to find an opportunity.
And one more thing.
Take a look at the Hamada.
What is this!
What!
Hey!
What is this!
azione
Hey!
Ohhhh!
I can see your eyes
Oh sensei, it's cold.
There's mud in my eyes.
It was good.
It's got out!!
Chrysanthemum mud.
ify checking
My eyes are already dry.
Please take off your mask.
1,2,3,4
There are 5 of them.
Look.
Who are you?
Come here.
You are so energetic.
Who are you?
What?
Take off your goggles.
Who are you?
Dave.
Dave Spector.
What are you doing?
Look at his face.
There is a patting center near here.
Yes.
I was doing it.
I saw it.
No, no, no.
It says 100,000 yen.
I want to give you 100,000 yen.
No, no, no.
What?
I'll be in trouble if you come in.
Why?
This is the last one.
I wanted to give you the last one.
That's right.
If you get in the way, you'll be in trouble.
Why are you making a fuss?
If you're a foreigner, you'll be colorful.
I don't think so.
I don't think I'll be colorful.
It's cheap, so it's okay.
I'm enjoying it on a regular basis.
That's right.
I want to participate.
It's not that easy.
It's okay to do it on a regular basis, but you need to change the picture on TV.
That's right.
Then let's do it.
No, no, no.
What?
Referee.
There's a picture, so I'll accept it.
Mr. Suga.
Why can't you do it?
I'm doing it on a regular basis.
It's an opportunity.
Yes.
I'm doing it on a regular basis.
What?
Regular people don't enjoy it that much.
I'll do it as soon as I can.
Do you want to be forced to do it or do you want to go home?
I don't want to be forced to do it, but I want to do it on my own.
That's right.
You don't like it, do you?
Go home.
Please don't come for five or six years.
It's been a while.
It's been a while, five or six years.
What's that feeling?
Hey, hey, hey.
I've been doing it for a long time.
Yes.
I can't help it if I do more than this.
Do you give up?
Do you want to do it again?
I give up.
Do you give up?
Yes.
I give up.
Do you give up 100,000 yen?
Mr. Matsumoto.
I give up.
Do you give up?
Of course.
I give up.
Well, we've prepared the prize money.
Yes.
This time, everyone will draw.
I'll never do this again.
Thank you very much.
Thank you for your hard work.
Ladies and gentlemen.
How does a sandbag get sand?
Well, the sandbag in the old days.
The sandbag in the old days.
I don't know if I can say this.
It's the same with everything.
There's a saying that it used to be good.
Oh, well, there is.
That's right.
For example, in the old days.
I really only ate natural things.
Well, even if it's fish.
Now it's time for Western food.
But that's normal now.
Tatami is a good song.
It's just like tatami.
There's no real tatami.
I see.
It's like a tatami carpet.
Good things are disappearing.
The sandbag is the same.
The sandbag now is not serious.
What?
It used to be serious.
What do you mean?
It used to be sandbag.
I see.
The sandbag now is pro-wrestling.
It's decided.
What?
It's noisy now, isn't it?
It used to be noisy for children.
But now it's noisy.
What are you doing?
Why are you putting sand on the sandbag?
The PTA is noisy.
If you complain, the old lady has no money.
What are you doing now?
The old lady...
It's a lie.
What's a lie?
I didn't put sand on the sandbag.
You didn't?
I didn't.
Why did you put sand on the sandbag?
I pretended to put sand on the sandbag.
I put on a kimono.
It's OK to wear a kimono.
Really?
That's OK?
That's OK.
So you didn't get the sandbag.
Now all the monsters are lies.
Really?
Yes.
How did the old lady put sand on the sandbag?
She really put sand on the sandbag.
Did she put sand on the sandbag?
No.
She put sand on the sandbag.
If I say this much, the old lady will get angry.
Can you hear me clearly?
Don't get angry.
There was sand on the sandbag and sand on the sandbag.
I see.
Did you use the sandbag separately?
Yes.
In the past?
I see.
Now I only use sandbag samples.
If I put sand on the sandbag, the old lady will get angry.
I see.
Now I only use sandbag samples.
The old lady is not as small as she used to be.
Is that so?
Compared to her age, she looks bigger than a monkey.
I think so.
I don't think so.
Yu-gi is the same.
What do you think?
I think Yu-gi is the same.
Don't say that!
I have a question for you, Matsumoto-san.
How humble should you behave in front of a great person?
And if you're rude, how should you react?
The greatest person in the world?
He's amazing.
Who is he?
He's in the Soviet Union.
In the Soviet Union?
Pescatora.
La Pescatora.
Which one?
Don't lie to me.
You can't say La.
I can't say La.
What does he do?
He's a student.
What?
What do you mean a student?
If you're a great person, it's your prejudice that you're older.
I see.
Even high school students are great people.
This is the greatest person in the world.
So what makes you think you're great?
That's the question.
It's a philosophical question.
What makes you think you're great?
But what's written here is a little strange.
This isn't it.
I thought it was a little strange.
Why?
What happens when you're rude?
I see.
You don't get angry.
Really?
Because you're a great person.
No matter what you do?
Yes.
No matter what you say?
You laugh.
Humans are big.
But the louder you laugh, the more angry you are.
Then you're angry.
Right?
I'm starting to understand that.
For example, you spill water.
You think you're a great person.
At that time, you start to get close to each other.
You smoke.
I don't smoke!
Why don't you smoke?
This is the most angry person in the world.
But you don't do anything?
I don't smoke.
You tell me to stay at home.
Right?
If you stay at home, you'll get a cramp in your shoe.
You're really a student.
I knew you were angry.
Mr. Matsumoto was elected the other day.
Yes.
It seems that he lost the election because he couldn't be on TV.
What is the cause of the defeat?
First of all, the biggest reason is that I didn't run for office.
This is the only reason.
I didn't put up the election posters.
But I was running for office.
What?
I had a huge burden.
But I don't understand that.
But I had the feeling that I was running for office somewhere.
On Sunday, when the election was open.
I was looking around.
It doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter, so I didn't look around.
I didn't look around.
But I was looking around while doing the dishes.
You're the only one who's looking around.
But I didn't run for office.
I said it by accident.
I thought the Japanese people didn't understand.
No, I don't understand.
I didn't run for office.
But I don't understand why people don't run for office.
I don't understand that.
I thought so.
I can change.