Happy birthday to you, happy birthday to you, happy birthday dear Hama-chan!
The first episode of Gagi no Kikai Arahen! Gekidasu Chikichiki Star Bowling!
Hey, hey, hey!
You know, we haven't really done anything that's really, you know, sports-like.
Yes, yes, yes.
So today, we have a pair.
What? What's good about that?
You can throw first, so...
I have nothing to do with that pair of yours.
Idiot.
You throw first, right?
Yes.
Well, I'll throw first, so it doesn't really matter which one you throw first, whatever you throw first, and then, you do the processing.
Oh, I see.
And then, we have the players who will go against us.
Yes.
The pros.
First of all, we have Namiki Pro.
Hello.
He's right in the middle.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
Today, we're going to have a Star Bowling match.
Is that so?
Yes.
Namiki Pro is wearing a lot of foundation.
We're two people, so Namiki Pro needs a partner.
He's good.
You have one, right?
Yes, I do.
This is Nitta Pro.
Nitta and I are a pair.
This is a foundation.
I can't sleep.
And...
Yes.
He's going to explain.
I'm calling him again.
Yes.
He's going to explain.
This is Sakariko Pro.
Today, he's going to explain.
He's telling me to be strict, but...
I'm worried about how to be strict because everyone is so good.
Do you know how to do it?
Yes, I do.
How is it?
This pair and this pair.
It's a beauty pair.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
Now, let's start the Star Bowling match.
Here we go.
Nitta, please look at the form.
It's amazing.
It's pretty good, isn't it?
Yes.
Are you going to throw it to the manager now?
It went to a good place.
Yes.
Amazing.
I'm better than him, aren't I?
Yes, you are.
You're looking at it the wrong way.
It's a mistake.
This program is brought to you by Sunlux.
Don't look at the camera.
But you're looking at it the right way, aren't you?
Yes, I am.
Now, let's see what Hama-chan is going to do.
I've been listening to it for a long time.
The score is 71 to 57.
I'm counting on you.
I'll catch up with you.
Hey!
Oh, no.
What's wrong with you?
Is that a real ball?
Oh, no.
I'm sorry.
It's a real ball.
You can't do that.
I don't know.
It went to the middle again.
Nice ball.
Amazing.
If you're a man, throw it stronger.
What is this?
How is it?
Oh, no.
There's a difficult one left.
Let's get a strike quickly.
Why?
It's a good target.
Nice cover.
Oh, no.
Please give him some advice.
No, I don't need it.
It's already broken.
Don't leave it.
Oh, no.
Dutty was very good.
That's how much it's different.
The last one was a great strike.
That's all for today.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
I don't think it's very interesting as a viewer.
But Mr. Mitsuta did a great job today.
That's right.
The two of you were very cool.
Mr. Mitsuta's design was very impressive.
We won the championship.
Mr. Mitsuta and professional Nitta.
Congratulations.
Girls shouldn't leave anything behind.
It doesn't mean that the line here is twisted.
Mr. Mitsuta is here again today.
Hello.
You're on a TV show.
Be quiet.
Are you all local candidates?
I'm sorry.
It doesn't matter.
Why?
You have a lot of sauce on your lunch box.
Of course.
Why?
Bring it to me.
What are you talking about?
I don't know.
Recently, when you take the Shinkansen, you read the newspaper, right?
But when I read the sports newspaper, I don't know what to say.
Why do you play baseball so much now?
Yes.
Professional baseball.
Is baseball getting more popular these days?
Yes, it is.
Why is that?
Because the sun is strong now.
I wonder why comedians don't treat baseball players like that.
What do you mean?
If there is a funny joke, I'll drink it the next day.
It's a great joke.
It's as great as Matsumoto's joke.
Matsumoto's joke is great.
I think it's as great as the home run and the audience cheering.
I think they use their brains.
They have a lot of skills.
That's right.
Why do they treat baseball players and comedians differently?
I get annoyed every day.
Every morning, when I read the sports newspaper, I get annoyed.
I get annoyed.
I get annoyed every day.
I don't want you to get annoyed the day before.
I get annoyed when I'm not in the mood.
I don't think that's true.
Do you write the content?
Yes.
In the conversation?
What do you say?
Matsumoto is going to regret it.
I think it's okay.
Why are comedians so low?
That's how it is in the entertainment world.
I've been working hard.
A cute girl with a face like an idol.
I just came out and got angry.
That's right.
I think it's sad.
She became a big star.
She doesn't have any skills.
She's just cute.
If she becomes a big star and appears in front of me, I'll get angry.
That's sad.
She's saying hello to the audience.
I'm going to be angry with the audience.
That's sad.
Comedians are not good.
Even baseball players say good things when they hit the home run.
When I come home from the home run, I'm angry.
That's why comedians are not good.
I'm angry because you're not funny.
You don't have to be angry.
I'm not funny when I'm sad.
If I get angry, you'll be angry.
It's not good when you laugh at me.
But when I say something, it's a big laugh.
That's right.
I'm helping you.
But if the audience sees it, I'll get angry.
Why?
I'm sorry.
That's not true.
You're a fool.
I'm not a fool.
That's not true.
If I'm reborn, I don't want to be a comedian.
I don't like baseball.
I don't like baseball because of the rules.
You're trying to change the subject.
Someone decided to hit the home run three times.
I can't accept that.
I don't know if there's anyone who hits the home run four times.
Hit the home run three times.
I don't know if there's anyone who hits the home run three times.
Why do you accept it?
I can't accept what people think.
You can't do anything.
You were doing a bowling experience.
I don't like that.
You don't like it.
I don't like it.
Why are you smiling?
I was saying that.
It doesn't mean anything.
I said it because I was fast.
I can't do anything because I said it.
It's a training for people who need it.
It's useless in real life.
Have you ever been a guest next door?
I don't have it, and I don't have to tell you that.
I don't need it.
I don't have to tell you that.
I don't have it.
It's a training for people who need it.
Excuse me.
Is there anyone who eats oysters?
I'll ask the person next door.
You talk for a long time.
Please wait here.
I'll ask the person next door.
I'm hungry.
Mr. Matsubara came out.
What kind of person is he?
He's a fat person.
I have a guest.
What is it?
I'm eating oysters.
That's good.
Would you like to eat with the guest?
I'll be told.
I'll be called.
Then the guest who came first will be excited.
Hey, Akagi.
Please come out.
What is it?
What's your name?
My name is Kobayashi.
How old are you?
I'm 21 years old.
Do you have a boyfriend?
I have a boyfriend.
I just heard it.
That's right.
I'm sorry to hear that.
I've been showing off the most until now.
I usually hide it.
I have a lot of friends.
Is that so?
Please cherish your love.
Thank you very much for today.
It's rare to be so clear.
Let's go to the postcard.
I really like down-down.
Especially Hama-chan.
He's cool.
Is that so?
Please listen to the story below.
The program is wrong, but you can laugh.
I'm on a regular Monday.
I'm sure I'll meet you and take a picture.
I pretended to go to school on Monday.
I left the house and took the train.
I should have taken the Shinkansen.
I live in the countryside.
I didn't know where Alta was.
I couldn't find Alta.
That's why I don't give up.
I took out my savings.
I couldn't meet Hama-chan.
I didn't know where Alta was.
Please read it normally.
When I came home, the teacher came.
I found out that I was absent from school.
I had a fight with my parents.
It was terrible.
When I went to school the next day, the teacher called me.
He asked me which was more important, school or downtown.
When I said downtown, he asked me if I looked down on me.
He told me to stop going to school.
I just told him the truth.
I'm living a dark life now.
Please give me an old man.
He told you to stop.
I don't know.
Please give me an old man.
You're homeless, aren't you?
You're happy, aren't you?
You've come this far.
Should I send you to him?
I thought about it.
But there's something like this.
Kuniko Nakai from Yokosuka.
She's 22 years old.
She wanted an old man.
She said she was cold.
She's so pitiful.
She's cold.
If she does that, I can't help but get angry.
I heard that the TV show talent wants an old man, too.
They say that.
They say that Yukari Morikawa is coming.
That, too.
That's why I'm going to do it after I see him.
I see.
The talent is going to book a seat.
Come and see.
Sit in the audience seat and give it to her after the recording.
If she wants it, come to the venue.
Don't you want to see it together?
I don't.
If I see it, I'll give it to her.
I'll give it to you.
You are making sacrifices in various ways.
It's normal, but it's cold.
It's difficult.
I don't know which one to choose.
I don't have it.
I don't have two.
You guys are laughing too much.
You guys are going too far.
I don't have two.
I choose this one.
It looks good on you.
You are from Niigata.
You don't even go to school.
I'll give it to Minoru.
I choose this one.
Ichikawa Reiko.
The ultimate choice.
Is it written here?
Please put it here.
The ultimate choice.
Which one do you choose to quit?
You can laugh.
You are a child.
This is the ultimate choice.
Which one do you choose to quit?
You are a child.
Let me tell you.
Which one do you choose to quit?
I choose this one.
Children.
If you are a child, you can do what you want.
Tell me if it's good.
It's half past ten.
It's early.
Jamon is next to the big star Junichiro.
I'm watching the newspaper. There's a group of teenagers behind me.
Oh, really?
Yeah.
I'm going in there.
Excuse me.
I can't talk at all.
You're late.
That's not true.
What are you looking at?
You're laughing so hard before the show.
Look at the audience here.
Hey!
Excuse me!
You're not going to say anything.
This is...
This is not something we decide.
Oh, my.
It's that.
The show is the most important thing.
We both want to continue.
But this is...
This is...
Wait a minute.
Let's move on.
Let's see.
If you were told to hit one of them, who would it be?
Kiyoshi Nishikawa or Katsura-san?
You're late!
How about this?
I'll let you say it.
So, this one or this one?
Which one?
Let's do it on the count of three.
Wait a minute.
You're definitely going to do it.
I'm going to do it.
So, this one or this one?
I'm definitely going to do it.
Don't betray me like that.
One, two, three.
I'm definitely going to betray you.
Let's make it a two-shot.
I can't let you frame out like that.
One, two, three.
Let's just say one more.
Four or five years ago,
at the Hyokin Yobi High School in Fuji,
when Downtown came out as a regular,
when Kiyoka Nijiko-san came as a guest,
it was about a kiss.
There were two victims.
I think one of them was Mach-chan.
What do you think?
That's exactly right.
That's true.
Kiyoka Nijiko-san kissed him.
That big mouth.
That person was amazing.
Really.
Was he a guest?
Well, I still can't forget the feeling of his lips.
It was like his skin was rotten.
That's true.
It was like a marshmallow.
It was like a marshmallow on his face.
That's right.
After I finished filming,
I cried in the bathroom.
You were tricked.
Really.
It was like a shower.
Can you act now?
That's right.
I'll start with what I have to do.
Today?
The other day, I did the chameleon costume.
Yes, yes, yes.
I said I wanted it,
so I'm wearing this much.
So, can you take it off?
Thank you.
There are many things in it.
I want the wings.
I see.
I heard there were many helmets.
There are no helmets.
No way.
There are only the bow and the body.
No, no, no, no.
Only the body.
The body is big.
It's a 12-dollar soap.
I've never said that.
That's too much.
Let's go with the bow.
I'll wrap it up and send it to you.
This is Ayako Tanigawa, 15 years old.
I'll send it to her.
I'll write a letter,
and I'll answer all your questions.
Please send them to me.
I'll be waiting for you.
I'll be waiting for you next week.
Goodbye.
I'll be waiting for you.
This program is brought to you by
Sponsored by