I'm tired.
It's cold today.
It's hot today.
Really?
I'm sweating.
Really.
Again?
It's hot.
Who is it?
No, no, no.
Thank you.
Go!
Congratulations!
What are you doing?
Hurry up and hand it over!
Why are you so cool?
What is this?
Hamada-san.
I heard that it's your birthday today, so I brought you a present.
No, no, no, that's not necessary.
Please accept it.
No, no, no, no.
I won't accept it.
I've already received this before, and it's already become a big deal.
No, no, no.
It's time for Valentine's Day, right?
Yes.
This year's Valentine's Day, Oshima, who confessed his passionate feelings for Hamada and sent a great death, is finally defeated in the end, but this time, Oshima's love for Hamada is burning.
This program is brought to you by the sponsor you are watching.
Please take it.
No, it's a picture.
I brought it from Oshima.
Well, maybe, but...
I don't like you, dad.
It's your birthday after the show.
I don't like you.
Shut up, you dumbass!
Shut up!
Shut up, you!
Hey, hey!
What? Don't be so loud!
Shut up!
Hey, hey, hey!
Stop it! Stop it!
Stop it!
What are you doing?
What is this?
You're making a scene.
That's enough.
Listen to this.
Let's eat.
Please accept this.
That's enough.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
What is this?
Let's eat.
You guys are so annoying.
The type of woman is different.
If it's a girl, everyone will eat you.
If you get angry.
What are you talking about?
He said many times.
He said that he likes a girl who doesn't get hurt even if he puts a
quagata in her nose.
I like a girl who doesn't get hurt.
Really?
But there is no quagata.
I don't have it.
What's wrong?
Oh, there's a scary guy!
What?
He's following us!
We can do this!
You're really something.
There's a scary guy!
What?
Really?
You're really something.
Wow!
Go!
He'll definitely turn around.
We can do this!
Are you ready?
Go, go, go!
I'll go.
Hamada-san.
Yes?
Please come out.
What the hell?
She's crying! She's crying!
You idiot! Where are you going?
Where are you going?
That's strange.
That's not what I meant.
What's going on?
What was that?
I went to the love hotel. I know nothing.
That's what you're saying.
I like fat women.
I don't like middle-aged women.
I don't like them at all.
I like them more fat.
You know, the balloon that goes in your nose.
I've heard that they say that.
But that's serious.
Even if it's wrong, there's no balloon.
Well, it's a bit sudden. So, I'll do my best next year.
Ah!
Here!
What?
The giant balloon!
It's stuck!
I can do it!
It's low.
Let's do it!
This is the giant balloon.
This is it, right?
The giant balloon.
What?
Everyone, let's eat cake!
I'll go right now!
I can do it!
You can do it!
You're cute!
Mr. Kamada!
Yes?
Go away!
You are a little...
Wait a minute!
It's hot!
What is this?
Please go out with me.
Go out?
Wait a minute.
Huh? Why?
That's not it.
Why?
What?
Why did you reject me?
Because...
You should have said it after we broke up.
That's right.
You should have said it at the right time.
You should have said it when we were in a good mood.
I didn't.
You should have said it after we broke up.
Nonki?
Oh, yes! I remember!
What?
Hama, you like to be a comedian, don't you?
That's right.
It's very simple.
I wonder what it is to be a comedian.
It could be a hip-hop star.
I think he likes it.
He likes it.
I said it to myself.
I like that kind of girl.
I suddenly felt like I liked her.
You liked her?
Yes, I liked her.
I liked her even more when she was near my face.
Really?
I heard that.
What is this?
It's carbonated water.
I can get it with this.
It's leaking.
It's low grade.
It's yours.
I can get it with this.
Do your best.
There's everything I want.
Okay.
Good luck.
It's your chance.
I'll be right in front of you.
Good luck.
I'll be right under your screen.
Okay.
Bye bye.
What are you doing?
You're making me angry!
It's not coming out well!
You're...
You're not the same as before!
We have to go to the drama location now.
We're going home.
We're not going anywhere today.
I'm the only one who has nothing to do today.
That's right.
Thank you.
Wait a minute. What's going on?
Let's go, Mr. Hamada. Let's go. Let's chase him.
Let's go this far. Let's go.
Let's go to the drama. Let's go.
Really?
Wait a minute.
The person Hamada is going to shoot is the popular drama, Ashi-Tanarusa.
The main character, Hamada, is doing this shoot on a very busy schedule.
He is showing a serious expression that is different from a smile
In such a busy filming site, the broadcast special of Thai, Mr. Mori is sneaking in
It's the real thing
What are you doing now?
No no no
Ah, there he is
There he is
It's the real thing
From now on, it's the real thing
This is bad
But it's better to go
It can't be helped
I'm going
Hey, I started eating hot Doria.
Oh, by the way, Hamada-san, you seem to like hot Doria.
And you like it with bare hands, right?
I've heard of it.
Really?
What do you mean? You like hot Doria with bare hands?
I like rough women.
So you like hot Doria?
Lucky! You can do it! Do it!
Do it! You're a drama actor now!
It's starting!
It's okay, it's okay. Look back, look back.
Oshima!
Hey, hey, how many are you going to do?
Hey, hey, let's go.
This is serious. This is serious.
This is serious.
Come on, let's start.
Let's go with this.
What the hell?
What's going on?
That idiot!
Cut!
Please don't say that.
We're doing this for business.
Yes.
It's not that kind of condition.
Please do something about it.
Please.
I understand that you're worried, but
Please, please.
Hey, someone is behind you.
It looks like it.
Do your best! Do your best!
What are you doing?
Please help me!
Go home.
Don't you know what you're doing?
You're in the way. Go home.
Oshima, go home.
You should go home.
Go home.
Please take care of me.
You're in the way. Go home.
Don't laugh.
Matsumoto.
You're a hacker.
You're not a hacker.
It's a drama.
Drama!
Cut!
Okay, okay.
It's over.
What are we going to do?
Let's go! Let's go! Let's chase after them!
What are you doing?
What a great vitality.
You're doing it.
I don't know.
I wonder if he's a drug addict.
I wonder if he's at work.
There he is.
He's got a little bit of a thrill.
Hamada-san, by the way,
I've heard that you like girls who have protruding eyes, like fox eyes.
I've heard that.
He wrote that on Mausoleum Yoshimoto.
I think I've heard that.
He wrote that.
I don't know but if you wear a stocking and put on a parachute and get blown by the wind...
Then you'd be able to go fishing.
If you were in that situation...
Even if you say that, there's no way there's a huge fan.
You're right.
A huge fan!
I'm wearing one!
I can do it!
I'll go!
You're amazing!
Stop it!
Are you okay? I don't know anymore.
It's really starting.
Can I start around here?
Yes.
There should be more.
Search for it.
Search for everything.
Somehow.
It's a failure.
Ah, it's coming!
Yes, I'm sorry.
Ah!
Who did this?
That's scary!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
What's wrong, what's wrong?
Please date with him!
I'm telling you to go home.
Please take it.
What's the point? Go home.
Go home.
I told you to go home, but you still said that.
What's this?
This is not what we were talking about.
What should we do?
So, should we really stop?
Really?
Right?
Should we give up?
I can't give up.
This love is impossible.
This love is impossible!
Hanagata-san has moved!
Please hurry!
I'm busy!
Stop it!
You're a stalker!
I can't give up!
You're a total fool!
You know it!
He's not Hamada's type. He's S.
He's the type that bullies women.
That's good.
Really?
He even uses water to...
What's that?
He's not a bad guy.
Can he do that?
He can do it.
Really?
Really? But if he tries to do that, he'll get hit by a rato.
You're being drenched in water with a rat.
That's what it is.
It's a special story.
It's impossible.
There's no water or rats.
It's no good.
That's right.
That's why I'm saying it.
Wah!
A rat!
It's stuck!
It's stuck really well.
Even the water pump!
Huh?
Hey, hey!
Maybe your destiny is to become the king.
I'm going to go.
Hey, are you going?
Kame! Kame!
Why do you always do it when it's the real thing?
This is a very serious scene.
It's a scene like that.
What are you doing?
He's really something.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Wait a minute, wait a minute.
I understand how you feel, but I don't understand how you feel.
I don't understand how you feel.
Please, let me go.
Don't get in the way.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Run away, Oshima!
You guys are overreacting!
We won't let you get close to the scene.
We promise.
We don't have any drama that we don't care about.
That's right.
We don't care about the drama.
Please.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Really.
Yes.
You gave up.
It's not about giving up.
If you listen to him, you'll see what he's like. He's a wreck.
Nobuko, what are you doing?
Nobuko!
This is a bowling alley.
What are you going to do?
It's your job.
Let's give up.
Wait!
Bowling!
I'm serious.
I'm coming.
What are you going to do?
But, you know, you're bowling, right?
I'm talking about now.
Yes.
Hamada-san loves to get strikes.
Really?
Really.
But, you know, it's the same thing.
It's the same thing.
It's convenient like this.
In the bowling alley.
You just need to get a strike.
Well, I'm sorry.
Hang in there.
You can do it.
Stop it.
It's not real.
If it's not real, he will be in trouble.
Alright! I'll strike a little.
Okay!
Alright!
Let's go!
Alright! Let's go!
Go! Go! Go!
Hey!
Please go out with me!
No, no, no!
Mr. Hamada, Mr. Hamada!
Please, please!
Mr. Hamada, what are you thinking?
Mr. Hamada!
Please, please!
What? Was it this kind of character?
You woke him up, Mr. Hamada!
You shouldn't have woken him up!
Sorry, I was just standing there.
You were just standing there.
I don't know, really.
Shut up!
Sorry.
Come here.
I'm sorry.
Let's go.
I told you.
Jeez.
I knew it.
Next time.
Wow, amazing.
What the hell.
Hey.
I can't hear you at all!
Hey!
What are you doing?
Robocon, let me go!
Robocon!
Let me go!
Are you okay?
It's okay to be like that.
Take it easy.
What the hell!
Don't do that.
I'm going.
I don't know what to do.
Is he okay?
The way he walks is a bit...
Next time, if you go to a golf scene, you'll see how much you'll be looked down on by the club.
Yeah, this time it's scary.
It's scary, so let's really stop.
Let's really stop.
However!
I was wondering why he wouldn't accept it so much.
He likes short-cut girls.
Short-cut?
Isn't that enough?
That's more than enough.
I think that's enough.
I think that's impossible.
You can't do three shots in a row.
That's impossible.
It's not possible.
I think it's better to go home.
What?
That's the
golf club.
They are playing golf.
What?
Oh, really?
It's stuck, Oshima!
It's stuck!
Hey, hey, hey!
Go and tell him!
What are you doing?
I ran over there.
Yeah.
What should I do?
I wonder if it's okay.
Then, I'll go back to my original position.
Yeah, go back to your original position.
Let's go.
I'm ready.
Hey!
Hit!
Please, please, please!
Please!
Stop it!
You said you can't do it anymore!
Please!
Sliiidee!
Ah!
Slippery, slippery, slippery, slippery.
What are you doing?
I hate you!
Ouch!
Robocon! Robocon!
Help me, Robocon!
Stop it.
Hey!
You guys are so annoying.
I don't know. I don't know.
I don't know.
Why?
You are so stupid.
You like this kind of thing, don't you?
I told you. I told you.
Hey, you.
I told you.
I like this kind of thing.
Here is your present.
What are you doing?
You!
Get out of here!
I don't think this is enough!
You!
I'll come back!
Get out of here!
You bastard!
I'm sorry.
I don't know what to do.
You couldn't stop him?
I think he'll come next week.
What?
Are you serious?
Seriously?