After this, let's hit the punch-bomb at the Gake no Tsukai in downtown!
What?
I can hear it!
What is it?
What's going on?
What time is it now?
It's a little past 5 o'clock.
That's right.
It's already 6 o'clock, isn't it?
What's going on?
Isn't it already 6 o'clock?
You're always angry.
Good morning.
Excuse me, I just got a call from Matsumoto.
Yes.
It looks like an accident.
What?
What kind of accident?
Well...
He said he got hit by a fly.
Oh, really?
Yes.
I see.
Good morning.
Matsumoto, did you get hit by a fly?
Yes.
What? Did you hear that voice?
I heard it a little while ago.
What?
Well...
I'll go to the salon for a while.
Yes.
My shoulder hurts.
It's okay.
It's not a joke.
It's pretty late, isn't it?
Yes.
It's a call from Hikako.
Hello, this is Hikako.
Hello.
It hurts.
Is it Matsumoto?
Yes.
It hurts.
I'm sorry to hear that.
What?
It's not a call from Matsumoto.
Oh, well...
I see.
Do you know where he is?
I don't know.
You don't know where he is, do you?
I don't know where he is.
Let's ask him.
I'll do it.
Don't do it.
You can't do it.
There's no point in doing it even if you get injured.
What are you saying?
It's a TV program.
Yes.
He's an actor and an actor.
Put it on.
Is it close?
It's almost there.
You said it's almost there.
OK, I'll put it on and go.
Let's go.
Huh?
What?
What is it?
Where is it?
Hey, hey, hey.
What are you doing?
Get out of here.
We're friends.
Stop it.
Get out of here.
What's wrong with him?
It hurts, it hurts.
Are you OK?
I'm shaking.
I'm sweating.
Did you do it on purpose?
Yeah.
Huh?
Well, that's what the police say.
Yeah.
It's 64 and the other side is bad, so you're OK.
I don't think it's your fault.
I think it was pouring.
Yeah.
I gave you a strange chance.
You're sweating.
I think it's because your body is burning.
You're sweating because it's hot.
Yeah.
Are you OK today?
Shiroku.
Let's go to bed.
We can't talk much.
Yeah.
It's a variety show, but we won't get injured.
What do we do?
Matsumoto.
I.
I'll do it.
Matsumoto.
I gave up.
Master, master, master, master, master, master, master, master, master...
I'm really sorry to hear that.
Excuse me, I just got a call from Matsumoto.
It seems they have an accident.
What kind of accident?
I heard that you are from Okamagura.
What are you talking about?
Okamagura?
Yes.
What kind of Okamagura?
I heard that you are from Okamagura.
You are beautiful.
It's the first time I use a needle.
It's beautiful.
The punishment is not bad.
Let's do our best.
There is still a punishment game.
Yes, there is.
Let's do that.
My nose is drooping.
Everyone says that my nose is drooping in the opening.
But I can't get that blue lantern.
It's hard.
I don't know the school.
I can see it when I look up.
It's really cool.
It's blue.
I can't get it.
No matter how many times I do it.
This job is hard.
Yes.
There are people who are always angry.
Even if they are fighting.
What do you say?
They say,
What are you doing?
It's a joke.
There are times when it becomes a joke.
Do you understand?
I understand.
If it's a fight on the street.
They say,
Is there such a stupid story?
It's a fight that's established.
They say,
What are you doing?
This is too much.
It's not a fight.
But they say,
That's you.
No, no.
Sometimes it's closer to a joke than anything.
This is a job disease.
Yes.
Usually.
I'm saying a little bit.
Yes.
You're taking a bath.
The man next to you.
I was in the middle of a fight.
I don't know anything.
You can say,
Hey.
Yes.
It's the same as that.
I'm always thinking about something like that.
I'm going with this kind of biology.
I can't help it.
I see.
What are you going to do today?
So, after this,
There's a punishment game left.
There's something I have to do.
It's a punishment game.
Well, I'm not losing in rugby.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, for the time being.
I played with all of them.
I'm not playing in a team.
I'm already losing.
No, I'm not losing at all.
No, I'm not losing.
If I played seriously,
There's no sport that can beat me.
You know that.
I'm still saying.
Did you touch the ball even once in the last game?
What's wrong?
Something's going on in the back.
I don't know.
That rugby is made up of fake rules.
What do you mean?
Do you know?
Do you know? Do you know?
Let's stop it.
Well, shall we say it?
What kind of nonsense is that?
So, the real rugby is
It's about 40 minutes and 40 minutes.
That rugby is that everyone has no physical strength.
That's right.
Think about you.
Why?
I did it in 10 minutes and 10 minutes.
That's my body.
Why?
No, for me, 10 minutes is really a little bit.
What do you say?
There's something close to an audible.
From there on, it's called a stretch.
10 minutes is still a disaster.
It's a disaster.
It's a jellyfish.
Do you understand?
I understand.
I'm going to go from there.
I don't know.
Even in Yamato, it takes time to make a wave.
What are you going to do with Yamato?
No, no, really, really.
That's why I didn't touch the ball.
I was looking at it.
I'm in a hurry, but I'm scared.
That's why I'm going like this.
I see.
It hurts.
What are you going to do with the past?
I said, okay, I got it.
When it comes to this,
It's already.
No, it's not.
It's over in the first half.
There's a second half.
There's a second half left.
My body is like this.
It's like this.
Everyone's starting to move again.
Let's go like this.
Are you watching again?
Why are you running?
Are you still watching?
No matter what I did, the time was short.
If I had 10 minutes left, I would have done it.
What are you doing?
You're doing a great job.
Don't say such a thing.
It's true.
That's enough.
You say you didn't do anything.
You say that, but you didn't do anything.
I didn't do anything either.
I touched the ball twice.
I grabbed it and ran.
Even though I was defeated.
I also scored two goal kicks.
You were like this.
When I looked up, the members were like this.
Everyone was moaning.
I always say this.
What?
If I don't save and play sports,
If I move like you do,
It's really amazing.
It's a spring-bucket bowl.
I don't know.
No, really.
If I kick that ball as much as I want,
It's going to be a big deal.
What do you mean?
What do you mean by a big deal?
I don't even know that.
What?
Is there such an excuse?
I don't know.
It's not an excuse.
I got it.
I'm going to quit the group.
What are you talking about?
I should go to individual matches.
If I get kicked by so many people,
You!
What are you talking about?
It's the same with baseball.
I lost because you kicked me.
What?
Really?
Did you save your strength?
I did. Of course I did.
Of course you did?
Of course I did.
I'm glad you gave me a big one.
My strength is...
My arm...
What?
My strength is...
My power is...
My arm is...
The power of a gold mine.
What are you talking about?
Do you understand?
So what?
You shake your arm like this.
You're shaking it off, right?
The power you gave me at that time
It's not a big shock to your arm.
The base that supports your arm
Your strength is
It's as good as you.
It's going well.
But if I put out all my strength,
I'm really going to lose my arm.
You don't like it, do you?
I can't lose my arm.
I don't like it.
You can't lose your arm.
When we're having fun together,
I can't lose my arm.
You're not happy.
It doesn't matter.
I don't like it.
That's why I'm doing it because I don't want to bother you.
You can't lose your arm.
That's why I only throw you Herrnachocodama.
suffered
Hey, don't call it Herrnachocodama.
You're a Herrnachocodama.
If this is what I'm like,
I'll throw you, right?
Let's do arm sweep.
The arm goes like this.
Can you get me a blow?
Then you'll live.
When it comes to the outro.
100% I can't get a hold of.
I'm not worried about it, but I'm scared of the catcher.
I'll pay for it.
You can't do that. I'm doing it because it's heavy.
I don't know what you're talking about.
It's you. Don't say it's heavy.
I've never said anything that I don't understand.
You can say it now.
I can't lift my arm.
Even if I lift it with all my might.
Do you want to buy it?
What are you doing?
Why am I a punishment game?
You're unlucky.
Why?
Do you want to do judo?
It's true.
I'm good at judo.
Okay.
Let's do it.
I'm really good at judo.
Is that so?
Yes.
But I hate judo.
You can't do that.
There's one more thing.
I have a big chest.
Your hands and feet are slippery.
Why do you have a big chest?
It's disgusting.
I don't know.
I don't want to show it.
I don't want to show my chest.
Okay.
Let's go home.
It's difficult to have a big audience.
At that time.
So, how can I say?
There are times when the audience is heavy.
There are.
Yes.
So, when everyone is gathered together,
There are times when unlucky people are gathering together.
Yes.
So, the audience is heavy.
The atmosphere is heavy.
Yes.
There are times when the audience is heavy.
Especially, there are many female guests.
There are also female guests.
Yes.
And if it's a heavy day,
Your face will turn blue.
If you are seen like this,
I want you to say,
Oh my goodness!
It's heavy.
It's great.
Oh my goodness.
It's different.
And female bodies.
It's annoying.
Yes, it is.
Incredible things are going on.
What are thinking?
If we get out like this,
It must hurt so bad.
It hurts!
I'm surprised!
It doesn't hurt!
It's fine!
It doesn't hurt, but it's bleeding!
Even though it's bleeding, it's fine!
That's great!
When I was a kid, when my dad was thrown into the sea and drowned,
I was told that there was a danger signal.
When I was in elementary school, I rushed into a concrete pillar with great speed from the face.
When I thought I was going to die, I saw a skull mark in front of me.
I've been saying this for a long time.
What is it?
There should be some kind of sign before a person dies.
Oh, is that so?
Get on more!
You're shy, aren't you?
Oh, is that so?
Don't say that.
I'm sorry.
There should be some kind of sign before a person dies.
What?
Why aren't you surprised?
There should be a sign.
Oh, is that so?
I can't tell you that there was a sign.
I can't tell you because I'm dead.
Yes, yes, yes.
I understand.
There should be some kind of sign before a person dies.
What is that?
Is there a personal difference?
No, that's why I said there should be a blue flower before I die.
That's because you almost drowned in the pool.
There's a lot of oysters around you.
He's about to die.
You say there should be a blue flower.
What kind of blue flower do you think it is?
What do you mean?
That's it.
Specifically, it's emerald green.
What are you talking about?
What kind of color is emerald green?
What kind of color is it?
It looks normal.
It's close to that.
This one?
There's a flower like this.
That's before you die.
There's a flower like this before you die.
It's dangerous to have a flower like that.
Is that so?
I'm sure there's something like that.
The moment you hit a car,
you say something to your right.
That's it.
Who is whispering to his right?
Is it a god?
I absolutely believe in that.
From the building,
you jump down.
You fall to the ground.
It's about one meter above the ground.
You jump down.
When you're about to hit the ground,
you say,
Thank you very much.
I'm sure there's something like that.
But it's funny if you hear that before you die.
Why don't you give it a try?
On the car.
Is it your first time meeting?
If you get on the car
and drive right to the wall,
you'll probably hear it.
That's how dirty your eyes are.
You know, there's that thing that's been done recently.
Air bomb.
I think it's difficult to be a shinigami for that reason.
You're in trouble.
Yes, yes, yes.
Shinigamis are always watching.
They think, I'm going to do this, I'm going to do that.
I don't know why the shinigami these days hit cars.
In the old days, you could just say, see you.
You could just look at the steering wheel and see if it's airbag style or not.
They say bad things.
I see.
You have to check that first.
I have to check it first.
Shinigamis are in trouble these days.
You're in trouble.
You can't say that.
I'm sorry.
I have something I really want to tell you, Dauntan-sama.
The man in the Lark commercial for cigarettes,
why is he always aiming for someone's life?
I don't know.
He used to run away in a car on a narrow street.
He used to run away on a boat or something.
He used to carry a bottle of champagne and drop it.
He was always aiming for someone's life.
I wonder if everyone knows about this.
Hey, Lark.
Do you know about this?
Yes, I do.
This man used to smoke a lot.
What did he smoke?
What?
Well, I told him to quit smoking.
What did you tell him?
I told him to quit smoking.
He didn't listen to me.
You should have told him.
I should have told him.
You're a bad guy.
You're right.
Yes.
Come here.
You're a bad guy.