We are now at the station of Monzennaka-cho.
I have no idea where we are.
Last week, we wanted to go to a place where there are no people at all.
We wanted to go to a place where there are no people at all.
Suddenly, you got on the subway.
The meaning is different.
We went to Toyo-cho, which is two stations away.
Did you go?
Yes, I did.
The girl's nape is like this.
Like this.
Can you point at her?
What are you doing?
Are you pointing at the girl's nape?
This girl's nape is like this.
How about this girl?
Oh, close your eyes.
Where are you going?
I'm going home.
Be careful.
She's dyed her hair.
Where are you going?
I'll shake your hand.
What are you doing?
If you're going to see her, take her with you.
What are you going to do?
I'm going.
You're going, aren't you?
What are you doing?
What a big dog.
Hey, come here.
What are you doing with that dog?
Don't you do anything to people who are walking?
I'll bite your nape.
You'll bite my nape?
Idiot.
I'm at Wakatake today.
There are already a lot of dirty people here.
Already.
Mom.
Where is your mom?
There.
Thank you very much.
This is downtown.
Downtown.
It's like a
Did you buy this for me?
Yes.
This is the most expensive show I've ever been on.
It's beautiful.
Amazing.
If you turn on the lights, it's going to be cool.
I've been walking for a long time.
Shall we start?
Let's start.
This is Wakatake.
Let's have a lot of fun.
Thank you very much.
Have a nice day.
It's fun.
This program is brought to you by Toyo Suisan, Oyama International Products, and these sponsors.
Thank you very much.
This is the fifth time.
It's the fifth time.
To be honest, this is the most painful show I've ever been on.
There are many guys here.
There are a few guys today.
Depending on where you are, there is a theatre nearby.
Most of the people there come.
There's also a young guy called Otoyan.
I wonder how much they'll understand.
I think it's difficult.
Today's the 5th time, so I have to change the topic every time.
I have to change it so that they can hear the new one.
The topic is almost gone, and it's hard to speak clearly.
It's a very difficult situation.
It's no use saying it.
So today, say anything. I'll do anything.
There's a lot of good stuff.
I have a lot of good things.
I'll give you one.
This is the most popular topic.
There's a chocolate pocky.
Or you can put it in your ass and change it to a pretz.
Don't take it.
This is good.
This is good wherever you go.
You can do the opposite.
You can't take a pretz.
Don't do it.
I'll change it to something I say.
I'll take it too much, so if I do more, it'll be a strawberry pocky.
Stop it.
I'll take this.
I have a lot of good things, but I'm scared of the TV show.
It doesn't matter if it's summer or winter.
It's a world you don't know.
For example, if it's a basic person, it's a mental picture.
An old man comes out and explains.
This is an example of something.
It's scary, isn't it?
For example, a hand was reflected on the shoulder.
Do you know?
I took a commemorative photo with a friend.
A hand was reflected on the shoulder of a person.
Bang!
Ah!
Where is it?
It's there.
A hand was reflected on the shoulder.
A hand was reflected.
When I took a picture, there was an officer of the Self-Defense Force standing behind me.
That's not true!
I'll take a picture, but you're not in the Self-Defense Force.
There's nothing behind you.
It's just behind you.
There's nothing behind you, but there's a hand behind you.
That's the kind of person you are.
That's not true!
Hey!
I'm staying at home!
I can't trust the self-defense photo.
There's more.
The officer of the Self-Defense Force.
Do you know?
When I took a picture.
Here.
Around the waist.
The officer of the Self-Defense Force.
He has a cut on his forearm.
His head is rough.
His face is covered in blood.
If something were to happen, would he have a cut on his forearm?
What do you mean by what would happen?
Are you asking if something is wrong or not?
Are you asking what would happen?
Is it about the service?
What's wrong with that?
If something were to happen.
What would happen?
Your arm is cut!
If something were to happen, would you have a cut on your forearm?
I'm definitely sure.
That disgusting face was on the back of my waist.
Bam!
Ahhhh!
I'm a servant of the government.
On the waist?
The disgusting part?
Here?
That's a...
Poset.
You're lying!
If you wear that disgusting poset, I'll kill you!
I'm telling you to kill me!
No.
Where do you sell those posets, you idiot?
I sell them at Tokyo Hands.
The blue part here is just right and you can wear anything.
You're lying! You're lying, you idiot!
I can't believe it.
You're lying, lying, and you're walking down the street and your shoulders are touching...
Yeah!
Just walking down the street and being a busybody is a lot of fun these days.
There's nothing wrong with that. What's wrong with that?
You just walk down the street and in some unknown street you pass by and your shoulders are touched
and you don't care about that.
When I came back home, I saw blood all over my shoulder.
What are you doing?
Are you a little drunk?
The sponsor is...
What is that?
There is only 4% alcohol in it.
I can't drink any more.
That's too much.
It's a little different from usual.
It's called the 3-piece.
I don't care.
I was touched by the sponsor.
I was touched by the sponsor and went home.
I was bleeding.
It's scary.
I'm the only one who's scared.
I was touched by the sponsor and went home.
I was more scared.
What?
I was scared of the park near my house.
I heard it and everyone screamed.
Stop talking.
I'll tell you a story.
About three years ago,
I was walking alone in the park near my house.
I saw a man with a pale face coming down from the slide.
Brother, brother.
I was touched by the sponsor.
When I looked back, the man was gone.
I went to the jungle gym.
When I got home, I saw blood all over my shoulder.
It's dirty.
It's scarier than death.
It's scarier than blood all over your shoulder.
It's scarier than poop.
It's scary.
What are you talking about?
It's scarier than death.
If you eat too much peanuts,
your nose will come out.
If you eat too much peanuts, your nose will come out.
It's scarier than death.
If you are a detective or a police officer,
and a murder happened somewhere,
where is it?
It's in the apartment.
Go and open the door of the apartment.
There is a body covered in blood.
There is a body covered in poop.
Which one will you kill?
If there is such a person,
I'll kill him with a stick or something.
If there is such a person, I'll kill him with a stick or something.
What do you know about the body covered in poop?
You are talking nonsense.
You are saying that it's scarier than death.
I'm not saying that.
I'm saying that I have a spirit.
You have a spirit.
There is still something scary.
You have to listen to me.
Do you know?
There is a woman who lives alone.
He sits in front of the church.
He is prayerful.
But
He isn't talking to his grandfather who died three years ago.
He can feel lonely because he is alone.
Heís talking to his grandmother.
The woman in the back acts as if she was siebie.
The woman in the back acts as if she wasitié.
And he is very quiet.
You are saying that you want to go to see the mother of the dead.
Do you know what means?
I don't know what this is.
What the scary story is.
The old lady, even though she was dead, she didn't accept it, so she sat in front of the Buddha's altar by herself.
The old lady is still alive!
The old man died, and the old man came out!
I told you to sit in front of the Buddha's altar!
The old lady isn't a ghost?
No, the old man came out, and said,
I want to say something, but I can't.
The old man?
The old man said, I want to say something, but I can't.
I understand the old man's feelings.
He's a pervert.
You're stupid!
No, he's a pervert!
He's a pervert?
He said, I want to say something, but I can't.
That's why he came out.
Are you forcing me?
That's normal.
There's a waterfall.
There's a rock at the top of the waterfall.
What are you talking about?
If you look at the rock at the top of the waterfall,
there's a woman standing on the rock.
What?
If you look at the rock at the top of the waterfall,
there's a woman standing on the rock.
What?
If you look at the rock at the top of the waterfall,
there's a woman standing on the rock.
What?
You're good.
You're good?
Are you listening to me?
There's a woman standing on the rock at the top of the waterfall.
What?
It's hard work.
If you do it, you'll do it.
Don't fall and die!
Don't fall and die on the rock.
Say that you came out to the rock because you're a pervert.
Are you forcing me?
I can't believe that.
Say that you came out to the rock because you're a pervert.
What?
I can't believe that.
You said that you were possessed.
That's the scariest thing.
Do you know what happens if you're possessed by a white snake or a fox?
That's amazing.
When I was in high school, my classmate did this.
When the teacher was writing, he was sitting.
He jumped.
He jumped?
What was that?
He jumped.
I don't think he was possessed by anything.
He was the one who was always in the class.
That's not true.
He was possessed by a white snake.
My classmate saw him while he was writing.
He saw him?
He saw him.
He saw my classmate while he was writing.
What are you talking about?
You're a pervert.
That's not true.
You said that.
What?
You just heard that.
Why are you talking about me?
That's right.
He was possessed.
That's scary.
What do you mean?
For example, I think there are people who drive cars.
There are dogs and cats next to you.
You're being pulled.
They're passing by.
When I passed by, I thought, that's so sad.
It's an animal ghost.
When I thought that's so sad, they came in.
For example, a dog.
Yes, yes, yes.
One of my friends.
He was caught in a burning fire.
I felt sorry for him.
Didn't you hear that?
He was running on the street.
He was being dragged.
I felt sorry for him, so I came in.
Where were you running?
I was running.
On a rainy day.
I saw a burning image.
I felt sorry for him.
I went down and put a blanket on him.
I went in.
After that, I talked to him.
He was crying.
My relative.
He was caught by a mackerel.
He was running in the rain.
I saw a mackerel.
The mackerel closed its eyes quietly.
I went down and put a blanket on him.
The mackerel was running.
I took off my pants.
The mackerel was smelly.
He was the only one who was laughing.
I said, let's go to the beach.
He said, go home.
Yes, yes.
I went to the beach.
I was scolded by a mackerel.
Let's go.
It's a sound.
It's a sound that I rarely hear.
Thank you very much.
That girl is a good girl.
Yes, she is an assistant in the program.
I'm still recruiting her.
The staff asked me if I had a TV show.
By the way, I'm glad I'm not angry.
What?
You are a bad person.
I'm glad I'm not angry.
I'm not angry.
I don't know because I'm wearing makeup.
But when I take off my makeup, my face is red.
Don't say such a thing.
This is the fifth time.
I'll give you the nose hair product.
Please take a look at it.
I'll use it later.
I'm not good at this.
This is a person.
Kurimoto Maki-chan.
I'm still in the second floor.
I'm having fun with it.
I'm still in the second floor, so it's okay.
Will you continue to do manzai?
Don't you have any more material?
That is the place of the downtown.
I believe that even after 20 or 30 times, I will continue to do manzai.
Please do your best!
It's the story like this.
What do you think about this?
20 or 30 times, he will continue to do material.
Hmm...
What do you think?
Thank you very much.
Even if it's a joke, in the end it's all up to me.
Yes, yes, yes.
Right?
I'm the only one who can think of a joke.
And then...
You recruited an assistant, right?
And then, there's this thing where they tell you to stop doing things like this.
This person told me to put in a photo.
Yoshida-san.
Yoshida Satomi-san.
Please send me another one.
He sent me a photo like this.
Ouch!
And this is me, right?
Even if you hate me, you won't understand.
Umm...
If you don't think about it.
You're giving me a lot of energy.
That's right, but...
This kind of thing...
Even if you tell me this is a photo of the culprit, I can't solve it.
Have you ever been angry?
I haven't been angry recently.
I'm having a lot of fun every day.
Why is that?
Why?
The place has changed.
You can't solve it that easily.
I can solve it.
I'm also from Tokyo.
You're annoying.
I'm going back to Osaka tomorrow.
I don't have the feeling of going back to Osaka.
I'm going to Kansai.
The intonation is different.
Yes, yes, yes.
You're going to Kansai?
I'm going to Kansai.
There were a lot of letters like that.
There are some difficult words in Osaka dialect.
I asked you how about Osaka dialect.
That's right.
In my makeup shop,
There's no dip.
There's a new product.
New.
It's a new product.
I took it and said,
This is a plate.
It's a plate.
Can I use it?
What?
I don't know what a plate is.
If you say plate, it's like a sanitary product.
That's not it.
This is a plate.
This is different from the intonation.
What I'm saying is a plate.
The sanitary products are amazing these days.
What are you talking about?
It has nothing to do with you.
The absorbency is amazing.
It's nothing.
My mother
When I used the absorbency,
It went up.
You're lying.
The absorbency is amazing.
You know,
There's something on the eyes.
What do you call that?
Monomorai?
Monomorai.
That's not it.
In Osaka, it's called monomorai.
It doesn't make sense.
In Osaka, it's called
Mebatsuko.
Don't laugh.
Don't make fun of me.
Mebatsuko.
Everyone laughs when I say this.
When I'm sleeping, I laugh like this.
Mebatsuko.
What's wrong with you?
I'm so angry.
That's right.
That's what it is.
For example, people who are watching
This is what it looks like in Osaka.
What do you mean by this?
That's what it is.
So maybe
Let's do it once.
Let's do it.
This is what it looks like.
I'll use it like this.
I'd like to do it again.
You studied today, didn't you?
What do you call monomorai?
Mebatsuko.
That's right.
You've learned one thing.
Mebatsuko.
Here you go.
So,
You've learned one thing about Osaka.
That's all for today. Goodbye.
No.
It's over.
How was it?
Well, it was good.
There were a lot of people who laughed.
So,
There were a lot of people from the city hall.
I don't usually have much fun.
I'm happy.
That's what it looks like.
And
I've been checking a lot.
Oh, before the show?
Yeah.
I picked up about four people.
You picked up about four people.
That was good.
Four people.
That's right.
If it were those four people,
I'd give them about 50,000 yen.
That's where I usually spend money.
I'm thinking about going somewhere next time.
That's right.
We're all together.
If I go somewhere else,
I feel a sense of freedom.
That's right.
Well, it doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter.
Well,
It's decided.
Of course, that's right.
What?
That's right.
Well, that's it.
Well,
There were a lot of people.
Osaka-men's way of speaking.
There were a lot of things.
That's right.
Goodbye.
This program is a production of TOYO.
Ooyama International Products