In the first episode, we will be talking about the story of the child's use.
Yamazaki Ose, 36 years old, same age, talent, 1000 yen cut, Last Samurai!
Yamachan is outside, right?
It feels like he was taken out.
Hello, I'm Yamazaki Ose.
I know.
Today, I think I beat a comedian of the same age as me.
What do you mean?
I'm 36 years old, and I'm Niji's father.
Niji's father?
I don't need those characters anymore!
Well, that's something you've said a lot.
Right?
Well, honestly...
That's what I mean.
How many of them are there?
The 36-year-old game character.
There's a lot of them.
Yamamoto Kokuraku, Hoto Yamaguchi...
Today, I thought I'd beat this guy first.
Oh, wow!
Are you the same age?
Mr. Higashino.
Look at this guy!
He's a senior.
I have to defeat him to get my love.
Look at this cold-hearted guy!
He's a person who has never loved anyone.
He once threw a dead turtle into a trash can.
He said, BOOM!
Can you imagine?
He's such a person. I have to defeat him!
I see.
You are the enemy of society.
What can I defeat?
What is the thing that I can be the best?
Well, it's not comedy.
Well, comedy is also the same.
Sword!
What is the sword?
It's the sword art.
Sword art.
I'll show you the sword art today.
That's why you're wearing this today?
Of course.
I'm calling that guy, Kouji Higashino.
Really?
Come out!
Good morning!
It's been a while!
It's been a while for the Konoha group
Have you been out?
I have. I took off my underwear.
I took off my underwear here.
I don't remember at all.
No, no, I'm not in the east.
Ouch, ouch, ouch.
I came to Dubai.
No, you came to Dubai, so you're in the middle of the Haneda.
Sorry, sorry.
It's like a matcha and a
Wait a minute.
Ah, don't pull it down.
Just a little.
What the hell is that?
You bastard!
You're not worth anything!
I'm sick of this.
I don't care how many times you say that, but I don't have any money.
How many years have you been married?
Two years.
You have a funny face.
He's really angry.
I've been married for two years.
Even if Sanae gets angry, I'll be fine.
First of all,
Are you divorced?
Why did you get divorced?
You're not the one to say that.
I thought your family was the ideal.
Thank you very much.
I'm sorry.
Let's get back to work.
Wait, Dachi-san!
Wait a minute.
I thought it would be better to say something real.
The reason I wanted to defeat you is because you're hard to get along with.
What?
You can see it now, right?
It's really hard to get along with.
I see.
It's harder for me to get along with you.
I want to beat you from the top!
Okay, then let's end this with the one who has 10,000 points.
I thought so too.
That's fine.
Do the judgement.
The judgement of love.
I have 10,000 points.
Are you ready, Anjou-san?
Yes, yes.
The fight is about to begin.
Do it seriously!
Of course I will!
Do you think I'm going to do it with a lie?
Don't say such cold things!
He's really angry.
It's really hard to get involved.
I thought it was a woman.
Yamada Keho is 36 years old.
That hurts.
He's 36 years old in the east.
Last samurai.
Ready?
Start!
Yamada-san, you were doing kendo.
You were so sloppy.
Hit!
Oh, no!
It's not even one point yet!
It's a tie!
I can't do anything about this!
I'll use my sword!
A sword is a sword!
A sword! A sword!
It's over!
I'll use my sword!
The last samurai!
What?
How is it?
Oh no!
Ken! Zaki-san, Ken!
Kenjutsu!
What the hell!
It's Ken!
Zaki-san, you're getting beaten!
You're getting beaten!
What the hell! Why are you getting beaten with a Ken?
What?
Oh my
The end
What the hell
This game
Kouji Higashino wins
This is the worst
The worst
The camera is a little bit out of order.
It's okay if you just do the last one, but just a little bit.
Excuse me.
It's okay if you just do the last part of Yama-chan, but just a little bit.
I want to see the part where you can hit Yama-chan's pie again with the Gizu table.
Just the last part?
What?
That's not true!
You can't do that again.
That's the last scene.
Really?
That's not true.
I can't do that.
I have a question.
That's the last scene.
The scene where you go like this.
No, no, no.
Excuse me.
No, that's not it.
The last part of the tape is the part where the fire goes off.
And Yama-chan, the part where you fall is the part where you fall.
No, it's a little...
What's the problem?
The tape is not spinning at the end due to camera trouble.
Why?
That's impossible.
This is...
I don't know.
That's a little tough.
I don't know what to do with this.
No, it's not.
Where is it not spinning?
I got all the tape from half way that velocity.
Right.
She threw the tape from half way that velocity of her pie...
In half way what do you mean?
She didn't make any circle since she threw the pie away for иск?
She makes some circle, but her sometimes is jammed up somehow.
Some well Forming sensations in various electrical Contacts.
Nah, nah, nah, nah...
How long do you do circle?
About 5 minutes from the end of the video.
No, no!
I think it's about 5 minutes.
Yama-chan started and it took about half an hour.
That's tough.
Why didn't you call me halfway?
You should have stopped me halfway.
I'm sorry.
What?
Yes.
You can't even get a third of the money.
I'm sorry.
You've done the same thing over and over again!
Yes.
I'm sorry.
What are you going to do?
You can't do it again!
Yes.
What are you going to do with the shakuhou?
You can't do it again. What are you going to do?
I have a plan.
Yes.
What the hell is this?
Sorry.
You should have done something.
I want you to do something for me.
Well, anyway...
For example, in Higashino...
I want you to do something for me.
That's what I want.
I'm not sure if I can do it.
It's been a while since I've had a pin-up.
You can't do the story you were doing.
Senior.
I'm grateful for that.
Then, can you prepare a guest?
Excuse me.
Thank you.
Can you wait a moment?
I thought you were going to say, I'm sorry.
I was wondering why you weren't looking at the camera.
Hey, who are you talking to?
We'll be back and talk about the eastern story.
You've got your costumes ready, right?
Yes.
Thank you.
I wonder if it's a little too much.
I don't want to do it like this, but I wonder if it's a little too much.
I can't move.
I'll be here all the time.
Oh my god...
Let me explain to the viewers once again.
This time, Yamazaki was the star of the show.
But it was all a lie.
The battle with Yamazaki and the pie he brought out were all a prank to make Higashino do the Senor.
The tape didn't stop.
The story of Senor is about 16 years ago, the story of Higashino who was doing a lot of muscle-baka character at the time of his debut, and he played it with high tension.
What's wrong?
West!
I'm not feeling well!
Higashino decided to do a story related to it.
Check the content in the old video.
I was so happy.
Today, Higashino is going to do a story.
There is a little bit of a story boom in the world.
Even if you put a lot of effort into it, it's still a good story.
I think it would be good if I could do my best in a medium-sized place like this.
I think this would be a gold medal for comedy.
Oh, there's a lot of Kami-san from Enta.
I think I'm the type of person who can go out of the East.
There are already a lot of customers.
Then, the East will do the story.
I'm looking forward to it.
Let's listen to it.
Toh!
This is funny.
The tension is different from the other one.
Good evening.
I'm Senor.
Senor?
What's wrong with you, everyone?
You were so excited.
You're so mean!
Cheer up, Mr. Miyashita!
Today,
I have a lot of worries.
I want to solve them.
Please go out with me.
First, I'll give you my advice.
I respect you, Mr. Senor.
I hate music time.
That's because I'm always teased by girls.
How can I become a good singer like you?
I can eat poop, right?
It's a very difficult problem.
Then let's solve it.
You don't have to sing.
That's it.
Next.
I'm the same.
I'm a 14 year old pig.
I'm being teased at school.
I want to be a body like you, and be popular with girls.
How can I become that body? Please tell me.
Please give me your pen name.
The best pen name in the newspaper.
I got it.
Then today, to become this body like Senor,
I will teach you specially the shape up exercise.
Music start!
Raise your legs!
Next, bring the chair.
Put your hands on it.
Spread your legs.
And drop it.
Your face is...
Your legs are too long.
I'll give you.
I'll give it to you.
Wait, wait, wait.
Music stop!
Don't say anything about today!
It's fluffy.
I've seen it.
Yes.
Ai Hai?
What about the voice?
I don't know.
It's flying.
Rather than flying, it's like...
I can't speak.
You can't speak.
It's hot.
It's not a shock, it's like a mental pressure.
Ah, I see.
I understand.
I thought it was a prank.
Well, it was a prank.
It was a success.
What do you think is a success?
Well, that...
Don't be so mean!
No, I'm not!
We were just pranking Higashino, but in a way, the one who got the most pranked was the guest today.
What is this?
You're not like that!
If you want to be more beautiful, you should have come back to Senryo!
Wakana...
Say it!
I was scared of the fall.
Don't say such things.
But this is only in the exit.
From here, there are gold medals of laughter.
There are many places.
There is a god of entertainment.
I want you to go there.
Me?
I want you to do your best in the lottery.
Seriously?
You're going to make me do this?
I'm going to do this.
Look at me.
I can't help it if you say no.
Roll it more.
I can't help it.
How do you roll it?
This is wrong.
No, no.
Stop it!
What's your problem?
There's a good thing here.
You two are going in here.
It's because of the explosion.
You can't do that.
No no no no no.
You're going to blow up.
Stop it.
Stop it now.
It's different from DX.
DX?
I'm looking at DX a little bit.
It's getting really warm.
You can do it, right?
You can change it with your feelings.
We can change it.
Yes.
Then, you can change it.
Thank you.
I'm sorry again.
Oh my god!
You are so kind!
I can't believe it!
You nitwit!
DOUGHBUL!
Acting like a clown, sorry everyone
The M!PQUADcounty is from Asia
The YThese JiUamM öğ но is from Asia
répondbr Armor you can only see me
The M!PQUADcounty is from Asia
The YThese JiUammILLER is from Asia
get it?
As expected......
I love you, Mama.
There was something like that recently.
No, no, no.
When you do this kind of work, you often have to stop the passers-by in the location.
Yes, yes.
But there is also the opposite.
Can you stop them?
Tokyo has a lot of dramas, right?
I see.
Do you have any special moments that you want to share with us?
I haven't had a normal life yet.
Oh really?
I've seen you doing it there.
Like an AD.
I'm sorry, I'm a little...
At that time, I was so angry that I even opened the Thai government.
What?
It had nothing to do with me.
No, no, it had nothing to do with you.
You were the one who was in the middle of it.
It had nothing to do with me.
And the other day, I was a fool. I went to the Kinsa station and I was doing a location shoot.
I was doing my job, right?
And a woman from the A.D. told me to wait.
That was my second generation.
I told the car in front of me,
Excuse me, I'm sorry.
And then, the next one was this star, Matsumoto.
【Laughter】
He's just Hero tumbling down.
It's down and you're just acting like an idiot.
You wanted to see the cz fields, right?
You wanted to see them and And finally they were used in the place in front.
The horns flew...
【Laughter】
So that's not the case with this guy.
You're talking nonsense.
Yes, I'm the second generation.
You don't say anything to me.
You say sorry to the first generation.
You're an idiot.
When I get out of the car, I'm so excited.
I'm trying my best as a mother.
I'm in Tokyo now.
I don't know what to do.
Come on, come on.
I'm not angry.
Don't say that again!
I don't know!
I'm writing it!
You're really angry!
You're calm.
I'm angry.
Well, I tried my best to make you angry.
That's what makes you angry?
You're an idiot!
What's that?
Please say it!
You don't have anything to say?
I didn't see anything!
You're a beast!
I was waiting for you before, right?
I was, right?
I was waiting for you.
Yes.
I was just there, at the car that was waiting for me.
There was a boy there.
Like a ambulance.
I see.
No, no, no, don't stop, go!
Stop!
This is a bad situation!
I can't watch this!
I thought you were the head of the village, but you're acting like a dead man!
I don't understand what you're saying!
That's because my mother is in Tokyo!
I don't remember!
I was tickling you in the country, but in Tokyo I'm going to tickle you. I'm going to erase you.
I don't know.
I'm going to tickle you.
Well, well, I understand.
Please be careful about that.
I don't get sick of it.
When I get angry.
I don't see dogs or anything like that.
I don't really watch things like that.
That's interesting.
I'm not saying it's interesting.
I don't watch it.
What's interesting?
I'm not saying it's interesting.
You're trying to make me watch it, right?
Even with a hamster, you can do something like this, right?
What?
I know, I know.
I don't really watch those.
I watch more of the ones that are on the corner.
That's also...
This is...
Mom, I...
I can't read the lines.
It's the moment, now!
That's the end.