Yōkan no Kō
Yōkan usai wa nakayoshi ga
Itsumo futari de mitsu yōkan
Yōkan no dana
Yōkan no yome
Yoru wa kuriyōkan
Akaburi no
Kane motteru na
Akaburi no pōru wa omae ka kurabu no nee chan ka dōchikai
Goseien torimasu
Pōru no goseien
Kane motteru
Dōkai de no oasis desu kara
Pōru no goseien
Nakade isu aru janaisu ka
Nankara chair
Kasaari to kasanashi ga
Kasanashi no hou ga yasui n desu yo
Yappa kasari
Kasari no hou ga
Kasari de goseien
Pōru no ichimai
Nannimo kute nai no ichimai
Omae Daisuke Hanako no Hanako
Yakamashi wa
Pōru no ichimai
Tashikani ichimai
Nani iwarete goseien desu iwarete ai goseien
Eh goseien suno?
Maman tokai no oasis
Kōra itte shimaeru
Kisai na
Kitanai ne 3000 yen no parasol nashi no hou wa ne basho kimatterun desu yo
Parasol aru iwi yatto kocchi nan desu
Kocchi iwaretemu wakaranai
Kono 3000 yen to kono 5000 yen wa jitsu wa dekakute
3000 yen no parasol nashi no hou wa
Dandan taiyou ga ugokidasu to kage ni naru desu yo
So if you have a parasol you can stay in the sun for a long time.
I see.
But if you have a parasol you can stay in the sun for a long time.
So you don't know what it is.
What is a parasol?
I think you should move the chair.
No, you shouldn't.
The place is already decided.
If you move the chair, it will fly away.
It will fly away like this.
But you have 5,000 yen, right?
Yes, I do.
That's why I don't have that much.
It's the oasis of the city.
To be honest, I have money.
You have money?
I have a lot of money in my house.
What does it have to do with money?
I want to be a thief.
He is a fool.
I want you to take money from me.
That's what I think.
That's expensive.
Yes, it is.
Really?
I went to the pool and thought about it.
I thought that downtown was not a good place for children.
That's sad.
I've been thinking about it.
That's a lie.
What is it?
I think you're the one who...
Wait, wait.
I thought it was a picture of a car.
What is it?
It has nothing to do with it.
When I was a kid, I thought it was a picture of a car.
What is it?
It's a picture of a car.
It's a lie.
It was really amazing.
There were four boys in the pool.
Was he a good boy?
I don't know if he was a good boy.
He said,
Ma-chan, play with me.
He is a child with bad taste.
No, no, no.
I like children, too.
I asked him what he was doing.
He said,
I'll run away, so you just have to catch me.
I'll catch you.
He was screaming.
I'm sure it's a lie.
He was screaming, too.
It was too long, and he was becoming an old man.
I don't like it.
I don't know.
Well, it's okay.
Ha...
Huh?
He ran quite hard with his left foot.
I don't think he came down.
Now?
You can just step on it
Don't talk like that
It's disgusting
What are you talking about?
Kazumoto-san
Yes
Why do F1 racers
When they are in the pit and want to change tires
Don't they try to finish the race
They don't try to finish the race
That's right, when they are in the pit they just sit
They don't even want to get off
Isn't that fine?
Then you should have done it earlier
You should have done it earlier
Yes, yes
Ah, that's how it is
They work with their lives on the line
They are fighting in a world where they don't have a soul
In that kind of situation
There is a great sense of movement in their bodies
Do you understand?
Do you understand that?
If you don't understand then it's fine
I do understand
What are you talking about?
Ah, really?
If you don't understand that then I'll go on
Yes, yes
After all, their bodies are very hard
No matter what
Do you understand?
Yes
If you don't understand then I'll go on
After all, you can see that their claws are getting longer
That's because they have been running for weeks
No, no, they want to go, they want to go
What do you mean they want to go?
They want to work harder
They are being pushed into something amazing
Their claws and hair are getting longer
When they arrive they are getting longer
They are curious about that
So they go behind them and bite
So you shouldn't move too much
Let me say this clearly
I want to give them a little more time
I want to give them time
I want to give them a little bit of time to play
You should have told me when I read this
I'm listening
Are you going to end it?
Wait a minute
I understand
I'll say it next
Yes, yes
Matsumoto-san is good at fighting
I can say this
If a person who is beaten up like a piece of junk gets beaten up even more, how would you describe it?
A man, especially a man
You might see a man like that somewhere
But for me, it's my spirit
My spirit is something that exists for me
In words
I have seen a man who is beaten up like a piece of junk
I see
But normally when a man is beaten up like a piece of junk, he loses his spirit and stops
But in my case, I have more spirit than that
So even if I get flustered, I still go
I see
That's why I was beaten up like a piece of junk
That's why I have seen a man who is beaten up like a piece of junk
So how should I describe it?
You can say it
What?
So how should I describe it?
You can say it
You have to take a shit while you are talking
Please tell us
More than a piece of junk
More than a piece of junk?
Do you know what a piece of junk means?
Like a piece of organ
Yes, organ, like a face
That's what it means
It's more than that
More than that, it means
Acetate.
He's acting like he's acetate.
And on top of that...
There's more on top of that.
And on top of that, there's Leon.
I feel like I'm going to lose.
That's how it goes.
And on top of that, there's Polypillepillone.
And what's even worse is that...
In the morning, he's 20 and his face is 80.
I can't believe he's 80.
He's caught and beaten up.
And his face is 20 and his back is 80.
Humanity has a history of 4000 years.
There are still five different ways of swimming.
The only person who can think of the sixth way is Matsunosu.
Please, teach me.
What's a crawl?
Swimming backwards.
Butterfly.
Dog swimming.
There's one more.
Let's do this one too.
Are you going to show me?
Sure.
Stop that!
Let's go!
Are you ready?
On your mark, get set, go!
Here we go.
I'm being introduced.
Wait a minute.
Can you do this?
I'm not doing this for no reason.
Explain.
Look at this.
I'm sending the next water here.
What's happening to the legs in the water?
You were doing this.
It's like this.
I'm not swimming!
You just sent the next water.
I'm sending the next water here.
I'm walking, I'm not walking.
It's not floating. It's going into the water.
What do you mean by going into the water?
Water of the future.
Water of the future, water of the past.
It's amazing. Water of the future, water of the past.
You can breathe easily.
Is your face showing?
It's showing. What are you talking about?
If it's not showing, then you should say,
Water of the future, water of the past.
You shouldn't say that.
You should say that.
You shouldn't swim.
That's because you're strong in the sea.
Why?
You can't put your feet on the ground.
When you do this, you'll be surrounded by squids.
Water of the past, water of the future,
Water of the future, water of the past.
That's right.