We won! The losing team will be punished!
We did it!
It's cold here!
Only the winning team was given these clothes!
It's so warm!
But!
In this cold, such brave men came!
Over there! Look!
We won!
They are just idiots!
Cool!
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
Look at that rough wave!
From now on, you guys will head towards that rough wave!
Okay?
Okay.
We won!
It doesn't matter if it's cold!
You guys are in the middle of the ocean!
When you come up, something is waiting for you!
Put your energy into it!
Are you ready?
Are you okay?
Okay, if I shoot, you will follow me!
Let's go!
You are the best!
I'm sorry!
Let's go!
It hurts!
My body hurts!
Let's go!
Sir!
Yes?
Hey!
Bring me that bag!
Let's go!
Moriyasu!
Yes?
Put this on!
You are going to swim in the sea of monsters!
Let's go!
Sir!
Sir, bring this!
Masumoto, bring this!
Bring this!
What are you doing?
I'm sorry!
Let's go!
I really worked hard today.
I don't know what to say.
I'm really sorry to have kept you waiting.
Today, I really...
Wow!
What's with your face?
You see...
I'm really tired today.
I'm exhausted.
You have a companion.
So when I'm tired,
no matter what I do, my face dies.
That's why it's like this.
When I'm tired,
I do my make-up like this.
That's how I show it.
But your face says you're tired.
My head goes bang, bang.
Why?
Because of what I did.
I jumped in.
It was really cold.
When I got tired,
I screamed.
I couldn't scream because it was cold.
I've never done it before because it was cold.
When I screamed,
my head went bang, bang.
My head went bang, bang.
You were the loudest.
Well, that's because I'm a stage performer.
It doesn't matter.
You were the loudest when 10 people came in.
What?
I was in the microwave that day.
It was really cold.
That's how cold my body was.
I'm tired today.
I'm sorry I can't talk.
That's that.
The opening is over.
It doesn't matter.
I'll talk about the penalty game when I watch the VTR.
You did it last week.
He's taking a break.
That's it.
You're not a backup.
If you take a break with such a simple feeling,
I can't do it.
It was hard.
That's a lie.
If you have a voice, you can come.
I couldn't come.
I'm sure I'll come.
I'm going to pee.
I walked a step.
It was a pee that was about to come out.
That's not good.
I'm going to pee while I'm on the show.
Who's going to blame you?
You're the best.
I'm going to pee while I'm on the show.
I had a fever.
It's not that bad.
I'm going to take a break.
I'm told that.
What's your fever?
30.
Wait a minute.
You should have started at 40.
I'm going to pee while I'm on the show.
I can't do it.
I couldn't do it.
I'm sure you can.
If you walk, you'll pee.
What are you going to do?
Don't you have a family?
Use that.
I didn't pee on that day.
You can't do that.
If you pee all the time, you can't do it.
I don't have a family.
I was surprised.
It's a tough situation.
I think.
I played a penalty game today.
The baseball game is over.
It's too early to play a penalty game.
I'm going to take a break.
I want to play something soon.
I can't forget today's frustration.
Do you want to play the second round of sports?
Gyo-san, you've lost many times in the opening, but it's not a punishment game.
That's right, that's right.
All the games I won were just a game in the opening.
I didn't play it as a punishment game.
That's right.
You played billiards, too.
I lost that time, too.
You can't play billiards, can you?
No, if I played it once.
What?
The first time, it started when I was in Gaki no Sky.
There's no second time in this program.
There was one time, right?
Shut up, you guys!
I don't care if you play it or not.
If you don't laugh there, you'll be punished at least once.
Then you'll probably be dragged around.
I want to see that kind of audience once.
Oh, really.
It's funny, isn't it?
You bought it once.
That's right.
Let's do something again.
Really?
Yeah.
Do something.
What do you want to do?
I want to do judo.
Oh, let's do it, let's do it, let's do it.
Sounds fun.
Really?
Yeah.
Let's really do it.
Yeah, let's do it, let's do it.
It's judo, right?
This is really really good.
I got it.
I got it, I got it.
Let's do it, let's do it, let's do it.
Oh my, oh my, oh my, oh my, oh my.
You know the greatness of my judo, don't you?
No, I don't know if I know it or not, but it looks interesting.
You're still doing a draft.
I'm saying this, but I can't do a cat in the air three times in a row.
That's not Nyanco Sensei.
Then I'll take you up there once.
You'd better not do that, really.
No, let's do it.
Let's do it.
What?
Try it on.
You know.
You're still doing a draft.
You're dirty.
What's dirty?
You didn't resist at all.
You're really.
It's dirty, so throw it to me, throw it to me.
I'm tired, and I'm called Matsumoto with a hard-wired.
What kind of?
I can't throw it, I'm good at holding it.
Hold it, hold it, hold it.
What kind of?
I'm just holding it.
I can't get this up.
You're standing up right now.
That's not the main show.
Then solidify it properly.
I'll solidify it.
Are you ready?
Shut up!
Don't change the picture!
What do you mean, don't change the picture?
Shut up!
Judo is not interesting at all.
Barbell.
What is a barbell?
I know what a barbell is.
I like barbells.
I like the enthusiasm of the barbell.
Ha!
That's why I said ha! barbell.
It's okay.
Let's fight.
If you lose, you'll get a little punishment.
What kind of punishment?
That's amazing.
No, you know what?
If you lose, you'll get punished.
I'll have to do something fun.
The loser goes to the SM club.
If you win, you can lose.
What are you talking about?
I'll beat you up.
I'm not interested.
What are you talking about?
I don't know.
I can't beat you up.
I'm embarrassed.
You're a fool!
You're a fool.
I heard about a girl who was working at the SM club.
You're working?
What is it?
I've done it once.
I'm talking to a girl who's really been working.
What is it?
I heard there are a lot of perverted men coming to the SM club.
I heard they eat poop.
That's a scandal.
They want to take a dump.
They eat poop under the bed.
You go to the toilet?
And then, Owarotan, Owarotan brought the poop to the toilet and told me to put it here.
He said that he would bring the poop to the toilet in a different state.
He said that he would put it in the refrigerator at home.
He said that he would clean it up again when it was dirty.
Honemata!
Hello.
You're not an amateur today, are you?
You're not an amateur, so you should talk more.
What's your name?
I'm Aizawa Kaori.
What are you looking at?
I'm looking at...
I'm looking at you.
You're not a man!
Oh, it came out again.
You're a pro today.
Yes.
Thank you very much.
Chichikuri Manbo-san.
Good evening, Machiyama-chan.
I always want to quit smoking, but I can't.
Machiyama-chan, you smoke, but have you ever thought of quitting?
Have I ever thought of quitting?
Me?
No, I've never thought of quitting.
You quit when you have a cold or a sore throat, right?
No, I don't quit.
I've decided to quit once and I'll keep doing it until the end.
No, you just quit because you think it's useless.
I've decided to quit once.
No, I'll definitely quit.
But recently, smoking is...
Smoking is amazing, isn't it?
That's strange, isn't it?
You don't need to smoke or anything like that.
But there are people who smoke on the Shinkansen, too.
That's why.
The feeling of having to put up with smoking for an hour and the feeling of not wanting to smoke while sitting next to you.
Which one is bigger?
That's because the person who can put up with smoking is much bigger.
I wonder if I can cry about that.
It's about the same.
I get angry.
I want to smoke, but I don't know why I don't smoke.
That's not true.
And even if you don't smoke, you might get cancer just sitting next to you.
I wonder if it's better to smoke that kind of thing.
I'm putting my life on the line to smoke.
I don't have the right to be told off by you guys.
You're putting your life on the line just to smoke.
That's true.
I only smoke.
What do you hate?
I hate natto.
I eat natto.
I'm sitting next to people and eating natto.
I don't want that.
I don't care if there's a gold natto.
Why is gold the only thing I smoke?
If you smoke, it's the same as smoking.
Natto doesn't harm you if you eat it sitting next to you.
Don't be silly.
I'm going to sit next to you.
I'm going to sit next to you a little bit.
Today's cap is sticky.
That's not true.
I don't care about your body.
I don't like it.
It's disgusting.
I don't care if it's disgusting.
Why am I getting angry?
Lastly, a girl from Ibaraki Prefecture.
I've been thinking a lot lately.
Women are not faces.
Even if you say it's true, it's unfair that you can only deal with beautiful women.
Because the first impression is the face.
The assistants on this show are all beautiful.
The ugly ones are useless anyway.
The ugly ones are women.
I want to be noticed.
Please make a place where girls like me can be active.
What kind of place do you want me to do?
It doesn't matter if you're ugly.
I want you to be on TV as an assistant.
I don't care.
You, you, you.
Don't say it over and over again.
People who have been watching this show for a long time.
I went home today.
Look at all the places where the assistants came out.
This guy is completely different depending on his face.
If an ugly girl comes out, he can't talk.
That's you, isn't it?
Don't say such a thing.
What do you think?
It's okay to use it.
If you want to do it.
What kind of personality and face do you want?
I don't know.
What do you mean you don't know?
I don't know if you're talking.
If it's beautiful, it's annoying.
If it's beautiful and annoying, I won't talk.
The cheeky guy just talks and gets angry.
If that's the case, it's a little disappointing, but it's quite interesting.
I don't know if it's better to talk or not.
For example, you can have fun while drinking.
This guy, Hamada Masatoshi.
It's a strategy to increase the number of fans even a little bit.
A person.
A person is like Momoko with high heels.
I don't know.
I'm Momoko.
That's what happens when I drink. It doesn't matter if it's beautiful or ugly.
But recently, cute girls have a better personality.
Ugly girls have a bad personality these days.
Really?
Cute girls have a bad personality.
I think cute girls have a better personality.
It's a truth, isn't it?
It's like I'm a woman critic.
I don't know.
I'm like a virgin.
I'm like a demon.
How many people do you think I've experienced?
Well, a hundred is useless.
Answer me.
What about me?
I'm saying a hundred, but what about Chuck?
How many people do you think I've experienced?
I don't know.
Don't lie to me.
I think I've experienced five people.
You must be lying.
Did you see it?
Did you see the scene?
That's not true.
Then what about you?
What?
How many people do you think I've experienced?
How many people do I have?
You're the only one.
How many people do you think I've experienced?
I'm not good at imitating women.
I love each of them very much.
How many people do you think I've experienced?
I'm sorry if I said something wrong.
How do you want to express it?
A woman you love.
That's like a title of a book.
How many women have been through your life?
You're not a woman, but you've been through it.
A woman who has been through my life.
You're crazy.
I get it.
How many women have been through your life?
A woman who has been through my life.
How many women have been through my life?
Let's go home.
I did it alone the other day, so I don't have the right to take a break.
I don't have the right to take a break.
Are you downtown?
I'm not downtown.
What are you?
I'm a human being.
Good morning.
Did you sleep well today?
Yes.
It was cold, wasn't it?
This Saturday, February 23rd.
I haven't decided on the place yet.
I'd like you to make a reservation.
I'd like you to meet a young man.
Who decided that?
Who do you think is young?
A cheap vacancy.
February 23rd.
I'd like you to meet a young man.
Who do you think is young?
Some of them are young!
Some of them are not.
Both of them.
Let's invite an assistant.
I'm not playing.
Not many.
If you want to be an assistant, you have to take a picture with the director, and the rest is all the same, so please take a picture of Akina gradually.
I'm waiting for you.
So, I'm going to use Akina gradually, so please look forward to next week.
Goodbye.
I'm going to do my best.
It's not an emoji.
It's an emoji.