The Heipo of the world, Saito Toshihiko
A man of miracle who went up to the chief director of Gaki no Tsukai
The first opponent is the popular idol, Amihama Naoto
The Heipo who was able to be alone with a personality problem
It was thought to be a happy goal
Amihama's passionate declaration
The Heipo of the world, the second time in a row
Mr. Ochi, you came again
It's been a long time
It's not something I do twice
I was about to do well
The next day or the next day's newspaper
I was already engaged
I was surprised
The girl I brought today
Please
If you don't have more fun, the girl
There are various specialties today
I'm telling you to take out everything you have
If you don't do that, you won't have fun
Please introduce the boy
Bon
This is my Aho Bon
It's been a long time
Saito Toshihide
Toritsu Mita High School
Where is it?
I'm in college
In college?
Height 162 cm
I think this is a lie
This is also perfect
I'm such a Toshihide
Well, today
Here is the girl I prepared
This is also good
Harakumiko
The gravure queen Harakumiko
With her mature adult charm
A woman who captivates male fans all over the country
To be honest, it was Amihama last time
How is it
Which one are you?
Actually, I like Hara-san
I have to send you a signal from here today
There was a signal last time
I'm shy, so I don't do anything
I did a lot last time
This time, I'm wearing this shibire fugu
I wear it to my penis
While I'm talking
Don't be bored
I thought it was like this
Oh, it's him
Who is it?
It's a secret
This program is provided by the sponsor you are watching
Don't be nervous
Be calm
Hello
Please come in
Excuse me
This is my Kumiko
Nice to meet you
I'm Harakumiko
Well, let's do it
Is it in?
Yes
Kumiko, please eat
Thank you
I'm nervous
Wait a minute
Wait a minute, Tojita-san
I came to see Kumiko
What are you talking about?
It's better to be a woman
I'm an old lady
Old lady?
Well, let's eat
Thank you
Cheers
Isn't it real?
When I drink this
It reminds me of my childhood
How is Kumiko now?
Don't you have a boyfriend?
Do you have a boyfriend?
What?
What are you talking about?
I thought you were talking about a pig
I don't have a boyfriend
You don't have a boyfriend?
That's good
Well, let's eat
Kumiko, please drink with me
Please drink with me
I don't drink
What?
Kumiko is drinking with me
Here you are
Please drink with me
My taste has changed
Please
You are a crazy old lady
Toshihide-san is very talented
He can do a lot of things
I have a lot of things to do
I'll prepare a little
I'm sorry
Excuse me
You
Are you going home?
Are you stupid?
I want a manly person
What are you doing?
Toshihide-san
You are the president of Scoville today
That's great
What's wrong with your wife?
What are we?
I didn't notice
It has nothing to do with you
We are in the back room
Let's talk together
I've been a big fan for a long time
I'm sorry
It's okay
I brought this today
If you don't mind, I'd like you to sign it
This again
This is a photo book
Thank you very much
I don't like this kind of stuff
I have a request
I've been a fan for a long time
I'd be happy if you could dance a song
You mean together?
It's like a team
Heipo-san is dancing
It's a dance
I can't dance if I don't stand up
I'm sorry
A little more
That's good
I'll move a little
Please turn your hand
That's good
What are you looking at?
It was a dream
Just a little more
What are you looking at?
It's been a long time since we met
I'd like to give you a present
I have something for you
Thank you very much
What is it?
This is a ring
I made it
What kind of ring is it?
No way
It's a present
I can't hold it
I have my own ring
Why?
Thank you
Did you put it there?
I'm not good at shaking
I don't know how to do it
I'm not good at it
I'm good at it
That's good
I prepared it for you
I gave it to you
I'll make you feel good
I'm not good at it
Don't step on it
Please lie down here
It's okay
Can I lie down?
Don't say that
I'll give you a shoulder massage
Let's massage
It's okay
That's good
Wow
I'll give you a massage
What are you doing?
You have to apologize
He came here
I wanted to sing
I'm going to stop the song
It was hard
I thought you were going to sing
I'm still in the first place
I don't know
I was really surprised
That's okay
Listen to me
There are really ugly men
There are a lot of them
No, I have a girl's bag
She's ugly
She walks like this
She's a go-go girl
The ugly man walks like this
He opens the door
He walks like this
The ugly man walks like this
I want to say thank you
Thank you for accepting this ugly woman
Don't talk
Hold her tight
I was just looking at her like this
I was happy
That's good
It's getting harder to play
Why is that?
I don't like it
Do you know that Matsumoto was arrested?
Yes
On the radio, Matsumoto was arrested
I'm sorry
This is so rude
I can't do what I want
This is the treasure of the country
I've been having a hard time
Really?
I feel sorry for her
That's what it means
I'm sorry
What have you been up to lately?
You haven't been out at all
I haven't been out for two months
I don't know what to say
I don't like it when it's not sunny
That's right
The weather is bad
I have something to say
That's a nice bath
Really?
Thank you
Wait
Who are you?
Come here
Don't write it
What is it?
If you look for it, you can make a movie
What are you looking for?
Don't wrap it up
What?
I've been thinking
Survival
Please do it
Alone
I want to go to a jungle
Go
I'm thinking of survival
I don't have a day off
Let's do it
Thank you
Why are you laughing?
Let's do it
What is the muscle behind a dog or a cat?
What is it for?
Please tell us
Isn't it a cushion?
I've heard of it
It's a cushion
There are two reasons
First, it doesn't hurt when you buy it on the floor
Also, I think the muscle is just sticking out
That's a big mistake
It goes like this
What?
Like this
It's round
It's like a roller
Of course
It goes like this
I've never seen a cat move that fast
If you hold a dog like this
It goes like this
It's like a roller coaster
If you hold it like this
It goes like this
It's amazing
What?
You can't lie like that
It's not a cat
When I was a high school student
I lied to Nagata
I lied that I had a cat
That's a good word
That's rude
It's really rude
I don't lie
It's a lie
Do you have a strong rock-paper-scissors?
I'm strong but I'm weak
I think I'll never lose
Then try it
It's fine
If I win 5 times, there's something
If there's nothing, I won't move
What do you mean?
If there's no reward, I won't do it
I need a lot of power
You need a lot of power
What do you mean?
You wanted to say something
What do you want?
200 yen
Don't say that in the bath
You should say it
You should say it between a big bath and a small bath
I'm tired
Then say it at 100,000 yen
I'll say it
100,000 yen
Check with Suga
Otherwise I'll give you power
With Suga?
You'll definitely lose
Rock, paper, scissors
When you said rock, I saw all your data
I got it
Rock, paper, scissors
What was that?
Can you do it like a prank?
First, I can't fly
Nothing will happen
That's all
If there is a principal like you
Students won't have fun at all
Nothing will happen
First, can you fly?
Can you fly?
Can you fly anytime?
Fly
Listen to my story until the end
If I fly to the edge of the ground, the water will open
Fly
If I fly now, the water will open
That's good
Are you stupid?
What will you do if the water stops?
That's me
If I fly, the water will open
Of course
You fly on the ground to open the water
How far can you fly?
Can you fly like this?
No, more
Like this?
No, like this?
Can you put a stick in my hand?
I can't do it
You fly like this?
You are stupid
No, like this
I don't understand
When I want to fly
I go like this
Last year
Last year?
I was watching TV at home
The water was floating
Next is a mountain
No
Next is a bye-bye game
What is a bye-bye game?
How far can you fly?
You fly like this
Why is it a bye-bye game?
I don't know. I was surprised at first.
It's hard when you die.
Why?
You're not strong.
My son was flying.
So your father was flying?
He found out.
What are you talking about?
You talk too much.
Tell me how to escape when you're in the basement.
Even now, there are machines and things like that, right?
Yes, there are.
What kind of things are there?
For example, if you get out of the line, you'll be rich.
I don't think that makes sense.
Really?
It doesn't make sense.
Why? It makes a lot of noise.
It makes a lot of noise.
If it makes a lot of noise, you won't be able to hear it.
The other day, when I played with Hatsune Miku in the fire...
It wasn't a fire.
What are you talking about?
What was it?
I got it. It was a thief.
It was a thief.
Right?
What was it?
What? I forgot.
It's true.
It's a nose voice.
The nose won't stop.
Try it.
It sounds like Dai-chan.
What are you doing?
I'm really sorry.
It wasn't this many.
The man gets even angrier.
I was wondering what he was doing.
He was using a stun gun.
That's not good.
It's the opposite effect.
Really?
If you get a cold, it means you've got a cold.
No, no, no.
I wouldn't get up if I got killed.
Please tell me what it's for.
What?
The gun.
It's really good for you.
Really?
You can use it right after you get home.
Anyone can use it?
After you get home, the man will attack you.
You'll be fine today.
No!
Don't say that!
You won't be able to break it today.
Oh!
I'm going to the theater!
If the man attacks you, you won't resist.
I won't?
You won't resist.
What if he takes you and tells you to do this?
I'll tell him to give me the gun.
What are you talking about?
I'll answer his needs.
You can't answer his needs!
He's not in the theater.
I'm really sorry.
Today...
That happens sometimes.
How did you figure it out?
It was pretty fast.
It was fast, right?
It was pretty quick.
It was quick, right?
But it can't be helped.
It was like a stung by a stun gun.
It was too quick!