The professional baseball is about to start.
We're going to play first.
Is the team already decided?
Yes, it's already decided.
This is the match team.
I'm looking forward to this pure white uniform.
The problem is this guy.
Don't push your glasses.
This is the match team.
There are a lot of otaku teams that don't look red.
What are you talking about?
You guys are like that too.
I'm like this.
What are you talking about?
It's a pure white uniform.
I'm selling it like that.
Why is that?
I'm a little...
Mario is like a mushroom.
This guy is always in my team.
I don't know why.
I didn't get beaten up today.
It's like Irochin's sword.
What is this?
It's a baseball game, so we have a referee.
Referee, please.
Takahashi will be the referee.
Please explain the rules.
As long as the ball doesn't fall on the ground, it's out.
That's out.
There's no passing.
You have to give it back to the referee.
You're doing a good job.
I'm just changing my talent.
It's a baseball game, so we have a referee.
Please explain the rules.
As long as the ball doesn't fall on the ground, it's out.
There's no passing.
You have to give it back to the referee.
You're doing a good job.
I'm just changing my talent.
Do your best.
It's out.
What were you thinking?
What are you doing?
It's okay.
It's in.
Referee.
What?
You're cheating.
You just hit me.
Referee.
Two strikes.
You're cheating.
You were just using your arms.
I'm going to die.
Ouch.
You're cheating.
You were just using your arms.
It's out.
You should hit the bottom.
He's a young man.
It's out.
Wait a minute.
He's on your team, right?
Give it to him.
It's broken.
It's not a matter of the bat. It's a matter of the captain.
It's a matter of the bat.
Jump!
The two teams are divided by 11 to 11.
I was assigned to the captain of the team.
Captain!
I didn't know that.
Please say something to the captain.
Thank you for your hard work.
The captain is in a bad mood.
He is such a person.
He is laughing a little here.
When he was sulking, he took off his shirt.
I don't know.
Today is good.
I'm not wearing a jacket.
I decided to wear a jacket.
Oh, you decided on your own?
Yes, I did.
Oh, I see.
There's a man in there, too.
That's right.
Right?
There's a man in there, too.
It'd be nice if there was something in here.
That's right.
Just a little kid.
Um...
The population table...
Is the population table in Tokyo?
It is.
Oh, I see. That's right.
I have to do that, too.
Um...
There's a lot of annoying things.
Like, there's a population table.
When you buy something.
You have to go home and get it.
That's right. That's how it is with me.
So if your passport runs out,
you have to go to Kobe.
That's right.
It's annoying.
And what's annoying is the videotape.
Um...
Why can't you get it at the office?
There's a lot of people who don't pay at the office.
They don't pay.
So...
Um...
What are you talking about?
You're so fast.
No.
The driver's license...
You're so fast.
What do you call it?
You still have your driver's license,
but you're still driving.
No, no, no.
That's amazing.
The driver's license is the best proof of military service.
Right?
Yes, yes.
There's a reason for that in your neighborhood.
That's right.
At that time, you were the chief of the police.
That's no good.
I don't live there.
You're angry, aren't you?
I'm already on fire.
You're already on fire.
You have a driver's license.
I have a driver's license.
That's weird.
You're so fast.
You have a driver's license.
Why?
If the other person is a yakuza,
why can't I drive?
Because I'm scared.
That's weird.
You're asking for proof of living there.
That's right.
That's why you go to a video store, right?
You go in and check other videos.
You haven't become a member yet,
but you check to see how much stuff there is.
That's right.
You look at it and then...
Especially, you go to a video store centered around adults.
If there are a lot of adults,
you think you'll become a member here when it's sunny.
That's right.
The clerk says,
Oh, it's Machan. Please sign it.
Oh, that's fine.
You sign it.
I want to become a member.
Oh, really?
Do you have a driver's license?
If you put it out, it's a ticket to Hyogo.
That's right.
It's no good.
Don't lie to me like that.
You said it was Machan.
You don't have to hide or run away.
Suddenly, the relationship gets weird.
That's true.
You're angry, aren't you?
I'm angry.
You didn't even sign it.
And then...
There's a 24-hour video store.
If you say 24 hours, you can go there at any time.
That's right.
You don't have to say anything.
Everyone knows.
When I went in there,
there were a lot of adults again.
There was an adult video that I really wanted to borrow.
I didn't put it anywhere.
It was there.
I really wanted to become a member.
I didn't go there directly.
I went to Yamazaki.
I was told it wasn't good.
Yamazaki lives in Kyoto.
It's not good even in Kyoto.
I live in the neighborhood, so I can't borrow it.
I looked for some people.
I wanted to borrow it on that day.
I wanted to see it 100%.
I thought I'd pull it up today.
I went home.
When I got to the apartment that day,
I asked them to make me a disciple.
I didn't have a disciple, so I couldn't do it.
I wrote a letter and asked them to call me.
I looked at it.
This is it.
If I had it, I'd call you.
I just wanted to borrow your video.
I still have a letter in my bag.
You don't trust humans, do you?
I went in and looked at it.
I didn't look at it.
I went to the counter first.
I went in and looked at it.
I said,
You're a nasty person.
Humans are cold.
I used to be like that in Osaka, too.
With a girl, you know,
Well, it was around the time of the year.
And then my pussy-chan would say...
Your pussy?
No way!
Ah, your pussy-chan!
Yeah, my pussy-chan.
I had to wear rubber gloves.
That's fine, isn't it?
I didn't have any!
I couldn't help it.
So I went out to the hotel.
I was walking all the way.
I couldn't stop.
You wanted to do it, didn't you?
I was walking a little, and there was a hotel.
I couldn't help it, so I went into the hotel by myself.
And the old lady said,
Do you want to stay overnight?
So I said,
Ah, your pussy-chan!
I'm sorry, old lady, but...
Can't you sell it to me?
It's changed.
I can't do that.
In the United States,
I was caught by a serial killer.
What kind of killer are you talking about?
He's a lolicon.
That's why he's after a boy in kindergarten.
A boy in kindergarten?
What are you going to do with that?
I don't know.
It hurts, old man, it hurts.
I can't stand it.
I can't stand that voice.
It hurts, old man.
Stop it.
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about a foreign country.
I'm talking about the United States.
You have a lot of imagination.
You're cool.
Hey!
I think more than I think.
That's weird.
It's scary, it's scary.
Let's get rid of it.
Get rid of it.
Why is the girl in Juliana dancing with wings?
She's not doing it.
She's a girl, but she doesn't complain about being cheated on her way home.
That's right.
Don't you think?
She's walking in that outfit on her way home.
She's being cheated on.
A cow is walking with iron plate and grilled meat sauce.
She's being eaten.
She's saying, ask me.
That's right.
It's terrible.
No, no, no, no, no.
That's not terrible.
That atmosphere, that lighting, that excitement, it looks good.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
That's right.
If you look at each one of them, it's like, wow.
If you look at each one of them, it's not a big deal.
That's right.
That's true.
It's the horror of the group.
If you're dressed like this in a group,
If a high school student is wearing a sailor suit and there are about 10 people walking around,
I think they're getting along well.
I want to be surrounded.
But if you look at each one of them,
If you look at each one of them, it's not a big deal.
That's right.
That's true.
What is the sign of a celebrity for?
Has anyone ever had one before?
I don't have one.
But sometimes I can't get it.
If there's a Shinkansen or something,
They say, sign it for me.
It's a habit to say, sign it for me.
If you're staying at a hotel and you ask for it,
They say, sign it for me.
I'm sorry.
I've never seen you with such a red face.
That's a bad idea.
You say it and then you say,
I'm sorry.
I've never seen you with such a red face.
The Shinkansen.
The other day, a boy from a school went back to Osaka.
He said, sign it for me, and I fell asleep.
And he came to me.
I said, I'm sorry.
He said, I'm sorry.
He said, I have an exam today.
Why did you do that?
If you say something like that,
I'm sure you'll get it.
I said, I have an exam today.
So what?
I can't do that.
It's not related at all.
It's not like I'm trying to get something on my birthday or exam.
It's strange.
It's like the last trump card.
If you get it, they'll do it for you.
It's all about timing.
Right.
It's not like I always get 1,000 yen.
It's all about timing.
I always leave early in the morning.
I get up early in the morning and go home late.
They ask me to come home and sign.
That's how it is.
I'm sorry.
That's true.
Also, in letters,
I have to carry my luggage.
I have to say thank you.
That's the end of it.
My hands are full.
I have to bring cigarettes.
I can't do that.
I can't even do that.
I have to leave cigarettes here.
Okay.
I can't do that with one cigarette.
I can't do that.
I'll have to get more cigarettes every day.
I can't believe this.
There are 3 or 4 packs of cigarettes.
It's terrible.
Hey!
I can't agree with that.
The other day, I was listening to Mr. Imada's radio.
Me, Matsumoto-san, and Ritton Chosadan, who are young people, were at a pizza restaurant in Osaka.
We were drinking tea, and we were told by the Osaka team to come out later.
When we went outside, there were about 20 people on the team.
There were about 20 people on the team?
There were about 20 people on the team.
At that time, Matsumoto-san thought that he couldn't do it if he hit him from a talent.
He told the people on the team to hit him quickly.
That was amazing.
You're scaring me.
What are you doing?
You're doing something bad, but you're telling me to hit you quickly.
You shouldn't think about that.
If you hit me first, the director of the next day...
I didn't hit you. I didn't do anything.
Why did you hit me?
I didn't do anything.
He didn't do anything, but he told me to come out.
That's why I said, what are you doing?
He said, what am I doing?
He said, what are you doing?
I thought I had to hit him.
What are you doing?
He said that.
He didn't say anything.
He said it himself.
He's the leader.
I'll hit you.
What are you doing?
I'm just kidding.
There was a 45... what are you doing?
How did you evolve from 45?
I had to protect the young people.
That's why I said, hit me.
What are you doing?
But if you hit me, I'll make it double.
Say it.
I don't want to say this on TV, but my special move is a cross counter.
If the opponent doesn't hit me, I can't use that move.
Because it's a cross counter.
I'll use the opponent's hand to do this.
That's right.
But he can't use his hand.
Because I'm big.
Wait a minute.
Do you understand if it's a flag?
No, I'm big.
I didn't say anything.
As a human being, I have a deep feeling.
I feel like I'm being beaten up.
There are a lot of people who want to brag about hitting a comedian.
I'm sure there are.
I'll tell you.
But I can't be proud of it.