This way, please.
All of a sudden?
I'm sorry.
Please explain the situation.
Today, the two of you are always working hard.
We're working hard.
In the sense that we're trying to get rid of the loan...
Sorry.
I want to be in the middle.
In the sense that we're trying to get rid of the loan...
Sorry.
We've already prepared the inn.
Really?
Yes.
Please have fun today.
No, not this way.
This way.
Oh, this way.
Can you take me there?
What? You're going to pick me up?
You're going to pick me up?
Yes.
Mr. Wataru is here.
This is amazing.
This is nice.
Yes.
Isn't it nice?
We've prepared all the food in Edo.
All the food in Edo?
Yes, we've prepared all the food in front of Edo.
Thank you very much.
Please have a drink.
How did you do today?
Not bad.
This is nice.
We'll be moving soon.
Is that so?
This is the first time we've been on a boat like this.
Isn't it?
I'm sure it is.
But, we're not getting any laughter.
It's not funny when we're talking.
Yes, you're right.
We're not funny.
It's fine.
Please wait a little.
Please take a look.
It's very beautiful.
Take it off.
This program is brought to you by the following sponsors.
If you're doing something like Taiko Moji, you don't have any talent.
Do you want to do it?
Please do it.
This is Entakinawa.
Please watch my performance.
Yama-chan!
Gag!
Yes, I'm on a yacht in the world.
It's so cold.
We've arrived at the point.
Here?
Yes.
This is Entakinawa.
This way.
What?
Why are you hiding your face?
I'm not hiding my face.
Are you serious?
Yes, I'm serious.
Oh, I see.
Can I go?
Yes, you can.
I'm looking forward to it.
Can I say anything?
Anything is fine.
Girls!
I love you!
Excuse me.
I'm going to practice with this on.
Why are you all bending your back?
What is that old lady with glasses?
She looks like an educator.
Is she an educator?
Oh, I see.
She's an old lady.
I'm Aoi.
I still like you.
What's your name?
I'm Aoi.
I'm Satsuki.
I'm Yayoi.
I'm Misetsu.
I'm Koume.
I'm Okamoto.
I'm Mameyako.
Forget about Mameyako.
Some of the baseball members like her are very good at baseball.
You don't need to say that...
I see.
You're so good at this!
Is it fun?
This person is...
Aoi-san
Aoi-san, don't be shy
It's your first time but do you want to try?
I don't know
That's all
Thank you
What?
That's all
Thank you
I got carried away
That's all
From now on, we will see the performance of Mameyakko-san who has been doing this for a long time
What? This old lady has been doing this for a long time
Mameyakko-san has been doing this for a long time
This guy, wait a minute
Hit him
Please wait
I'm sorry
Seriously
Scary
Huh?
I'm Daigyu Suga!
Daigyu Suga!
You're so ugly!
You're so scary!
So scary!
Daigyu Suga!
You're so ugly!
Hey!
What's up?
You're so annoying.
By the way, you guys...
Yes?
I've been watching you guys for a while.
You're so disgusting!
He's angry.
You can't even do the Shachi-hoko.
I'll show you the real Shachi-hoko.
This is good.
That's good.
You have to show us.
You've come this far.
You have to show us that you're different from these people.
Daigyu Suga.
The one and only Shachi-hoko.
You're so disgusting!
Look!
What are you doing?
Shachi-hoko
Brother!
You're the best!
Why are you so loud?
The best Shachi-hoko, Daigyu Suga!
Why are you looking at me like that?
Daigyu Suga!
You're disgusting!
That's enough.
Daigyu Suga
We don't have much time today.
We have time, but you don't have to go home.
We're pushing the time.
When the time comes, you can go home.
I'll talk to you on the bike.
It's not like that.
What are you talking about?
What should we do?
We're doing this show once a week, right?
There's no such thing as an interesting happening in a week.
There's no such thing.
There's a lot of small things.
The other day, the day before yesterday,
there was a crow in the house.
There was a crow.
When I hit the crow,
the machine couldn't catch it.
When I looked at it, it only had a crow's face.
It was cute.
I thought there was a crow somewhere.
It had a bulging butt.
When I touched it with a tissue,
it had a different face.
It was sitting like this.
What's so interesting about this story?
It's not interesting, is it?
But that's how it is in a week.
It's not like that, is it?
It's not like that.
If you put on a lot of color, it's even worse.
It's even worse.
It's like you're trying to make people laugh.
I don't like that.
I'm cold myself.
So I say what I want to say.
That's how it is.
Thank you very much.
I'm going to the commercial.
That's fast.
Do you know how hard this is?
We've been doing this for six years.
Don't cry.
Say something.
Something has changed.
That's what I was looking for.
There's a lot of change.
That's why.
We've only done 17 episodes.
We're all the same.
That's right.
You should go out to a lot of places.
You should be in a fashionable relationship.
Are you fashionable?
I'm not like this.
I'm just like this.
Don't say that.
If you're doing it with the same people, you should copy me.
You're the same.
But...
But what?
There aren't a lot of people who want to go out.
You have a lot of experience.
I want to go out a lot.
I want to go out to a lot of businesses.
Do you want to go out?
What?
Do you want to go out to a lot of businesses?
No, I don't want to go out.
Do you want to go out?
No.
What are you doing?
Just a little bit.
Why?
Are you stupid?
No, really.
You should go out.
No, I don't want to go out.
You should go out with me.
What do you want to go out?
I want to get a lot of prizes.
Why?
I don't want to go out.
I want to go out to a lot of places.
Why?
I want to get a lot of prizes.
But...
I want to go out to a lot of places.
If you go on a trip, I won't have the right to go out.
But if you go on a trip, I won't have the right to go out.
Is that so?
Why are you not commenting?
I don't want to talk.
Do it on TV!
I wasn't interested in it.
You weren't interested in it?
Even this?
I don't want to talk.
I see.
You're going to be in a drama again, right?
I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry.
You're going to take all the young women in Japan...
What are you talking about?
That's why I'm talking about this guy.
I want to tell you guys.
Don't compare the drama with reality.
It's completely different, isn't it?
That's true.
For example, if you're weak...
If you're weak, you should open a sleeping class.
What are you talking about?
I'm not interested in it.
You're interested in it?
It's wonderful.
Actors are interested in reality and drama.
They think I'm like this.
I'm like this.
It's totally different.
Normally, I'm like this.
I'm not interested in it.
I'm thinking about the short story.
The apple is the best product in Japan.
This is...
Why do you think it's the best product?
You may think so now.
My story is always like that.
At first, I think it's strange, but in the end...
It's strange all the time.
In the end, everyone is convinced.
I'm not convinced.
I'm satisfied with Ayahuya.
Don't say Ayahuya.
What?
Speaking of the best product in Aomori Prefecture...
Don't say what?
That's my job.
Speaking of the best product in Aomori Prefecture...
It's the apple.
It's the same.
The best product in Aomori Prefecture is not only in Aomori Prefecture.
Do you understand?
That's why I'm familiar with the Japanese products.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I'm familiar with the Japanese products.
I'm familiar with the best products.
You can say that.
You're familiar with the best products.
I'm familiar with them.
Are you sad?
I'm not sad.
I'm familiar with them.
I'm sleepy right now.
Why?
Speak.
Why are you sleepy?
I'm sleepy.
The apple is coming out in Japan right now.
About 45% of this product is from Aomori Prefecture.
And the remaining 55% is from me.
I don't understand the meaning of the word, me.
I'm the one who created it.
How do you do it?
Well...
About once a month...
Sometimes I do this.
I lie down.
It's tiring, isn't it?
I do this.
How do you do it?
Then the person who made it will come.
The person who made it will come?
The person who made it will come.
I'll lie down.
And the person who made it will do it.
The person who made it will do it.
Do you cut your nipples?
I don't cut my nipples.
Who cuts their nipples?
Gyo-cha does.
If you don't, your nipples will fall off.
Right?
Rinkan is also completely white.
Ah, it's not Rinkan.
What is it?
Eh?
It's Newton. Who is it?
It's me, isn't it?
Can you say it?
Yes, yes.
Newton.
Ah, that's how it is.
Mike Tyson's left arm has a tattoo of respect for Moutakuto.
What kind of tattoo is there on Mach-chan's left arm?
My tattoo is a bit different from normal people's.
Ah, is that so?
Well, I don't know how to say it.
I remember a lot of anger.
Does it come out when you're angry?
When I'm angry, it's like...
I think it doesn't smell.
What?
What kind of tattoo comes out?
Mike Tyson's Moutakuto.
Yes, yes, yes.
What kind of tattoo comes out?
Ah, it comes out in various ways.
Why does it come out in various ways?
There are various things that come out of nowhere.
Are you really angry?
Really?
What?
What comes out?
Well, this is...
What?
What kind of tattoo comes out?
Why don't you tell me?
What?
What kind of tattoo comes out?
Well, let me tell you.
It's usually a tattoo of a girl I'm dating.
Ah, yes.
Yoshiko Inoshita.
Ah, Yoshiko Inoshita.
That's good.
And Keiko Inoshita.
Ah, Keiko Inoshita.
That's good.
Well, that's a life.
That's a life.
It's troublesome when you break up.
That's right.
You can use a stone.
You can use a cicada.
Please do something.
Mr. Matsumoto, an animal scientist who's in the top five in the world.
Why can a crane support its body with such thin legs?
I also...
So you're an animal scientist?
That's right
So you're in the field of expertise?
Of course, it's a very specialized field
I'm mostly researching the legs of cranes
Specialized in what?
I'll be honest with you
Of course!
I don't care if you call me a thief
Of all the living animals in the world
The one with the best balance is actually a crane
So?
I really wondered why
In the end, what that means is that
The legs of a crane are actually about 4 meters long
Downwards?
It's a fence!
It's like this thing that comes out of the ground
It's still growing in the middle
There's this thing in the middle of the long part
There is
There's still more down there
Depending on how hard it is, there are a few
There are times like this too
What?
There are times when it goes in like this
Ah, when there's a hard rock underneath
So it's called a fence
There are times like that
It's diagonal
I don't think I've seen anything like this before
If it goes BAM! it won't break
It won't break
It's going all the way down
If it goes BAM from the side, it'll break
That's because they've done a lot of things like that before
The old cranes used to break
Ah, really?
But they said, this isn't good, let's gather
Gather!
They said, what is it?
What is it?
A lot of things came
Too much
I'm sorry
You were there
Toshimitsu, you were there
Who is it?
Toshimitsu!
Toshimitsu of the crane
Yes, what is it?
What is it?
Toryo
Toryo?
No, not Toryo
Erai-san's crane
You can't do it
Let's gather some wood
Let's make some noise
It's yellow
Let's make some noise, let's confirm
It's dangerous
Nagai-san, there's this too
How do you do that?
Hurry up and erase it
Now I'm one of the old cranes
The first time I did it was 26
6 years ago
Thank you very much