Hello.
Yes, yes.
I was just thinking...
No, no, no.
This is a long intro.
It's long, isn't it?
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
Yes, yes.
You...
Your heart isn't here.
Well, you know...
Are you okay?
No, I can't go home.
In public shows,
there are people who lose their motivation.
They don't all smile.
No, no, no.
They're the type who are brought here.
It's probably luck.
I think it's definitely luck.
I didn't want to see anything.
You didn't raise your face, did you?
No, I didn't raise my face.
You were like this the whole time.
It was like the morning of a school trip.
It was just a pillow.
I was holding a pillow like this.
That's terrible.
Didn't you say you were going on a trip?
What kind of trip?
You said you were going on a trip when it was over.
If there wasn't a regular show, I'd like to be on it.
I'll be there.
So I was wondering what to do.
Go somewhere.
Thank you for your help in the drama.
You don't have to say it like that.
Thank you very much.
Well, I don't know what to do if I'm told this is a school trip.
It's better to say it like this.
There was some weird atmosphere.
In places like this, there's usually a lot of people.
But when you're in that kind of atmosphere,
it's like, wow, who's this guy?
It's Hamada! It's Hamada from Dandan!
That's disgusting.
No matter what they say.
Really.
Well, I don't care.
If I'm told to dress like this,
they'll be like,
Oh, really?
Really, it was kind of amazing.
But, you know...
What?
The drama is so tiring!
Shut up!
I've been doing it for three months.
That's true.
The last scene I was filming,
what was it?
It was a mess.
The last scene, the last cut,
I thought it would be a little more moving.
I had a bouquet of flowers and asked for a word.
That was the situation.
But that...
Right behind that,
there was a clerk.
The clerk's location was like,
Get out of the way!
It was like, gah!
It was starting.
And I was like, I don't care about you guys.
And the clerk was like,
Thank you very much!
It was the worst way to end it,
to make it look like he was running away.
You should've moved to a different location.
Really.
I didn't know what to do.
But that's how it was.
I want to go on a trip.
I really want to.
You should go!
I don't have time.
I have to go once a week.
This is...
This is going to be a hot topic, right?
That's true.
Wherever you go,
this is going to be a hot topic.
It's like the old Itom.
I don't know about that.
Didn't you take a break from Itom?
You said you were going on a trip with your family.
I didn't take a break at all.
You didn't take a break?
No.
I remembered the story of how I got really angry.
The story of how I felt sorry for Mach-chan.
This guy...
It's New Year's Day, right?
It's New Year's Day!
You always take a break on New Year's Day.
On New Year's Day,
this guy...
I don't know what he said.
He said he was going overseas.
He doesn't take a break on New Year's Day.
New Year's Day is three or four days, right?
You said you wanted to go on a trip with your family.
If I wanted to go, I would go every year.
I can't go for three days.
He said he wanted to go.
He said he wanted to take a break.
I said, okay, I'll go.
I thought I'd take a break too.
He said, no, just Matsumoto should go.
I said, no, just the two of us.
Please take care of me.
I said it many times.
You said it many times?
Please take care of me.
No, no, no.
I said, no, no.
He said, no, no, no.
Abba-chan has a family too.
I was wondering what he meant by that.
He said, okay, then, please take a break on New Year's Day.
That's right.
I said I'd go for three days.
I said, okay, then, please take a break on New Year's Day.
If you say so, I'll go.
He said he would.
I said, okay, then, please take a break on New Year's Day.
I wanted to take a video.
I wanted to take a video of myself.
The schedule couldn't be filled in in that video.
If I didn't have a good friend...
You could go.
I could go.
I wanted to use the time I had at that time.
That's right.
It's work, it's work.
I said, please let me use it here.
He said, it's okay.
Did he really say, it's okay?
I was filming a video.
I used the time I had at that time.
I was in Kyoto.
I was filming there.
It was time for a good friend.
I happened to be able to watch it.
I watched it on TV.
Tamaguchi-san came out.
He came out in glasses.
I think it's okay.
He came out.
It's okay from there.
It's okay after that.
I don't know what to say.
Mach-chan suddenly got a fever and collapsed.
What?
Your family trip is going well.
Even if I take a break from work, if I have a fever, I have to lie.
What kind of fever is this?
Who has a fever?
I don't know about that.
That's how you do it on Uji TV.
It was really bad.
I felt a little better.
Now I have a fever.
Well, let's go home.
I want to go home.
Why?
Is someone waiting for me?
It sounds good.
Wow!
I have something I want to ask you.
What?
What do you want to ask me?
Stop pretending.
What?
Someone is waiting for you.
It's the first time I've said that.
I don't like it.
I'm so excited.
I want to go home soon.
No, no.
It doesn't matter if it's another show.
When a female guest comes, she says she's been a fan for a long time.
I don't know what to do when I'm told that.
That's why my face turns red.
I want to do something about it.
It's okay to be surprised.
It's a close save.
And when she comes back, her face will be strange again.
Why?
Really.
There are some female guests who come and touch me strangely.
If you do that, your face will turn red.
It's getting worse.
I used to be fine.
Why is that?
What's wrong with you?
Who are you talking to?
Your face won't turn red.
I want to go home.
Let's go home.
You said it perfectly.
In your hot underwear.
I don't remember such an old story.
I have a question for you.
Yes.
What should I do if someone takes my back?
It's said that you're the most free.
If someone takes your back?
If someone takes your back.
No matter how good you are, no one can take your back.
As long as it's me, it's okay.
Even if someone takes it?
Even if someone takes it.
What will happen if someone takes your back?
That's right.
For example, like this.
If you do this, you can't move.
In an instant, I thought I was in the end.
When that happens, you don't know what to do.
I see.
You can't move.
In your case, it's okay.
As long as it's me, it's okay.
What is it?
Let's take your back.
Like this, right?
Are you suddenly going to do that?
I don't think you can take my back.
Oh, really?
Yes.
Then what should I do?
What?
Take your back.
Take my back.
Wait a minute.
Let go of me.
It hurts here.
That's why I don't feel like doing it anymore.
In that situation, you lost.
That's not it.
You're not like that.
How does a fight start?
The water hits your shoulder.
That's fine.
You hit me, right?
Shut up.
Shut up?
Where did you find that?
Listen to me.
I was surprised.
The most important thing for me is not to go wild.
I see.
If I go wild, I'll avoid it.
I have to have love for the other person.
This is the rhythm of a rambutan.
My butt has been here all this time.
I'm sorry.
I told you to let go.
Let go.
If you keep doing this.
You're only using your upper body.
You're only using your lower body.
You will really let go.
You will have another love.
That's how it is.
Are you serious?
This is why I'm getting 800,000 yen.
That's the best for me.
It's a question for you, Mr. Matsumoto.
You were at the bar and was in the bathroom for a long time and people would think you were taking a dump.
When you were returning to the seat, you were a little embarrassed.
Why did you have to put on a show that you're not taking a dump?
Well, there are.
There are?
Yes, there are.
But I don't care.
Whether it takes long or short.
I'm going to the toilet, so I don't care.
There are quiet toilets.
I'm curious about the sound at those times.
If it takes a long time, I don't care.
Or if I have to endure until the last minute.
While talking at the coffee shop.
When I get to the entrance,
I say, sorry, I need to go to the toilet.
Then I immediately go out.
I immediately go out.
That's what I...
That's what you use.
That's what I think is best.
Even that can be seen.
The way you move your face.
Also, when you drink coffee at the coffee shop,
once...
What is it?
No, no.
If you decide on that, it's no good.
No matter what you do, you'll die.
What should I do now?
This is really...
I think this is a really good method.
You can do it as many times as you want.
What do you mean?
That's fine.
During that time, maybe that person is pooping.
That's what I think.
That's what you think.
You can think about it.
Just think about it.
If you can make it look like it was different later,
then the result is alright.
That's right.
It's a way to come back.
If you can make it look like it was different.
That's the best.
That's what I mean.
I can do it properly.
I really can.
You go like this, right?
Should we go out?
Where?
Let's go out to the toilet.
Okay.
Wait for me.
This is a really good method.
Okay.
I can do it.
That's the best.
I don't think it'll end like this.
No, no, no.
You can't go in from here.
I just think it's cool.
The other woman will probably think,
I don't care about that.
She'll definitely think that.
I think this is the best.
Really?
You don't think so because your boyfriend did that, right?
What's with you?
I feel like I can go home.
What's that?
This is the best.
Really?
You can use either of them.
Until the entrance.
No, I can't use the entrance.
Why not?
I'll definitely go out.
You won't?
I'll go out.
I'll go up and before I crouch,
I'll go like this.
Idiot.
You have your own will.
You can leave your grandma here.
You have something else.
It's impossible.
It's just this.
It's definitely impossible.
When you go out a little, it's fine.
But it's okay.
You're crouching.
When you go like this, you go like this.
It's okay.
You have a lot of willpower.
Until then, you won't be able to crouch.
If you're not good at it, you'll just come out like this.
It's definitely impossible.
It's impossible.
It's okay.
Even if you have a lot of panties,
it's better than nothing.
If you don't want to get caught.
Even if you have a lot of panties,
it's better than nothing.
It's better than nothing.
Even if you have a lot of panties,
it's better than nothing.
What are you talking about?
Senpai Nuguru
Matsumoto-san says that he was a baby for about 10 years after he was born.
The baby suddenly starts crying,
but there must be a reason for it.
Matsumoto-san, please solve the mystery of the baby suddenly crying.
This is a pretty deep story.
I'm sure there's a reason for everything.
I'm sure there is.
Normally babies cry when they're hungry, right?
No, they don't cry.
Even if you give them food, they suddenly start crying.
You didn't like it, did you?
That's right.
That's a stupid story.
It's because it's so annoying.
No one says it's annoying.
There's a reason for it.
Yes, there is.
Please tell me.
The baby cries on the train, right?
That's because he thinks about a lot of things and gets excited.
He has a father, a mother, a lunch box,
tea,
the scenery on the train is beautiful,
the mountain is over there,
That's because he's happy, right?
That's right.
That's the reason.
That's why he gets more and more excited.
That's why he thinks about a lot of things while he's crying.
He thinks, I feel good now.
I feel comfortable now.
My father was good too.
I want to live like this forever.
But I want to grow up to be an adult one day.
I have to study in elementary school.
I have to leave elementary school.
I have to take part in part-time jobs.
You're a cute boy!
What the hell are you thinking?
Who said I can't think?
There's a reason for it.
He thinks about a lot of things.
He's like a dog.
He's like a firefly.
Everyone is like that.
You think he's crying all of a sudden, don't you?
But he's not crying all of a sudden. He's crying for a reason.
No, he's not.
Well, of course, when a strange guy comes, he cries.
Who is this guy? Who is he?
That's right.
Say it! Say it!
I have to say it?
What are those pants? What are they?
So he cries.
The pants are long!
He doesn't hate it.
When he gets hated around here, he gets very angry.
Well, that's how it is.
That's how it is.
There are things like that.
Is that so?
Yes.
Please tell us a professional reaction to the moment a black beard came out in a black beard machine game.
Huh?
It's Kase.
This is...
But...
This is... I want to know too.
Even if you tell me a professional reaction.
But this is...
I don't know which one will win.
No, I don't care. I want to know your reaction.
Can I do this?
Sure.
Even if you tell me a professional reaction.
Well, it's different from an amateur.
That's true.
If you're an amateur, you go like this.
For example, if you put this in...
You can't do it with this.
It's a talking pattern, so it gets in the way.
But I don't understand it.
I think he'll say something when it goes bang.
He'll laugh at you.
I don't know.
It's dangerous.
I don't know what to do.
I think I know what to do.
This...
See? I just took it off.
This is bad.
You have to do it better.
That's right.
Even if you tell me, what should I do?
It's okay. You can use this.
I can use it?
For example...
Let's say you stick it out.
Okay.
And when you stick it out...
When it goes bang...
What kind of reaction will it be?
Let's do it slowly.
When you stick it out...
What should I make for dinner tonight?
You're the one in front of the fish.
That's too much.
This is normal.
I'm a professional at reactions.
But I want to be kind to black beards.
Is it okay to have black beards?
I want to express my feelings.
Is that dangerous?
Let's do it normally.
I don't like this.
This is...
This is a professional reaction.
Do you understand?
Black doesn't even make a sound.
He only pulls his body.
I'm tired!
It's too early!
You should have black beards for the third one!
I don't care! I'm tired!
Please do it properly.
I've done it before.
Like this.
But that was the snow Matsumoto Hitoshi.
I want you to see the difference.
You should have said it first.
That was the snow Matsumoto Hitoshi.
I felt like I was playing with my family.
That's why I did it.
I'll do it properly.
I'm scared.
You should have said it.
Are you okay?
It's too early!
That was the snow Matsumoto Hitoshi.
I've done it before.
This time I'll do it with my legs.
Even if I do this...
I can't do anything.
It's too early!
What are you doing?
It's strange.
Do it again!
I want to do it properly.
That's right.
I'll do it.
This is scary.
I hate this.
Thank you very much.
Why?
This program was brought to you by these sponsors.