Yoh-kan, Yoh-kan, Yoh-kan
Yoh-kan Kusai wa Nakayoshi da
Itsumo Futari de Mitsu Yoh-kan
Yoh-kan no Tanna
Yoh-kan no Yome
Yoru wa Kuri Yoh-kan
HON-HON!
Yoh-san joined us today as well.
How is it, seeing Dantan for the first time?
Even if it's not the first time, there are people like that.
But it's not the first time at all.
Ah, is that so?
When you experience it, it's surprisingly...
It must be smelly, right?
It's smelly, right?
Really, it's really...
You're very charismatic, aren't you?
I think you have a lot of thoughts.
Because when you see a talent for the first time, you have a lot of thoughts, don't you?
I wonder if it's okay to be happy about it.
It's okay to be happy about it.
It's okay to be happy about 6-4, isn't it?
Eh? 6 is normal?
It's okay to be happy about 6.
Ah, is that so?
Well, it's okay, isn't it?
There are things like that, but...
I, you know...
I discovered a lot of things.
And I was able to make a good reason for it.
If you listen to this story, I think everyone will think,
Oh, Matsumoto is really amazing.
I think you'll be able to think like that.
Ah, I see.
Do you want to hear that story?
Actually, he said it because he wanted to.
Well, I really want to hear it.
Well...
UFO.
Time machine theory.
It's something that can be said.
By who?
By me.
By me?
It's something that I can say.
If you listen to this story, you'll think,
Ah, Matsumoto has started again.
This guy is completely crazy.
He wants to come out of the ***.
You think so, don't you?
But this is amazing.
It's different.
This is different.
It's easy to understand.
So, according to my theory,
Everyone often talks about aliens,
but there is no such thing as aliens.
Aliens are future people.
You can call them aliens.
But future people are aliens,
and aliens are future people.
Do you understand?
I clearly understood this.
Why is it so...
It's like a world of loneliness.
Why is it like a world of loneliness?
Please come in more.
You understood that, didn't you?
I understood that.
I see.
I don't understand anything.
You don't understand anything.
What kind of place is it?
I sometimes see UFOs.
Well, not often.
I come to see UFOs.
It's impossible for UFOs to attack earthlings.
I see.
In the end, they will kill us.
If they attack earthlings and kill them,
the history will be messed up.
There is a possibility that our existence will disappear.
In movies, aliens often attack earthlings,
but there is absolutely no such thing.
I see.
Yes.
What is it this time?
I am waiting for the end of the war.
Shut up.
I understand.
I am listening to you seriously.
Speak.
My friend's mother saw a huge UFO during the war.
What do you mean by huge?
During the war,
when there was a lot of air raid,
there were a lot of UFOs.
That means there are a lot of UFOs.
It's huge.
I saw it almost every day at that time.
I haven't seen it recently.
The reason is that I came to see it.
I came to see the war.
I came to see World War II.
UFOs are sightseeing.
In the future, there will be a travel agency.
If you ask me where I want to see it,
I will say it's a war.
This is called Hawaii.
It is the most difficult thing to see a war.
As a UFO.
Because everyone is running away.
Even if you see a UFO, you can't help it.
That's why there were a lot of UFOs during the war.
Do you understand that?
You can follow me up to this point.
After the UFO fell,
I became a captured alien.
Annan has already been decided.
I will definitely...
Why did you become 36 years old and step on the box?
Please continue my story.
I'm sorry.
Please shorten the tempo a little more.
I want to travel by UFO.
If you want to go to the past,
Please follow the rules.
There is a rule that you should not get off.
If you get off and have contact, it will be strange.
But what is it?
There are times when an old man goes abroad and becomes drunk and strange.
In this way, you can remove the feeling of traveling.
So the captured alien is drunk.
He's like, no, no, no!
Swing monster!
It's a bloody leg.
Because it's a bloody leg, it's both sides.
Finally, the cold day came and I was told to go home.
There is no doubt.
Do you have any comments on this matter?
No.
Wow!
It's a fun theory.
But I think it's definitely true.
There's no mistake about this.
Why is everyone smiling?
The storm of failure.
Failure. Failure. Failure.
Smile of love.
Well then.
There's a lot of things we have to do today.
First of all, let's have a match.
That's fine.
Let's call the Hamada team.
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
Are you ready, Mr. Matsumoto?
Yes.
This time, it's a four-man vs. one-man match.
It's one-on-one.
Yes, yes.
We've decided that it's one-on-one 100m.
This time, our staff is going to do a simulation.
Oh.
This is Tanaka.
Yes.
This is Endo.
This is Yamasaki.
This is me.
We're going to do a simulation.
Please take a look.
Yes, yes.
Please.
This is Yamasaki.
Yes.
Oh, that's it?
Yamasaki.
This is Tanaka.
Tanaka.
Yes.
This is Endo.
Is this me?
This is completely different.
This is half a year later.
It's been half a year.
This is me.
The Hamada team is completely different.
Oh, poor guy.
Oh, Numa.
Why is it Oh, Numa?
It's crazy.
Why is it up?
It's up.
This is Mazo.
Yes.
That's good.
It's amazing that Sugata-san just came out.
Sugata-san is already used to it.
That's right.
Sugata-san is not a skirt.
The first time, each of the four is running 25 meters.
Yes.
That's 100 meters.
I see.
Passing the baton.
This is the first time.
Yes.
Next.
Let's see.
Ready.
First of all, Yamazaki-san.
This is Yamazaki.
Yamazaki.
This is me.
This is Endo.
Endo is fast.
This is Tanaka.
This is a good match.
Wow.
Yes.
Yes, Numa.
Numa is the same.
Are you kidding me?
This is a good match.
This is 25 meters.
That's why.
Sugata-san.
The second time.
Yes.
This is 20 meters.
The last time is 40 meters.
Yes.
Hamada-san is 40 meters.
Hamada is 40 meters.
Yamazaki, Endo, Tanaka, me.
In this order.
Pay attention.
2, 2, 2, 4.
Ready.
He didn't raise his thighs.
But this is slow.
It's 20 meters. It's short.
This is Baton.
I'm Baton.
He is laughing.
Seriously.
But this is close.
He is laughing.
What happened?
He looks like a murderer.
He is smoking.
Next.
The first time is 94 meters.
I see.
The last time is 2, 2, 2.
Hamada, Yamazaki, Tanaka, Endo.
Yes.
This is...
Hamada-san and Matsumoto-san.
Hamada and I ran 94 meters first.
94.
At the next step.
I see.
This is...
2 meters, 2 meters.
That was close.
That's why.
It's important.
The last time is 2, 2, 2.
94.
It's the same as the last time.
It's the same.
Hamada-san is the last one.
This is advantageous for me.
At the first step.
This is difficult.
This is...
This is dangerous.
This is advantageous.
But,
Onuma-san is fast.
He's catching up.
He's not catching up, Yasuda-san.
He's not catching up.
But,
Matsumoto-san won this.
This is interesting.
I tried this.
I see.
Can I say one thing?
This is the most shameless location in Japan.
This is a simulation of the staff.
I tried various patterns.
For example, 2 meters, 2 meters.
I can't do this.
I can't move my legs.
What should I do?
That's not good.
That's advantageous.
It's just a loss time.
The last one is not good.
But,
The last one is 2 meters, 2 meters.
It's still there.
But,
It's not interesting.
After all,
It's better to run to some extent.
It's okay if you decide.
If it's not good, I'll say it.
Is that so?
It's up to you to decide.
You decide.
You guys are idiots.
Idiots.
25, 25, 25.
This is the first one.
This is normal.
What's the order?
The last one is Hamada.
Let's go one on one with Hamada and Matsumoto.
The last one is...
It's not one on one.
You guys are idiots.
That's right.
The last one is 26 meters.
It's not good.
That's not good.
I'm the only one who thinks it's funny.
No, no, no.
It's funny.
It's a service cut.
I don't need a service cut.
It's an image.
It's your image.
It's 1 meter.
What kind of image is that?
It's an image of 26 meters.
I see.
I think it's here and here.
It's different between me and Kosei.
Yamazaki's baton is easy for Hamada to hold.
But Tanaka's baton is hard to hold.
I don't know.
I don't want to do it.
Hamada is not bad at all.
He's not bad at all.
And he's slow.
You have to remember it.
That's right.
Don't be slow.
Listen to me.
Don't be bad.
What are you doing?
Mr. Hamada.
I'm done.
Stand up.
What is this?
He's sleeping.
Stand up.
There's such a thing.
It's hard to decide the order here.
That's right.
The order is like this.
Let's leave the last one to Hamada.
I'll leave it to Hamada.
An anchor.
Really?
Yes.
You're the top, right?
I'll be the top.
Really?
That's fast.
At this distance, I think I can do it.
My power?
This is...
It's 25 meters.
What?
I just decided.
It's 25 meters.
Are you listening?
So I can't do it.
Then I'll be the third.
You just decided 25 meters.
That's not good for Akko.
It's not good for Akko.
Is this 25 meters?
This is the most...
Decide that.
But...
I think so.
For example, I'm 10 meters.
10?
10 meters.
The rest is 20, 20, 20, 40.
Which one?
Which one do you think?
That's right.
Yamada-san should be shorter.
Why didn't you ask for your opinion?
Yamada-san is in the center now.
Why are you in the center?
As a leader.
Of the blue team.
I can't be stupid.
Isn't it good?
I'm sorry.
That's the real thing.
We're running.
Four of us run 100 meters before the show.
We calculate how much we can run.
But you guys are not as young as you think.
I don't think I can run that many times a day.
But if you do that once, it will be 3 hours later.
3 hours later.
So we gather at the studio at 6 o'clock.
That's fast.
Isn't that fast?
It's hard.
It's hard to gather at 6 o'clock.
We have to practice the baton after that.
Then it will take an hour.
That's right.
An hour?
The baton practice...
I can't accept the baton practice.
Why?
I can't accept it.
I can't do that.
Why not?
I mean...
It's good for us.
No.
Your baton is my support.
That's why.
No.
It's your feeling.
We have to do it well.
We have to do it quickly.
You can say that.
You have to run 50 meters.
I have to run fast.
That's right.
You have to run fast.
I can't do that.
You have to give it to me.
You can't run fast.
If you think like that, when will I lose?
You can't be stupid.
I'm not stupid.
I know.
I don't look like that.
I don't like the baton practice.
Why?
I'm the one who designed the baton practice.
What?
You need to look at the baton and deny it.
I want you to look at my baton practice.
What kind of business do you have?
I think this is the best one.
I like the normal one.
It's heavy!
Really?
What is this?
I can't see!
Yamazaki!
What was that?
I'm sorry.
Why did you say that?
I can't see!
If I can't see, I can see again.
This is no good.
It's heavy.
I knew that this would be rejected.
That's right.
Please look at the next one.
How about this?
I can't see!
It's thick.
You shouldn't hold the baton like this.
Is this a pipe?
Yamazaki!
It's a pipe!
It's not a pipe!
The pipe is like this.
It's a pipe.
It's not a pipe.
The next one is this.
It's a pipe.
I can't see!
This is good.
If you drop it...
I have to calm down.
I can't do that.
This one is good.
This is good.
Like this.
I will run with this one.
I will run with both of them.
Just once?
In such a short amount of time, how can you do this?
Can't I choose?
No, you can't
And then, the costumes
Costumes?
Wait a minute
Is it okay to wear normal costumes?
No, I thought it would be better to think about costumes
I've been thinking about it
I think it's okay for all four of us to wear the same costumes
Because we're a team
I've been thinking about it
Please change your costumes
Okay
As a model
Which one do you choose?
Okay, I'll change
Okay
Hurry up
Which one of those three should I choose?
That's right
What if I don't have one?
That's fine
But
Don't you often see UO?
That's what I said, so I knew right away
Okay, let's start with Tanaka's costume
Here you go
What is it?
I don't know
It's a design
No
You thought about it, didn't you?
No, listen
If you think about the time
You can't avoid being sexy
I'm not sexy at all
It's easy to run
I know
I don't care if I don't wear it
Why don't you know about AHC?
It's shaking
The viewer's heart is shaking
What?
What is this?
Why are you so lonely?
Because I'm cold?
It's an interesting way to take a picture
Next, Yamazaki
I think this is fine
Wait a minute
Isn't this a trick?
I think this is fine
It's not a trick
It's a trick
Of course, there are four people
Each?
End
This is the best
Excuse me
It's not cute
It's a running pose
Why is this?
But I'm a see-through
There is such a thing
No
Genie is see-through
I've never heard
I'm scared
It's hard to run
From these three
No
I will run normally
What kind of clothes do you wear when you run?
I'm formal
Formal?
I don't agree
Do you run like that?
If you get sucked in
It's ruined
What are you talking about?
Please subscribe to the channel