Ladies and Gentlemen
Hello
Today you look like a manga artist
Yes, I look like a manga artist
Today, you are doing a punishment game at 5.29 am
Yes, I'm doing it
Of course, of course Kohaku will win
Yes, yes, yes
I thought so
Actually, I watched Kohaku too
I watched it too, for some reason this year
You watched it, right?
What?
Yachiyo no Kai came out
Yes, yes, yes
And gave me a card
I watched it
Here you go
It's all white
What is this?
I watched it
And I showed it to the audience
And everyone in the audience gave me a card
And I looked like I had a lot of red
Really?
Yachiyo no Kai has a lot of red
The audience gave you a lot of red
Kohaku, I really don't feel like I lost
I still have it
Well, this can't be helped, so I let it go
Well, after that
Well, after watching the video
My brain is
Brain?
You said brain
Please monitor it
Did you actually watch it this morning?
You guys are out
Please watch the punishment game
This is
Are you stupid?
I am
It's pretty long
Are you stupid?
This is the first job of ITele this year
I'm on it
This is
JOH TV Channel 4
This is Japanese TV
This is Hayami Yu's American Kiss
Please watch
I am
I didn't lose to Hamada
Kobayashi Sachiko lost to luck
If you could have been there
I don't know that mistake
It's true
Kobayashi Sachiko did it
I would have lost
If you could have been there
I would have made a big difference
I'm saying this again
Matsumoto Matakai
You are a great person
You might say that
I was picking up pachinko
What happened?
You were picking up pachinko
I was picking up pachinko
I saw the pachinko
Thank you
This is Yamaoka Yuza
This is
Hello
I'm glad you invited me to Yoshimoto
That's all
You were on that show
After the show ended, you called me
You didn't say a single word
You were on the show
I didn't know
You liked this song
After the show ended, you didn't say a single word
You must have made a mistake
I shouldn't have done that
If I hadn't made a mistake, I would have called you 20 times
Is that so?
Ha ha
What's with the ha ha?
What?
You're scary
I was doing it
Stop it
It's the result
I wanted you to be on the show
What are you talking about?
I wouldn't have been punished if I had told you
What?
It's nothing
You scared me
You were awake
You were in the opposite position
I was sleeping
You were awake
I wouldn't have been punished
Were you watching TV?
I was watching
You were awake and you were still awake after the show ended
I wouldn't have been punished if I had told you
It's the same
What?
I don't want to be on the show anymore
Shut up
I didn't do anything wrong
Why should I be punished?
I told you
I can win
You think you can win?
I won't be punished if I get 200,000 yen
That's cheap
It's like rugby
I didn't do anything wrong
Other players were playing
You were playing
Wait
Rugby
My mouth smells
Whose mouth smells?
My mouth says it's going to be sour
I'm really good at sports
Even if I get sick for a week or two
I have a lot of power in rugby
You can do it
What are you doing?
I haven't put on makeup
I'll do it
I'm sure I can win
That was funny
You guys are funny
But I'm the only one who gets embarrassed
You can't even come to my house
What are you going to do if you can't come?
I can't turn it around
I don't want to do it anymore
I can't sleep
That's good
It's good
It started this year
Do you have a day off this year?
I don't have a day off
You have a lot of days off
I was playing at home
I bought a kotatsu
That's good
Where are you going?
This is the first time
I'm talking to you
I don't have a day off
This is the first time
Really
And I'm sitting here
I can't stop
I know who I am
I'm a person who can't tell the cause
Maybe
I had this face
I'm bleeding
It started
I can't get on
I was walking down the street
I was looking at you
I was happy
You were late
I was late
You were telling your boyfriend
I can't tell
My boyfriend is okay
That's good
I came here with a strong will, so I thought this girl would be the same.
That's right, that's right.
That's what I thought!
That's what you thought.
Somehow, this...
She's back!
I was just talking about you!
Ah, the guest!
Congratulations!
Ah, I'm glad, I'm glad.
I'm glad, I'm glad.
I won't say it to everyone anymore.
I already know everything.
Ah, I'm glad, I'm glad.
But, I'm glad you brought it.
Right?
I was relieved.
It's really rare.
It can't be helped.
Right?
Ah, I'm glad.
What were you talking about?
That you bought a kotatsu.
Ah, when I talk about kotatsu,
there are people who stand up, aren't there?
There are, aren't there?
I bought a kotatsu.
You bought rice.
I bought rice.
Ah, did you hear that?
It's a pattern!
There's still more.
There's still more, there's still more.
No, really, it was a good price.
There's still more, isn't there?
Why is it so big?
It's on the side.
It's a star, isn't it?
It's Nanga-sama, isn't it?
It's amazing, it's amazing.
Who is it?
There's still more.
No, this time, I just took my parents with me.
You just took them with you?
What?
I just took my parents with me.
It's the first and the last time.
Ah, your grandma,
and my dad,
and my mom,
and my sister, right?
Oh, your sister went too?
Yes.
And me, my brother-in-law, my sister-in-law,
my brother-in-law's father and mother-in-law,
and last year, I went too,
but I'm riding on the Orix picture,
and the couple there,
and the parents and sister there,
It's a circus!
That's amazing!
It was really hard.
Where did you go?
I went to Gamu.
I went to Hawaii last year, and then to Gamu,
but it wasn't fun at all.
Why?
I've never been to Gamu.
Only the entertainer, Mitchan.
What about Mitchan?
Did he come with his husband?
With his child.
I thought I'd go again.
I went to a duty-free shop or a shop,
and they talked to me,
and I said,
I'm going to take pictures,
so don't do that!
It was going on like that,
and I was sleeping, eating.
And the woman in front of me was like,
Hama-chan, Hama-chan!
I looked at her,
and the woman wearing glasses was looking at me,
and I thought I'd go again.
I didn't know what to do,
so I took her out and said,
Hama-chan, Hama-chan!
I looked at her,
and she was so ugly!
Who is this?
I looked at Mitchan.
Oh, Egbo.
It's Egbo's true identity.
Why do you have a dent?
What is it?
This is,
in the past,
once,
I've been dented.
You've been dented?
Once in the past.
By whom?
That depends on each person.
Oh.
Why?
That's why I said,
why?
That's because the reasons are different.
If the reasons are different,
does that mean you're all dented?
You're dented here.
Yes, yes, yes.
How did you get dented?
That's why there are so many reasons!
That's why I didn't say it!
I said,
say at least one example.
I see, I see, I see.
That's how it is.
That's right.
If you don't say it,
everyone won't be convinced.
This is,
this is a good thing
you just said,
Hama-chan.
Egbo-san,
an elementary school student,
a fourth grader,
Egbo-san,
let's take her as an example.
It doesn't matter who it is.
Hurry up and say it.
It's a girl.
At that time,
my father,
um,
got dented.
This Egbo-san,
um,
is from Tokyo.
She's from Tokyo.
So,
my father got dented,
and had to go to Hokkaido.
I thought about it simply.
But,
um,
for a fourth grader,
Egbo-san,
it's the most important time,
so,
my father and Hama-chan...
Don't say that!
Say that!
How did you get dented?
You should say it!
I'll say it, so shut up!
Don't say that!
It's not good, is it?
Even though you're here,
you're with your family.
Don't say that!
So,
with your family,
you're going to Hokkaido, aren't you?
Yes, yes.
Actually,
Egbo-san,
your favorite man...
Don't say that!
Say it!
So,
finally,
the day of moving...
Hurry up and say it.
...has come.
You did it, didn't you?
Did you go to Hokkaido?
Um,
well,
I took the train to Hokkaido.
I have to say goodbye to everyone.
Egbo!
Egbo?
No, Egbo-san.
Egbo!
It doesn't have to be a special name.
Why?
Say it.
It's terrible!
Don't say that!
What?
Hurry up and say it!
Egbo,
what?
I take the train to Hokkaido,
I take the train at this time.
I'm telling you.
But,
when the train is about to depart,
the man doesn't come.
So,
I take the train,
and I pass a mountain road,
but on top of the mountain,
there's a man waving his hand.
When Eiko sees this,
Pee!
I'm sorry.
You said you were peeved.
No, I was really peeved mentally.
I gave you a bad example.
It's the example of a person who is emotional.
That's right.
Well, that's what it is.
So, um...
What are you doing?
Peeing.
That's right.
The other day, I was so full that I ate a crab until I died.
What is that?
Oh, really?
I ate a lot.
Yes.
What?
You said you were full and ate a crab.
How do you say that?
That's good.
There's a little more.
What kind of person is that?
Wait a minute.
I was so full that I ate a crab until I died.
I ate a crab.