Next time on Gaki no Tsukai Arahen!
There's one more opening.
Who will be the victim of Tsukitsuki Touka's face?!
Well, as the title says, who will be the victim?
That being said, there's one more big theme this time.
After all, it's about making Yamazaki stand alone.
Is that so?
Of course it is.
Well, that's the reaction to that.
There's Yamazaki in that song, though.
Actually, I have a strong desire to make Yamazaki stand alone.
Ah, so it's still going on.
It's a big deal.
I see, I see.
I'll be doing that for another season.
Ah, is that so?
There's only one left, though.
Yes.
Well then, I'd like to start right away.
First of all, in front of everyone,
we have these transparent balls.
In these balls, one by one,
we'll put faces on them.
Please put your faces on them.
Only one person!
There's someone putting their faces inside the ball.
Well then, let's start right away.
Ready!
Poker Face!
Who's the victim?
Ready!
Put them on!
Don't open your eyes.
If I open my eyes, it'll be bad, right?
Yeah.
Ah, that face.
Wow, Yamazaki's face is so dirty.
Wow.
Wow, Sugachan's face is the worst.
This year, you're making fun of me.
What number do you think Mano-san is?
Number 4.
Number 4 is easy to put on.
Now, who's the victim?
There's no victim!
The victim is Yamazaki!
Next, we'll have everyone put on a mask.
Only one person!
There's someone putting their faces inside the ball.
That's why it's a pack.
Everyone, please look.
Like this.
It's like this.
Because it's a pack.
It's good, right?
Well then, let's start right away.
Everyone, please get ready.
Let's go!
Ready!
That's right, that's right.
That's right.
It's fine if you're stopped.
Put your glasses on!
There we go.
Nice.
What should I do?
This is a hard place to be.
Let's slowly increase the time.
What should I do?
Obviously, your actions are wrong.
Hidai-sama! Who is it?
Oh, it's you!
Actually, we have headphones in front of you.
Well, the music is playing, but...
Only one person!
That glass...
With his nails, like this...
Like this...
That sound is playing.
Let's go!
Hidai-sama!
Who is it?
Hidai-sama! Who is it?
I don't know this.
Hey, Mr. Yamazaki.
Yes.
The main character, Mr. Yamazaki, has a runny nose.
Well, it's his way of listening to music.
Oh, is that so?
It's easy to get on.
Well, let's go!
Hidai-sama!
Who is it?
I don't know this.
It's easy to get on.
Huh?
No, no.
It's easy to get on, isn't it?
No.
Ah, well, that's right.
Well, let's continue.
Yes.
Well, in front of you, on the table...
Well, gum is prepared.
Oh.
Well, um...
Everyone is chewing gum.
Only one person!
It's Gin.
Wow.
Let's sing.
Hidai-sama!
Who is it?
Mr. Takahashi is crying.
I'm not crying.
Huh?
Why are you crying?
I'm not crying.
Huh?
You're crying all by yourself.
Ha ha ha.
What is this opening?
Why are you crying all of a sudden?
Well, that's number two.
Yes.
Hidai-sama!
Who is it?
Ha ha ha.
Wow.
It's so big.
Ha ha ha.
Wow.
The last one.
Yeah.
Well, you're tired.
I prepared something sweet.
Oh, oh, oh.
Well, in front of you,
um, a shake.
I prepared it.
Oh.
Marium has been prepared.
I've never drunk this before.
Me neither.
It's very disgusting.
It seems to be very disgusting.
And after drinking it, you have to drink something like this.
If you don't drink it.
Poop is hard!
Poop doesn't harden!
It seems to harden like a stone.
Ready!
Hello!
How are you doing?
Is it funny?
It smells like the first time we met.
Who do you want to meet for the first time?
Okay, Mr. Mazo.
Who is the first victim?
I'm sorry!
Ladies and gentlemen.
Hello.
It's hard, isn't it?
Thank you very much.
But, recently, there are many angry children.
Oh, is that so?
If you read magazines, you'll see that they write about selfish things, right?
What do you mean?
Something like people's bad words.
Ah, bad words.
There are bad words.
The other day, you saw it, right?
What?
Asahi Entertainment.
Naughty talent special.
If you look at the cover, it says,
Dantan!
Wow, it's written, it's written!
I can accept people's bad words, but I can also accept my own bad words objectively.
Oh, I see.
You're being cheeky.
Sorry for that.
Hey, brother!
What are you laughing at?
You are...
You are!
You're writing down, down!
No, no, no.
What?
Ah, that person's a little angry, isn't it?
No, angry!
No, no, no.
It's because you're writing down, down.
It's not like I'm the only one who's upset that I didn't write it.
It's not that I wrote it in Downtown Hamada, I wrote it in Downtown.
That's not good.
Well, if you write it in Downtown...
If you write it in Downtown, that's not good.
It's just the two of us.
If you say it's in Downtown, then you and I are the same.
That's right, we're the same.
So we have to be cheeky.
We have to be cheeky.
We really have to discuss this.
Right?
The content is written in Downtown, right?
You did a 24-hour TV show, right?
I wrote down their attitude, so they're being cheeky.
Well, that's true.
Well, well, well, they're looking at my attitude.
If I'm told they're being cheeky, I can't help it.
Well, just write it down.
I thought, that wasn't really about being cheeky, was it?
Well, well, it wasn't about being cheeky.
Mask, mask, mask.
Mask, mask, mask, it's like ta-ta-ta-ta-ta!
I laughed.
After that, the producer told us that he shaved a little.
Then downtown got angry when they heard that.
We're working, so why are you shaving?
Why?
The producer had a beard.
He said he shaved his beard.
We shaved the beard of the producer.
We laughed and left.
That's a lie.
No, it's true.
It's not true.
Our producer doesn't have a beard.
It's true.
He's sitting there.
According to the producer,
It's a trend that's been selling so far.
I can't help what I've been told.
It was a proud beard.
It's a little too big.
There's a mistake about the producer.
There's a mistake.
It's not a bad word.
In a broad sense,
I'm still angry.
If you compare it to the eastern part of the country,
The western part of the country is angry.
The eastern part of the country is the western part of the country.
I'm just the western part of the country.
I thought I had to compare it.
I'm from Osaka, so I can't compare it to the western part.
The eastern part is the center of Japan.
If you say the eastern part of the country,
It's an image that has dominated the whole country of Japan.
If you say the western part of the country,
I'm a fox.
This is delicious.
I'm still in Osaka.
I don't like this way of writing.
It's a little too big.
I'm angry.
I don't know why.
I'm not a critic.
I'm angry.
I'm a little angry.
What do you like to watch?
What do I like to watch?
What do you watch?
You always say you watch this.
I see.
Is it your drama?
What do you watch? You always say you watch this.
I always say I watch it every week?
What is it?
I watch it every week.
If you have time to watch it at home, you should watch it.
What do you watch?
Morning Ten.
What is it?
I don't care about the morning.
What I wrote on that show is the name of a celebrity who was born on that day.
I thought you would say my name on September 8th, so I was watching it all the time.
I'm the same age as you, but I was told earlier than you.
I watch this a lot.
I don't really watch it.
Normally I don't watch it.
It's not an interesting show.
My show is the most interesting.
Don't you watch other people's shows?
It's not a big deal.
What is it?
For example, what kind of show is it?
No, no, that's a brother.
What are you talking about?
Don't lie to me.
What is it?
Tell me. I don't know which one is the most interesting.
There are many shows like this that are not interesting.
Most of them are not interesting.
What is the most interesting show that you don't like?
The one that I hate?
Yes, the one that I hate.
Don't think about it. Stop thinking about it.
You're stupid.
Die.
I want to do it.
No, you are wonderful.
Let's go to the post office.
John, wait!
Don't be so surprised.
I'm talking about John.
John, wait!
Say something.
What are you doing?
I'm not looking at you.
What are you thinking?
Are you stupid?
Why do the actresses who are selling because it is a commercial say such a stupid joke?
I want to throw it away.
For example, Yasuko Sawaguchi.
The wind is a stoner, but it's a stoner.
But such a joke is said when you go to the post office.
I can't help it.
We are the only ones who can say such a joke on the spot.
The wind is a stoner, but it's a stoner.
I'm a little confused.
It's very unpleasant to think of this as a joke.
Don't underestimate the joke.
I'm not underestimating it.
The wind is a stoner, but it's a stoner.
The wind is not in compliance with the official joke.
For example.
Why do you talk like that?
Let's say your name is poop.
It's not poop, but it's poop now.
The three horses ate the three horses.
It's not funny at all.
The three horses decided on their own.
The stoners decided on their own.
The wind is a stoner, but it's not funny at all.
Do you understand what I mean?
I understand what you mean.
It's not funny at all.
If you think it's funny and say it, you shouldn't laugh.
It's not funny if people around here say it.
Is that so?
I heard this from a friend of a friend.
When he was working at the post office,
There was a yearbook from Mr. Hamada's house.
When I looked closely, it was a picture of three families laughing.
Did you get that picture?
I don't have a picture of three families.
I took a picture of a child only.
You like that kind of picture, don't you?
If you ask me whether I like it or not, I like it.
It's just a picture of a child, isn't it?
Are you laughing at the picture of a child?
I don't know if I'm laughing or not.
If you do that, you won't send me to the yearbook.
Why don't you send me to the yearbook?
Why are you standing still?
Have you ever sent me to the yearbook?
I have.
I haven't.
But you moved to a new house, didn't you?
You're good at it.
I moved to your house in the New Year.
Why? I'm a new year's person.
If you're a new year's person, I'll send you to the yearbook.
You're lying.
Why does the old lady's bicycle brake?
The old lady's bicycle brake sounds like this.
Please tell me.
The old lady's bicycle brake is old, isn't it?
It's not being maintained.
But if a young person rides a bicycle like that, it's even more embarrassing.
There are some young girls who ride old bicycles.
The old lady's bicycle brake sounds like this.
It's hard to watch.
I've never seen it before, but there's a bicycle brake that stops the bicycle.
If you do this, the bicycle brake stops the bicycle.
It's like rubber.
That's a little different.
That's different.
It's common for young girls to ride bicycles.
That's right.
Why are high school students in the countryside wearing a helmet?
Why?
I'm sure they're wearing a helmet.
That's why it's dangerous in the mountains.
In that case, I think it's more dangerous in the city.
I've been chasing stones from above.
It's a rice field as far as you can see.
It's a blue sky.
There's nothing in the sky.
But the place you're chasing is like a cliff.
I see.
When you fall.
There's a mountain over there.
I'm sure I'm wearing a helmet.
I don't know.
I'm wearing a jersey and running.
It's definitely strange.
You can't wear a helmet when you're single, can you?
That's right.
But you don't have to wear a helmet when you play baseball, do you?
I don't know that.
Why?
There's no such dangerous sport.
I don't know where the ball will fly from.
You'll find out when you see it.
It's tough.
I can't avoid it.
You can avoid it.
It's not like it's going to fly with a liner.
Do you need a helmet?
I don't know.
If you hit a red ball, you'll get hit.
What are you going to do if you don't wear a helmet?
You're wearing a helmet.
So don't wear a helmet.
If you say that, it won't start.
What's that?
Everyone was excited when Sena came.
But for me, he's just a foreigner.
That's right.
He's just a foreigner to me.
He had a head like Zura.
He had a head like Toresu.
What's that?
You're not supposed to be driving.
I'm definitely faster.
It's like this.
He's been running for 300 kilometers.
I think I can do it.
It's 300 kilometers.
And then his head goes like this.
It's not just one person who runs 300 kilometers.
Everyone runs 300 kilometers.
If it's just one person, it's a loss.
It's not a loss.
It's a problem of whether you can do it or not.
The machine is amazing, but the person who is riding it is not.
It's the skill of the person who is riding it.
When I went to Kyosho...
Don't talk about Kyosho.
Is there a car like this in Kyosho?
Is this how you do the S-shaped crank?
It's easier.
I don't know my skills.
The instructor at the Kyosho shop said you were too fast.
That's stupid.
It's a white line.
The instructor at the Kyosho shop said,
It's too fast.
It's about 40 kilometers.
The instructor was surprised.
That's why I was dropped.
It's about 40 kilometers.
It's too fast.
Do you have a bike like that?
Are you stupid?
Do you have a bike like that at 40 kilometers?
I don't have much money.
I only have a little gas left.
I can't go home by calculation.
What does that have to do with the E1 machine?
I don't think about that.
I'm thinking about it.
I'm putting gas in the pit.
I don't have any money.
I'm working.
That's a lot of money.
What are you?