The winner is...
I did it!
What is it?
What's wrong?
3, 2, 1!
Hey!
Wait!
3, 2, 1!
The winner is...
I did it!
3, 2, 1!
The winner is...
I did it!
I don't want to lose by choosing a castle.
It's been a long time.
It's been a long time since I won.
Thank you, Kouhaku Udagashi-san!
Well, it doesn't matter.
I'm relieved that it's over.
To be continued.
Next time on Gaki no Tsukai Arahen!
Chiki-chi! 95's Young Artists!
Tatoeyo Seishiken!
I heard that there are two guests today.
The main guest today is wearing a number plate.
The first and third row.
Old man and woman.
They are the main characters.
I see.
How about you, Tatoeyo?
This...
The one with the nose hair.
How about you, Tatoeyo?
The one with the blue eyes.
You are a foreigner.
You are very Japanese.
The one with the long bangs.
Where is it?
It's short.
Next time on Gaki no Tsukai Arahen!
Chiki-chi! 95's Young Artists!
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
Young people, please come in!
Let's go in order.
Yamazaki-san, please play the number plate.
Yamazaki-san, there are two of you.
This is the Tohkai.
Tatoeyo has already started.
He has already started.
What's the number?
Number 5!
It's him.
Please come to the stage.
Yamazaki-san!
Tatoeyo!
Maneki-neko.
Yes!
Inoue-kun.
Fukudasao.
You just saw it.
It's not good.
It's not good at all.
It's not like this.
Tatoeyo is not like this.
What's the correct answer?
The correct answer is...
Is it correct?
Please tell us.
Is there a correct answer for something like this?
There is. There is.
The correct answer is...
Prince Hana.
The one who was called Prince Hana is like...
It's amazing how he nods.
Tatoeyo doesn't hurt himself.
He nods?
Yes.
He laughs and doesn't hurt anyone.
I see.
That's a good example.
That's Tatoeyo.
Inoue-kun, please come to the stage.
The next number.
What's the number?
Number 3.
Please come to the stage.
This is difficult.
It's okay if you don't cry.
I'll go on.
There's nothing.
No, no, no.
Yamazaki-san.
Please don't say there's nothing.
Yamazaki-san, that was funny.
You can come to the front and look at your face.
Everyone will come out.
I want you to say there's nothing.
There's nothing.
Next.
What's the number?
Number 13.
It's a man.
It's difficult.
Then, Tomoro-kun.
Tatoeyo.
Number 5222.
Next.
Yes, Yamazaki-san.
He's eating Japanese sake.
It's okay.
Let's go to Tatoeyo.
Tatoeyo, please.
Horse's quarter.
What are you saying?
It's okay.
He's laughing.
It's okay because he's laughing.
Don't get hurt.
Horse's quarter.
It's okay, right?
Isn't this horse's quarter?
Next.
Tanaka-kun.
Number 8.
It's here.
I don't know if it's good or bad.
Please read the atmosphere.
I'm saying something.
Tanaka.
Tatoeyo.
Sword.
Thank you very much.
End.
Yes.
Number 28.
Please.
Yes.
Thin forehead.
Bald.
He's laughing.
I'm sorry.
His reaction is fast.
Tanaka.
Yes.
I'm looking for a part-time job.
I don't know.
I understand.
Let's just go with the flow.
It's okay.
Shall we start over from the opening?
I don't know yet.
Yamazaki-san.
Yes.
Are you wearing glasses?
I'm wearing glasses.
There are so many.
There are so many people like me.
Really?
Yes.
I wanted to say this.
What number?
Number 11.
You're looking at him.
Yes.
Yamazaki-san, give an example.
Death.
No.
It's completely different.
Is it different?
Number 11 is a predator.
Number 20 is a woman.
Go ahead.
I wonder what this person is.
Yes.
Excuse me.
I'm going.
I'm back.
I succeeded in laughing.
It's a success.
There are so many people like me.
I finally laughed with applause.
Thank you very much.
You are in the picture.
Number 31.
You're in the picture too.
Yes.
Yamazaki-san.
Takoyaki.
Are you aware of it?
Why?
Is it cute? Takoyaki.
This is a girlfriend of Hangyodon.
You.
Yes.
You are in the picture.
Thank you very much.
Number 21 is good.
Number 21.
It's the birth of labor.
That's...
What is it?
Number 10.
I don't know if this is the last one.
Now.
Yes.
Nobita-kun in the picture.
It's some kind of bait, isn't it?
That's not good, Takoyaki.
That's...
Let's say number 24.
Number 24 seems to have something.
Electricity?
Hey, wait a minute.
Don't ask.
What is it?
Electricity?
But, well...
Electricity...
It's not bad.
Then, say it out loud.
This is...
It's some kind of seed.
He's laughing so hard.
Ladies and gentlemen.
I always do it like this.
Hello, hello.
Well...
Today, I can't do it anymore.
What?
My voice is so hoarse, isn't it?
Is it a cold?
It's terrible.
My voice isn't hoarse at all.
It's piling up here.
It's not at all.
I really wanted to take a rest.
When I think of the faces of the guests today,
I can't take a rest.
They're waiting for me.
Everyone is waiting for me.
I'm sorry.
Well, that kind of feeling is important.
I don't mind.
I don't mind at all.
No, really.
This job is really hard.
I can't take a rest.
I've recovered though.
I was a little sick at the end of the year.
You're still warm today, aren't you?
Let's hug.
That's nice.
Come here.
This is nice.
If no one was here, I would have gone.
But there are people here.
There are people here.
That's right.
This is my handwritten letter, isn't it?
It's okay.
I obviously didn't know.
Why is it your handwritten letter?
I had a fever the day before the baseball game at the end of the year.
I took a car alone.
It was 39.3 degrees.
I went to the emergency hospital.
Don't say that.
It's true.
I was waiting for two people.
It was cold in the corridor.
I'm sure it's true.
You're the only one who has a sore throat.
There are a lot of people waiting for you at the hospital.
That's right.
There are a lot of people.
There are people like this.
Are you okay, Murakami?
I'm going to take it off now.
Please be patient.
While Murakami was going somewhere,
I took it off.
Murakami, if you feel sick, please go.
Murakami, I'm sorry.
It's too late.
Please help me.
You're talking to yourself.
I don't need anything.
It's winter.
I stopped you.
I had a fever and it was hard, but I laughed while listening to it.
There are a lot of people.
My grandmother came to me.
Something's wrong.
What's wrong?
Something's wrong with my head.
You talk to yourself.
You're laughing at everything.
Close your eyes.
I've had a fever twice.
I had a fever before, too.
Please wait a moment.
I can't pee.
That's hard.
I'm sick, but I'm laughing.
There are a lot of people who are sick.
I'm still fine.
That's hard.
I can't breathe.
It's a nuisance at night.
It's like a hungry chicken.
I can't breathe.
I have something to say.
I haven't had a fever in a long time.
Thank you very much.
If I win the game and choose red, you have to say it's white.
If you lose, it's not cool.
It's not cool.
If I win, you have to say it's cold.
If you lose, it's not cool.
My staff gave me a mask when I arrived in Hawaii.
I heard you were in Hawaii.
When I arrived, I put on a mask and said it was a party.
I'm glad I was asked.
I said I wouldn't wear it.
He didn't say anything.
I didn't see it.
I'm working, so I can't see it.
What's going on in Hawaii?
There was no party.
Is there anything in Hawaii that makes you feel good?
I'm just trying to satisfy my sexual desire.
I'll leave it at that.
What?
Are you going to put on a mask?
It's okay.
Why?
It's because it's hard.
I'm having a hard time.
Drink it.
I'm really sorry.
I heard it's selling it.
At the Blue Sera shop.
What kind of day is it?
It's not usually sold, is it?
I can't stand it.
I've been saying this all year round.
What have you been doing?
I've been doing nothing.
Downtown's Matsumoto-san and Hamada-san are still wrong.
Downtown's bigger one is...
Still wrong?
The bigger one is Matsumoto-san, and the smaller one is Hamada-san. Is there any other way to remember them?
Well, Oba-han is still like that.
There are a lot of people who mistake it for Ucchan-nan-chan, right?
Yes, yes, that's enough.
I can afford it.
Ucchan-nan-chan and Matsugawa...
Matsugawa?
He's from the far north.
Is there any other way to remember them other than the bigger one and the smaller one?
There are a lot of things, right?
What things?
There are a lot of things.
What could it be?
There are a lot of things, right?
There are like 50,000 things.
What could it be?
There are things that are tattooed and things that aren't.
Which one is tattooed?
Why?
Are they tattooed?
Something like that.
I see.
There are things that have a saber.
That's easy to understand.
And...
And what else is there?
There are things that are tattooed on the skin.
What things?
There are things that are tattooed on the eyes of the sapphire.
Something that isn't tattooed.
That's a way to understand them.
The first one.
Yes, yes, yes.
Those things that are tattooed on the sapphire.
That's what my grandmother says.
There's no mistake.
First of all, there's nothing to be mistaken about.
Why do old people tremble?
Do they tremble?
Old people tremble.
Small dogs and old people tremble.
That's not because it's cold.
What?
It's not because it's cold.
It doesn't matter.
It's not because it's cold that old people tremble.
Old people tremble in the middle of the summer or in the spring.
It's because they're motivated, isn't it?
That's right.
It's like, I'm still alive.
If you think you're still alive, don't you tremble?
What is that? Please tell me.
It's because they're trying to go somewhere, right?
They're trying to do it with their blood.
What?
The pulling power is working somewhere.
They're stopping it.
They're trying to do it with their blood, right?
It's just a matter of time.
What is the most painful language you've ever heard?
I'm Kiri Kiri.
That's strange.
But if you think about it, it seems like there are a lot of repeating words, right?
Is that so?
Yes.
Don't you think so?
That's not true.
Zuki zuki. Uzu uzu.
What is uzu uzu?
It doesn't seem painful.
Uzu uzu, doesn't it seem painful?
Princess Princess.
Now, Toyokawa Etsushi. Is that okay?
I don't know.
Toyokawa Etsushi, is that okay?
Toyokawa...
Why does it say Toyokawa Etsushi here?
You're the one who said that.
Toyokawa Etsushi is a neutral guy like Takeda Shinji.
How can you be neutral?
I can't change that.
I can't make that face.
But you see, sexy guys, right?
I'm always called sexy.
Who?
I was called that when I was in elementary school.
You were called sexy when you were in elementary school?
I was called sexy.
I was called after the Segawa guy.
In English.
Oh, really?
Yes, yes, yes.
I'm from Matsumoto, so it's different.
I'm always called sexy.
I was called sexy after Segawa.
Yes, I said that.
You said that too?
You're really sexy, so you look like you've run away.
Right?
Really?
You're not good at all.
Vintage fashion doesn't suit you.
Wait a minute.
Have you ever done it?
I've done it a lot.
I'm always called leather.
People say I don't know if I'm a man or a woman.
People say that to you?
Yes, yes, yes.
People still call me that.
When I say, huh?
They say, huh?
I'm always called leather.