Chikichiki Magic Taneakashi Daigassen!
Good evening. Today we are going to talk about Magic Taneakashi Daigassen.
Let's introduce our guests.
First of all, Magi Shiro.
Next to him is Matsumoto Shito.
Hello, nice to meet you.
Today we are going to do some magic.
We are going to show you how to do it.
I am good at it.
How many types can you do?
I can do about 7 types.
Shut up!
You are not a bad guy.
That's why you can eat, right?
I will never go to the same place again.
Today we are going to do some magic.
Let's call the teacher.
She is Sumie Sensei.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you too.
First question.
There are 6 cards with a dice mark here.
We have a dice here.
Please roll the dice.
The person with the black jumper.
3.
Please roll the 3 cards.
Please clean up the rest of the cards.
This is not to show the front.
This is to show the back.
The back is red.
This is also red.
All of them are red.
Only this one is blue.
This is the magic.
This is easy.
Really?
This is magic.
Can I do it again?
You can't do it again.
You are the president.
Please go back to your seat.
The answer is...
What is the correct answer?
There is a dice mark here.
So...
On the dice?
There is no 3.
No matter how many you roll?
There is no hand.
I know that.
I think this is right.
He quickly gave us the blue contact.
He gave us the blue contact?
Even if you look at it, it is blue.
I don't know.
This is that.
Is that okay?
Even if I roll this,
I think the 3 will come out.
If you roll 10 times, it will be 10 times.
What?
The 5 came out.
What does that mean?
What?
As expected, it is Trump.
Hey!
You just raised your voice.
You are such an old man.
What is the correct answer?
It is a secret.
You don't look at it much because it is night.
I am looking at it!
The 3 cards have different colors.
So...
For example, if the opponent takes the red card,
I only showed the blue card.
I don't do it until I do it.
Because I am the president.
Is it okay to show it so far?
It's okay.
Because you are the president.
Because I am the president.
I see.
It's funny.
Final Tuesday
This program is brought to you by these sponsors.
Yes, the second solution.
Now, a lot of summoning has depends on you right now.
If you bend your arms, it's a super magic.
I won't bend my arms today.
I have a card for this kind of telepathy experiment.
Matsumoto-kun, please take it.
When you take it, look at it and remember it.
Put it on your chest.
That's right.
It's a telepathy experiment.
I felt it.
It's not a curved line.
I don't know if I have to bend my arms.
What is a curved line?
Think about it strongly.
I don't want to think about it.
It's drawn in a straight line.
First of all, I can see the small bar next to it.
It's not one.
The other one is vertical.
Yes.
Can I look at it?
Oh!
Come on!
Don't you know this?
Think about it!
What is the answer?
Don!
Matsumoto-san and Guru.
I see.
I don't think this is wrong.
What is it?
Telepathy!
I don't want to do telepathy!
The correct answer is...
It doesn't matter what order it is.
You need to think about it.
Remember all the order.
If you move five pieces,
the bottom one is a star.
The top one is a triangle.
You need to remember it.
It's not telepathy.
I can't do this.
Do you need memory?
What kind of brain did you use?
I didn't know that.
I'm good at the trick of Trump.
How do you know that?
I didn't know that.
You are the captain.
There is a piece of Trump.
Pull it from here.
Remember this.
Show it to the camera.
This one?
You can't see it.
Did you remember?
Put it in here.
This is the opposite.
Like this.
I mixed it by mistake.
Mix it and hit it.
From the 52 pieces.
The ace of hearts.
How is it?
I don't have any balls.
The show has started.
What do you mean?
It has started.
It has ended.
Did you watch it?
It's not interesting.
I don't watch it.
I have been doing research.
When did you do research?
I have done research.
You are lying.
You shouldn't have done it.
Why?
I am curious.
How many types of people's expressions are there?
I have done research.
Crying, laughing, getting angry.
This is the basic.
There is something else.
There is a face that can't say anything.
Do it.
A face that can't say anything.
No.
That's not it.
What kind of face can't say anything?
A face that can't say anything.
What is that?
I was in a car.
A young man was driving.
He was walking in front of me.
He was angry.
His face was like this.
His face?
His face.
There is a face that can't say anything.
He must have been irritated.
That day.
There were a lot of bad things.
He was angry.
He couldn't stand it.
What is that face that can't say anything?
He was angry.
He was surprised.
His face was amazing.
Why do you keep looking at me?
He was like this.
Say it again?
Do it in front of me.
Let me do it.
I don't know if I can.
The face.
I will try.
I have some sea there.
Let me do it.
I don't know how to do it.
I will try.
It's like you're wearing it
Take it off
Okay
Your face should be facing the camera
How many times do I have to do it?
No, this way
Let's go
You're so slimy
That's not it
You shouldn't think like that
You should've...
You should've cried
You're so slimy
How many times did I have to do it?
I didn't cry at all
I was thinking I understood
So I canceled
Sorry but I can't say it
It's okay even if you can't say it
Recently was fun
When I rode a car in Osaka
When I rode a car
It lost control
That was for female roles
That person had driving
The man by my side
didn't do anything bad
The guy behind me was angry too. He was looking at me from behind.
He was looking at me from the side.
He was angry too, so he opened the window and there was a fight.
It was a fist fight.
I don't need that.
The guy on the other side was angry.
He was angry at me.
Who are you talking to?
He was angry. He was angry at me because of this car.
He was angry, but he was laughing at me who was sitting next to him.
I see.
If you were an amateur, you might have complained.
That's right.
At the moment you opened the window.
But when we met, it was you.
That's right.
I thought it was you.
With an angry face.
With an angry face, I thought it was you.
And then?
I laughed.
Let's try it.
It's still going on.
I laughed.
I laughed, but the guy who was sitting next to me said,
What the hell is this?
Then he left with a very pitiful face.
Let's try it.
Try it.
I'll sit next to you.
That's right.
Don't say, what the hell is this?
I'm sorry.
What the hell is this?
That's not it.
You.
What the hell is this?
You're bad.
I'm going home.
Look at that guy.
What the hell is this when you laugh?
Say it first.
I don't know what's going on.
I'm going home.
What the hell is this?
Let's try it.
What the hell is this when you laugh?
Hey, hey, you kicked me.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Wait.
You kicked me at the free talk.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Wait.
What the hell is this when you laugh?
Say it first.
I don't know what's going on.
That's right.
What the hell is this?
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Let's try it.
Where are you looking?
I can't organize it.
Say it.
I feel like I can do it with that face.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey, hey, hey.
That's not it.
I'm sorry.
I can't do it again.
That's not it.
That's not it at all.
Why are you putting your tongue out?
That's not it.
What the hell is that?
Do it like that.
This is too much.
I don't understand it anymore.
It must be this way.
How miserable.
That's right.
It's interesting what humans look like when they think this way.
Japanese people are said without any emotions when they are abroad.
But Japanese people really don't say it properly.
With facial expressions.
Japanese people are really bad at cooking.
There are only three things Japanese people are good at.
That's why this is no good.
Japanese people are often told that they don't know what they are thinking.
That's good.
Even if it's a sour face, you don't have to do it.
Try a sour face.
It stinks.
Do a sweet and sour face.
Try it.
A sweet and sour face.
Try a sweet and sour face.
Why are you looking at me?
I'm doing a sweet and sour face, right?
Why?
It's a sweet and sour face for youth.
You should eat something.
Why are you looking at me?
Why?
I don't know if it's good or bad.
Maybe you can do it.
What are you talking about?
I don't know if it's good or bad.
Maybe you can do it.
That's not it.
Let's move on.
Why are you like that?
You're not like that when you start with a sour face.
What?
From a sour face?
What are you talking about?
It's a sour face.
I brought it.
Who is it?
Thank you.
How about you?
There's nothing.
What is this?
I'm going to give this to the person I introduced on the show.
This is the person who does this kind of work.
Really?
Yes.
Thank you very much.
Please do your best.
I'm going to give this to the person I'm going to introduce on the show.
I'm a housewife.
I enjoy watching you every week.
I'm watching you.
When I look at the two of you, I feel like I'm watching Yumeji Itoshikoi.
Do you think so in Tokyo?
Do you know Itoshikoi?
When we first came out, we were told that we looked like Itoshikoi.
It's a teacher.
I was waiting for you to become a bigger entertainer.
I'm glad you're here.
I'm going to show you the most authentic comedy.
Don't forget that you're not just a young kid.
Thank you very much.
I'm going to give this mother a ring.
Listen to what I said the other day.
There was an old man in the train waiting for the express train to pass.
He waved at me.
So I said hello to him.
And then I realized that he had a line.
Why do men do this?
Wait a minute.
He was waving at me.
What do you mean he was waving at you?
He was waving at me from above.
He was waving at me from below.
I thought he was looking at me.
It's a sign.
Why do men do this?
I don't know.
He wasn't waving at me.
He didn't wave at me from below.
Have you ever done that?
No.
Good luck.
Have you ever done that?
No.
I've heard about it from you.
I'm doing it off the frame.
Why are you doing it from below?
I've heard about it from you.
I've done it.
You haven't done it.
You've done it in the car, right?
You've done it in the car.
You were waiting for your turn.
A woman was driving in the corner of the street.
You've done it in the car, right?
A long time ago.
Hang on.
You could have done it.
I've heard about it.
I've heard of it.
You've done it in the car.
I haven't done it.
Are you a monkey?
That was 9 years ago, right after I entered this world
The woman I was dating at that time was in her early years
In her early years, she was wearing a kimono with her hair like this
What?
Oh, it was New Year's Day
She was going to give me a kimono and a hair
I took her to the farm and waited for her
I waited for her and I couldn't go home
When I looked down, she was not there
She said she was tired
She said she was sleepy
I didn't do anything
I just wanted to hold her
When she was sleepy, there were not many men
Right?
When she was sleepy, she was harder than iron
That's it
I'm waiting for your letter
That's good
Let's go home
That's enough
Look at my finger
Look at the letter
It's harder than iron
Because it's diamond
That's what I wanted to say
That's why I wanted to say it
That's all
Thank you very much
Please come again
From now on, let's listen to the music
It's easy to go home
It's hard to go home
What kind of music do you want?
I don't want to make a fuss
I don't want to go home
Right?
Let's listen to it
I don't think it will come out today
You didn't prepare it?
Will it come out?
Oh, it will
That's what I wanted to say
Thank you very much
We want to go home
Thank you
Please come again
Let's listen to it again
It's cold these days
It's cold
It's cold at night
You have to be careful not to catch a cold
I caught a cold and went to sleep
Why did you catch a cold and go to sleep?
You don't have a blanket?
I have a blanket
I caught a cold and went to sleep
That's all
Thank you very much
Let's listen to it again
What?
You don't have a blanket?
Let's listen to it again
The meeting place of the
The meeting place of the word
Are you stupid?
Let's make it clear
What?
It's a water bridge, right?
It's funny
Harakawa Nihonari Station
At 12 o'clock on November 10th
We will prepare it
If we open it
We will get 4.9 billion yen
If we have that much money
We will think about it
You have a lot of money, right?
What?
I don't have money at all
And an assistant
I want to give you more
I will give you a little
If you give me now
I might be able to go to Nijio Prefecture
That's all
Thank you very much
Thank you
This program was provided by the sponsor you are watching