THIS PROGRAM INCLUDES CONTENT THAT
MAY BE INAPPROPRIATE FOR SOME VIEWERS.
PLEASE ENJOY THE SHOW
AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION.
The "mental" in Documental
is about mental toughness?
I haven't stayed on long enough
to feel mentally pressured yet.
I always get eliminated early.
I haven't been pushed so far
that I got all stressed. Not yet.
When it starts,
it's like you keep on bombing, right?
But that might make me laugh, too.
The fact that nobody's laughing.
I laugh at almost anything.
Of course I laugh at funny things,
but I laugh when they're not funny, too.
Nipple beams. They point outwards. Heart.
You laughed.
When you look at people who do comedy,
you'll find they're the kind of people
who have quite the imagination.
They laugh at even the simplest of things
because they over-interpret them.
That happens a lot.
Isn't it amazing? It goes like this.
It's that slow?
-By the time you get to...
-Huh?
-Yellow.
-Okay. Sorry.
It was such a natural laugh.
-A word for this photo.
-i love you.
Wait a minute!
You're eliminated!
Is Iio laughing?
I'll make that an orange card.
Why did I put that in my mouth?
He endured so much.
Here we go.
And your voice got so small...
That came too soon.
Is the meat ready?
-It's ready.
-Thank you.
-Do you want some?
-Yes.
Kurosawa, you don't have a mirror, do you?
-This is all I have.
-Can I borrow it?
-Sure.
-Thanks.
There's a mirror back there.
But I shouldn't be away
for too long, right?
-You're gonna wipe it off there?
-Well, yeah.
I see.
You only use one sheet?
One sheet can't be enough.
-Actually, one sheet's enough.
-Is that so?
Surprisingly enough.
-It comes off in one swipe, right?
-It does.
-Your makeup remover is amazing.
-But...
You can't wipe it quickly.
You have to let it soak as you go,
and slowly scrape it off.
-You figured that out by yourself?
-Yeah. You push down...
It's coming off!
-Push down, and scrape off.
-Your face look smaller.
-Really?
-Your face looks smaller.
That's nice.
-It's ready to serve.
-Thank you!
-Wow!
-Thank you.
We have meat!
-Here comes our meat.
-Wow, it looks so good!
-Here. I'll get some sauce.
-Okay.
-It needs sauce.
-Thank you, Miyasako.
-Wow!
-Awesome!
This looks so yummy!
-The restaurant came to us!
-This has to be good!
-The sauce looks great!
-He made the sauce?
-Awesome!
-It looks yummy!
It looks really yummy. It really does.
You can't eat it.
Huh?
I'm the one who cooked it.
All I said was, "It's ready."
But you didn't pay for the meat.
But they said I could eat what I wanted,
and that I could cook.
Only I cooked it.
-But you said it was a treat for everyone.
-You did.
I meant that showing you how I cook
was a treat.
-Huh?
-So we can't eat any?
-No, because it's mine.
-There's too much to eat by yourself.
-I'll leave some.
You don't go to a restaurant and
eat other people's leftovers, do you?
This is seriously tasty.
I made a thick sauce,
so it wraps around the meat.
-You know that Okinawan sauce?
-A.1.
I made it similar to A.1. sauce.
You made it a bit sour?
It's delicious!
-We've waited enough.
-Let's eat.
Whoa!
He stabbed us.
I'm full. I'm tossing this.
-You can't do that.
-It would be a waste.
Well, then...
Pair up and perform gags for your partner.
-Perform gags?
-Why do we have to do that?
You want to eat, right?
I don't want to fall victim.
What do we have to do?
Perform a gag at full-throttle.
It can be someone else's.
Someone else's gag? That's not right.
Give us an example first.
I don't know anybody else's gag.
But I don't have any originals.
Yes, you do. It goes like this.
That's his, all right.
-Is that a gag?
-Must be.
-It's just my self-introduction.
-To start things off.
Saying "I'm Miyasako" is an introduction.
But you go...
-Right?
-Your introduction gag.
-That one.
-Which one?
-You can eat some.
-Thanks.
-I don't get it.
-Me neither.
-Because I did a gag.
-Someone else's gag?
-That's how it works?
-Yep.
This looks seriously tasty.
That is crazy tasty.
What the hell?
-He ate it this time.
-What was that first thing?
It was a practice swing. Like in golf.
-For eating?
-Yeah.
A practice swing for eating?
"First Witness, Chopsticks Expert."
-Go ahead.
-Thank you.
-That was okay?
-Anything goes?
-Thanks.
-That was perfect, right?
Here I go.
Delicious!
I knew it.
Wow!
-It's really tasty.
-Yeah, it really is.
How about that?
I'm here to play "The Nose."
-Nose? A runny nose?
-He's "The Runny Nose"!
-Kukky laughed, right?
-Who was that?
-Was it me?
-Probably.
-Hang on. What about Itoda?
-Maybe.
-For this face?
-Which face?
It may be me.
Mr. Matsumoto.
I stayed silent and kept a straight face.
There are two this time.
I think Daigo deserves
a point for that one.
Yes.
Kukky was...
Well, let's take a look at Kukky.
I think he was laughing.
-But it was hard to tell under his makeup.
-I see.
-The makeup isn't a trick to hide.
-I know. Let's take a look.
How about that?
I'm here to play "The Nose."
-I held it back. I sure did.
-You think so?
-Did he hold it back?
-I did, right?
What do you think? Was it okay?
-Only just.
-I think it was okay.
But there's one more.
Itoda was close, I think.
-Me, right?
-Yeah.
How about that?
I'm here to play "The Nose."
What do you think?
-How should I call that?
-You think that's laughing?
You're defending yourself like that
a little too often, Itoda.
-I do that a lot?
-Yeah.
-Was it too much to overlook?
-Really?
There, there.
I understand.
Is Kurochan the only one?
-He has no cards?
-For the moment, yes.
-What are you doing here?
-Eh?
-If trash like you wins, I'll beat you up.
-Don't call me trash, or stardust.
He didn't. And you haven't done a thing.
That's not true!
You're right.
I think Kurochan is on zero points.
-He made Fujimoto laugh.
-Yeah. Well, I did it to myself.
And the thing with the milk.
If he keeps this up,
who knows what'll happen?
-He keeps getting us on the counterattack.
-Yeah.
-We give him the ammo.
-Exactly.
-It's your fault for setting him up.
-Yeah, you're right.
-Here we go. It's restart time.
-The meat has a real sweetness to it.
-Yummy.
-Delicious.
I think no one is expecting
a zombie to come in now.
-Like it?
-It's delicious.
-It's sweet.
-Right?
This will be a first for this show.
We'll have one zombie trying to take down
the other nine.
Here we go.
Zombie Time!
I forgot about that!
Just Nobu, right?
-Just Nobu?
-I think so.
He's the only one, right?
If no one laughs, that may make me laugh.
-Exactly.
-On the flip side...
Hey!
Hey, stop it!
I can't take it anymore!
It's insane!
The zombie room
is filled with water this high.
The zombie room...
Up to here...
The whole time.
-Look at his back.
-It's not wet.
-You're right.
-His back is dry.
-How did...
-Only his front...
Were you floating like this?
No, it was up here!
But your back is dry.
Huh?
Maybe I was like this.
Like I said, right?
Do not enter that room!
The zombie room is really scary!
-Did it start to flood after you arrived?
-No.
-It was from the start?
-They threw it in like this.
So it was after you arrived.
They can fill the room
by throwing in water?
This whole time?
This whole time.
The staff here are crazy!
And in the water, there are...
-What?
-What's in it?
Knights with spears. Doing this.
-Knights?
How do those underwater knights breathe?
Right.
-Something like this.
-They come equipped.
-Like a ninja?
-So they aren't ghost knights?
They're packed on all four sides.
Doing this.
All four sides?
Knights with spears?
Really, be careful.
-Okay.
-He's leaving?
And...
And?
Mao Daichi gives her best wishes.
-For real?
-Wow.
-I wonder why.
-Did you see her?
Thanks.
Does she know we're doing this?
She knows. Apparently she's a fan.
Did she watch any of this today?
Apparently she did.
-Really?
-On the monitor?
What did she laugh at?
She's sitting behind Mr. Matsumoto.
-What?
-Right now?
As a special guest?
-That's a first.
-They're co-hosts?
It's a Matsumoto-Daichi special program.
This show has changed.
So both are the MC?
It's a double MC, I think.
Is that so?
Flowerfield High School's cleanup hitter.
He probably doesn't hit many.
You shouldn't do that
with Ms. Daichi's gift.
She's watching us now, right?
That wouldn't feel nice.
-I think it's up to the individual.
-Is that so?
-Yeah, they can leave anytime.
-It's up to them.
-So we can move on and do our own thing?
-And forget about him.
-Oh, I want to eat some.
-Aren't you leaving?
It's delicious! What is this?
-It may be the best steak I've ever had.
-It's so good.
-Maybe it's the sauce.
-Yeah, that sauce is awesome.
-It would go great in a steak bowl.
-Yeah.
-Right?
-With lettuce at the bottom.
I'll go back once!
I'll retreat once.
And I'll be back.
Terryman and meat...
-That steak suits you.
-Terryman really likes meat.
It really suits you.
Depending on your emotional state,
that zombie could've made you cry.
It was a tearjerker.
But he showed great mental strength.
He did.
But I bet he goes home,
drinks a highball and cries.
He'll scream in the middle of the night.
Things kind of stopped.
-Things kind of stopped.
-They have a bit.
I'll sit myself down,
then roll back up and become Kaoru Yumi.
Kukky...
-Who are you?
You should know by looking at me, damn it.
I was in the band Bakufu Slump.
Which one?
I'm BBQ Wasada.
-Was there such a member?
-I don't think so.
-I remember Papala.
-BBQ Wasada?
I'm Papala.
You changed it?
-Did Papala look like this?
-No.
Is that a hat?
It's a hat.
-It's a piece of tape.
-It's a hat.
-It's a hat?
-Why are you here?
-It's a hat... Huh?
What are you doing here?
I heard you were doing
a good location shoot.
Oh, he's that director, Shinya Yamamoto.
-On location?
-On location.
Songs...
Songs are...
You can really feel it, right?
I said that looking at great scenery
like this might give me good songs.
You mean that it might inspire
an idea for a good song?
-Is he BBQ Suekichi?
-No, BBQ...
Actually, he went through some changes
and now he's...
-I'm Funky Sueyoshi.
-Funky...
-Your voice is back to normal.
-Why?
Are you Papala?
Are you asking me?
I'm Sumiko Nishioka.
Right?
-The dominatrix?
-Sumiko Nishioka?
Of Nabe-Pro.
For real? At this timing?
Can I return to normal?
Do as you wish.
That didn't go well.
It was a little complicated, right?
The way I incorporated so many things.
Bakufu Slump was a bit hard
to comprehend, right?
-The focus kept shifting.
-You're right.
You kept changing course.
We didn't know how to react to you.
-I didn't think it out.
-Think first next time.
You're so right.
-Good point.
-I get it.
He's back.
He spent ages back there.
This is all we get?
Unbelievable.
-No way.
-He's serious.
After all we've been through?
After such a long wait, is that all?
I started feeling hot, so I changed.
But wasn't that other shirt cooler?
I wonder what he watched growing up.
-What?
-Like, what comedy shows?
Firstly, what is that?
They're overalls.
-I know.
-I was getting hot.
Huh? Is that all?
Yes.
What's funny about them?
What's funny?
Hang on...
We have to make each other laugh, right?
You got changed into those overalls,
but what's funny about them?
What's funny?
It's not like that...
-You're not trying to be funny?
-No.
I just changed because I was hot.
-We're not kids, you know?
-Yeah.
You're not kids?
We're adults, so that won't make us laugh.
As an example.
Is that a paradox?
That's not quite a paradox...
-Your sides are open.
-Huh?
-The sides are open.
-Open?
-Significantly open.
-Here. Here.
-Look at your sides.
-Here.
Why? Is it broken?
He's so annoying.
Is something going on?
-Who's that?
-Who is...
Who are you?
My name is Daisuke Kishi.
I'm at Uzumasa Studios, on a break.
-I'm just taking a walk.
-Without taking your wig off?
I'm going back to the set after my break.
How long is the break?
-Eighty-three hours.
-That's super long.
If you have three days off, you should...
-Take the wig off.
-And go home.
-Look. Your head hurts.
-His wig hurts.
But I have to go back.
-Did you buy something?
-What is that?
This is...
It's a hamburger made of fish.
-A fish burger?
-A fish burger.
-A Filet-O-Fish.
-I got three of them.
-You'll eat three of the same burger?
-You could've made one of them meat.
Isn't that shirt too big?
It's size XS.
-XS?
-It's XS.
You mean XL, right?
-In which country?
It's made in Africa.
-Are they that big?
-Yeah, the pattern looks African.
It's an African shirt.
What role are you playing?
-The one I'm filming now?
-What's the title?
The film I'm shooting now is called
Daisuke Kishi: The Male Ninja-Girl
So you're the star.
A "Male Ninja-Girl"?
-You have an 83-hour break?
-Even though you're the star?
-They're filming inserts now.
-Insert shots?
How many inserts do they need?
-Maybe he's good at swordplay.
-Right. Can you show us?
Okay.
-If he's the star...
-There must be many baddies.
-He must be really good.
-I am.
-Can anyone start?
-Anyone can start.
Hold on a minute.
-His wig hurts. I knew it.
-It must be the wrong size.
It's too small.
That's why it hurts so much.
Moving around makes it hurt.
-Are you a poor swordsman?
-Yes.
Ouch.
Hold on a minute.
What is this?
-We thought that, as a period film star...
-You'd be good at swordplay.
You started all this.
So...
Behavior like that isn't...
-That was cheap.
-That was scary.
That was dangerous.
Adults shouldn't do things like that.
Watch out.
-He's a two-sword man?
-He looks strong. Dual wielding.
The eyes must hurt.
-Amazing.
-He's good.
-He's strong.
-I knew he'd be good.
-Thank you.
-What happened to that mirror?
-Kurochan, is that really...
-Yes?
...because you're hot?
Yes.
-Aren't you hot?
-If that's true, then I'm sorry.
I spoke inappropriately.
-I'm so hot.
-Is it that hot?
Aren't you hot?
-Why don't you undress?
-That hot?
-Can I undress?
-Sure.
It's so hot...
Who laughs at that?
Huh?
-How was it?
-You know.
Were you watching?
And before we know it...
Yeah, there's not much time left.
-It was an ice bucket challenge.
-Does anybody still do that?
Who tagged you?
I'm not quite sure.
You did it without knowing?
Sorry about the wait!
Well, well.
I'm sorry to have kept you waiting.
Thanks for waiting, everyone.
Let me solve your problems.
Okay? Go ahead.
I truly am sorry to have kept you waiting.
-You'll listen to our problems?
-And give advice.
About anything.
-Anything? Including love and work?
-Even how to lose weight.
Well, actually...
Shoulders get stiff in your forties,
and I'm pushing 50 now.
Mine gets sore. It's hard to lift my arm.
What should I do?
Eat sumo stew.
Sumo stew.
-That was a quick response.
-It was.
Eat more vegetables.
-Sumo stew has a lot of vegetables, right?
-That's right. Yes.
-Next.
-Well...
-I live in an apartment.
-You live in an apartment. Okay.
It's actually quite a nice
apartment, however,
my neighbor's dog is very noisy.
Eat piping hot sumo stew. Okay?
Really hot.
Eat sumo stew.
You get irritated because you're hungry.
Eat sumo stew. Right? That'll fix it.
-Is sumo stew the miracle cure?
-Yes, it is.
Pro wrestlers eat it too, right?
It has vegetables, meat, fish. Everything.
-I have a toothache.
-A toothache?
Eat sumo stew.
On the left side.
The right side hurts?
Eat sumo stew on the left.
Right? It's good at improving
your blood circulation, too.
-Sumo stew cures everything?
-Sumo stew.
Sumo stew fixes everything.
I owe everything to sumo stew.
-So, you done sumo?
-Huh?
No, wrestling.
-Arm wrestling.
-Arm wrestling?
Arm wrestling.
-How are your stats?
-My stats? Well...
Six wins...
27 losses...
937 ties.
-So many ties.
-Wow.
-That's a lot of ties.
-It sure is.
-You can tie in arm wrestling?
-You can. Scary, isn't it?
-Do you eat sumo stew?
-I eat sumo stew.
-You eat but you're weak?
-That's what helps me draw.
It's too scary to go without.
-What kind of sumo stew do you like?
-What kind?
Good question. What's your name?
I'm Terryman.
Terryman! That's nice.
What flavor sumo stew?
I like my mom's recipe.
-You like your mom's sumo stew?
-Enough with the Terryman character.
What is all this?
I'm trying to figure it out, too.
But I want to eat sumo stew. Right now.
-So that's how you feel.
-I see.
I need to eat sumo stew
more than anyone, right?
-Is that it?
-Yes.
What's he doing?
The ice bucket challenge.
-I think he should do it.
-Yeah.
Okay, here I go.
Miss Mako!
I'm cold! I'm cold! I'm cold!
Sumo stew! If you're cold, eat sumo stew!
-Sumo stew!
Ooh, sumo stew!
He's good.
-Are you cold?
-I'm cold.
Of course he's cold.
Want to borrow my T-shirt?
-May I?
-Sure.
Wear my T-shirt if you're cold.
How many did he bring?
He was wearing two.
I'm cold. I'm cold. I'm cold.
The wind. It's so cold.
It's cold. So cold...
You drank it?
You shouldn't do that.
It's full of minerals.
-He swallowed.
-Because it's made of seaweed.
I'm fine.
-Seaweed?
-It's made of seaweed.
-Is that sex lube?
-It's sex lube...
-Drink it next time you're ill. It works.
-Is that so?
But he told you to eat sumo stew.
You shouldn't drink sex lube.
-Eat sumo stew.
-Sumo stew!
-Have you ever drank this?
-No. I eat sumo stew.
I can't watch this.
What's wrong with him?
What are you doing?
-What are you doing, seriously?
-Why are you chewing?
Because it's hard to swallow.
-Like jelly.
-What category of humor does that fit in?
It makes me sick.
-Do you have a headache?
-I'm just a little feverish.
You keep saying that.
-Do we have a thermometer?
-It's okay.
Let me feel your head.
-Your head's hotter.
-Ouch!
Huh? Who hit me?
He forgot.
Why did you hit me?
Because your head was hotter.
By the way, you know...
We're not getting any Zombie Time.
It's because he's alone. You know...
-I see.
-It's hard to do it alone.
So we need to increase
the number of zombies, right?
Enough is enough. We need to make a move.
-Okay.
-Well, well, well...
-Well, well, well.
This is hard.
I brought a costume, but...
I doubt I'll get a chance to wear it.
Can someone wear it for me?
Like who?
It has to be someone that fits.
Daigo.
This is it.
That'll suit...
-Daigo.
-Or perhaps maybe Iio.
Me?
It's a high cut leotard.
-Is that all?
-Yes.
-You're showing it first?
Iio or Daigo will wear it.
If Kurosawa makes a choice, we'll wear it.
-Then, Fujimoto.
-Why?
-That's not right. Why?
-It would be a waste otherwise.
But why choose me all of a sudden?
Didn't you say either Daigo or Iio?
You might as well.
What do you think?
It will be super funny.
-And it's gold.
-Nice color.
If it was silver, maybe not,
but it's gold.
This?
-But, yes...
-And it's flashy.
What's going on?
He's watching something.
It's his mother.
-His mother-in-law?
-He really likes her.
He has photos, too.
Is it a video?
Looking like this at age 60 is amazing.
-She's sexy.
-Maybe she really is a witch.
-Yeah.
-She sure is.
What's he doing?
Haranishi...
-Haranishi came, too.
-Half of Haranishi.
-Haranishi is...
-He's hiding.
This DVD's amazing.
I'm so happy you wore it for me.
What's with the traffic jam?
-His belly button looks weird.
-It's like a crater.
-What is that?
-Is something inside?
-It's huge.
-There's nothing underneath?
There's nothing. Why ask?
Is your belly button raw?
-Is it raw?
-It's raw.
-Why is it like that?
-It's like...
There's a huge hole.
Is your belly button raw?
-Here?
-Yeah, there.
-You added something, right?
-Like a belt buckle.
It's perfectly round.
-Is your belly button raw?
-It's raw.
What's a "raw" belly button?
A raw belly button.
A raw belly button?
His balls...
-His belly button is poking out.
-Belly button...
-Ah, this isn't it. I did it wrong.
-She was recording?
-Wow.
-What?
-She recorded that earlier.
-No way.
It's a voice recorder.
Why did you record that?
Did we have a sound like that?
Kurosawa, you told me to wear this,
but now you're...
There's nothing for me?
-She wants you to dance, right?
-What's that?
To a world I haven't seen yet
Haranishi...
-That was...
-Not yet.
Even if I become a tapir
Or if I return to my senses tomorrow
I will live on tomorrow
I don't know the map from here on
What is the correct answer?
What is the...
Right?
The way that time stops
You have even less of an idea
What is freedom?
Do you know
the answer?
Please help me.
Help me.
Please. Somebody.
I don't like this.
I really don't like this.
Anybody.
Please, help me.
Please say something. Anything.
Give them the punchline.
-The punchline? The punchline is...
-Please.
There is no punchline.
I've never set up a joke
with a punchline...
I'm begging you.
Nishizawa, please.
Has anyone seen my Puma wallet?
-You're that kid from before?
-It's the same kid.
I can't find my Puma wallet at all.
Yeah. So, none of you took a Puma wallet?
Like we told you, it's not here.
It was definitely here.
-Were you practicing judo?
-Judo...
Well, I wear this when
I'm not practicing judo, too.
-That's your casual wear?
-I wear this casually, too.
Did you steal a Puma wallet?
-We didn't steal any Puma wallet.
-No. We haven't seen it.
I definitely lost it around here.
-Puma?
-Puma.
-Puma? It's not here.
-What color?
-It's blue checked.
-Blue checked?
-Shall we look for it?
-Yes.
Why did you drop your wallet
to begin with?
Huh?
Why did he go?
You, come on!
You, you, you, you, you, come on!
What character
What character do you usually play?
Usually
Usually I play cheerful characters
What
What goes through your mind
when you're doing it?
All of the members are finally here
We are rangers
Rangers
You are as cute today as ever
One step forward, two steps back
Always humble
Teddy Bear
Cute Bear
That was exhausting.
Goodness...
-Who was that?
-Damn!
-That was so long.
-Wow.
Wait a minute.
So long!
-That went on for ages.
-It did. I'm sorry.
-That took forever, right?
-It was so long.
That was so long.
Daigo!
-Really?
-Daigo...
To be honest, for several tens of minutes,
he's been virtually laughing
the whole time.
Maybe it was around the "Teddy Bear" part.
Always humble
Teddy Bear
Cute Bear
-Well, that was... You know...
-I know.
-I'll count that.
-It added up.
I'll count that one.
-I've already got an orange card.
-He already has.
-That means...
-Right. He is eliminated.
He's a zombie.
Now we'll have Chidori Zombies.
-Zombie Nobu is a bit depressed right now.
-You're right.
-Can I do anything with him like that?
-Right.
-Daigo, shall we?
-Okay.
Oh no. Zombie Daigo.
-You must keep it tight from here on.
-Why didn't you help me?
Don't forget, Kurochan's still unscathed.
-That's right!
-Yeah.
He doesn't laugh at all.
-You never laugh.
-How are we supposed to get him?
Yeah, but...
-This'll be tough.
-It's not good at all.
He's the kind of guy that drinks
sex lube...
I wonder why. Really, why?
I think...
I made this face that said,
"What's so funny about this?"
I kept that on the whole time.
So, I didn't have my normal face.
I was in some kind of character.
I had that face on the whole time.
I'm frustrated. Very much so.
But that foursome.
Of course you'd laugh.
One of them was an animal.
And the animal had the sharpest moves.
Teddy Bear
Let's go.
If Kurochan doesn't have a card yet,
we should all try to make him laugh.
You're right.
-I have no idea what he finds funny.
-He just doesn't laugh. Really.
Can't we tickle him?
Apparently tickling isn't allowed.
Please don't yank it.
I'd like you to take it off slowly.
Sorry. I do appreciate you taking it off.
You look like Oshima with that on.
-She does.
-Yeah.
-Like Oshima.
-Really like her.
You two really are a matching pair.
-They're a trio.
-Oh, a trio. Right.
-What's with the dog?
-I thought it was cute.
-And I felt shy.
-Is that Murakami?
-Murakami?
-Is it Murakami?
-Murakami...
-Oh!
The body belongs to Kurosawa,
the face is Oshima, and...
-That's the trio.
-Morisanchu all in one.
-I see.
-Wow.
The full set.
-What's that?
-Who's that?
Mich... I mean, Janet Jackson.
-Janet Jackson.
-Wardrobe malfunction.
-At the Super Bowl halftime show.
-That controversial one.
Lucky us.
Welcome to our lucky town
Here we have...
I'm Janet Jackson.
-Right, at the Super Bowl.
-That controversial one.
Nogera, nogera
What does "nogera" mean?
I hadn't thought about that.
-Just for the mood?
-I see.
That's amazing.
-That was good.
-Amazing.
You can't just say random things, right?
He's wearing that again.
What I was wearing before
was a little weird.
-You look hot.
-I am hot.
-May I take it off?
-You should take it off, if you're hot.
I'm so hot.
Huh? When did this happen?
What's this?
Huh?
What's this rubber?
Take it off! Take it off!
Take it off!
Take off this rubber.
Take it off.
Wearing something like this is weird.
Take it off. You have to.
I can't go around looking like this.
It's still on!
-You want us to stretch it?
-Stretch it, and take it off.
Take it off. Stretch it properly.
-Are you okay?
-After all...
That won't do at all.
Take it off properly!
Take it off, from a distance.
From a distance.
Do it
properly.
-Properly.
-You want it off, right?
Yeah, but look. Take it off here.
No, that's wrong.
No, take if off! Take if off!
-Take... Take it off.
-Take it off, right?
Hey, that hurts!
There.
You told us to take it off.
You wore it yourself.
Of course it comes off.
It won't come off by stretching anyway.
I'll put my clothes on.
I'm so hot.
What?
I knew it! It's still on!
Stretch it and take it off!
Stretch it properly!
It'll be the same thing over and over.
-Is there more to it?
-You'll do that forever?
Are we doing this again?
Stop cocking your head.
That's how we feel.
Right.
Stop it.
Show us your capoeira.
-Capoeira?
-Capoeira.
-You practice it, don't you?
-Yes.
-Right.
-You fight while dancing.
He looks strong.
Sorry, that's enough. I'm sorry.
Don't...
Don't ever do capoeira again.
Huh?
Don't stand right in front of me.
-Go for it more, Kurochan.
-It's your big chance.
According to the rules of comedy,
when he says stop, you have to go.
Why?
-You stink...
-Why?
You stink!
I don't have bad breath,
just a rotten stomach.
Miyasako.
Ouch! Reaping sword!
Ouch! Reaping sword?
Reaping sword...
Miyasako!
-You're still coming?
-Wow.
Miyasako!
Miyasako, why?
Why?
Hey.
Look at me properly.
Closed-fist punch, Genichiro Tenryu.
What kind of joke is that?
Stop getting in my face.
Miyasako!
I knew it would end like that.
What the hell are we doing?
Did you go to Stinky Breath High?
Eh, Stinky... No!
-Who did this?
-Your high school...
Who left a porn magazine here?
A porn magazine?
Of course I got a hard-on.
In the middle of a serious battle.
What were you thinking?
Who put it there?
Is it me?
I may have done it.
That was savage.
-You're insane.
-You're like a male porn star.
-You got a hard-on in the middle of this?
-For real?
That's Miyasako for you. He gets hard.
-That's amazing!
-That's Miyasako.
Being able to get a hard-on in a situation
like this is what makes Miyasako special.
-He's cool with things like that.
-Right?
-Wow.
-Amazing!
He may even get harder
in situations like this.
-Who was it?
-Maybe me.
Who was it?
It was you!
-Iio?
-It was Iio.
Who left a porn magazine here?
Of course I got a hard-on.
In the middle of a serious battle.
What were you thinking?
Who put it there?
Damn.
-You were on orange.
-Yes.
Since you're on orange,
it means you're eliminated.
What genre of comedy is it
when you show a hard-on?
"Exposing erect penises humor."
-You crossed the line with that girl.
-I definitely did not.
If you can get a boner in this situation,
you must have crossed the line with her.
Don't lie.
I didn't do it.
-Iio, good job.
-Good job!
-Good job.
It was a great performance. Thank you.
-I'm counting on you guys.
-Thanks!
-He got a boner...
-I'll miss him.
-It won't be the same without him.
-At the very end, he got a boner.
I never imagined Miyasako
would come out with a hard-on.
He got me.
Every time someone laughs,
Mr. Matsumoto enters the room, right?
It's actually a great relief.
When Mr. Matsumoto enters
with a smile on his face,
we know what we're doing is funny.
Without that, it would just be scary.
Yeah.
-Kurochan has no cards, right?
-So far.
-What makes you laugh?
-What's the hardest you've ever laughed?
Axel Hopper.
Axel Hopper?
-The "Pan-Pan, Spa-Pan-Pan" guy?
-No way! Well, he is funny...
Well, I prefer that type of comedy.
I don't really understand
complicated jokes.
-So you laugh at Axel Hopper?
-Rhythm acts?
Yes.
"Stupid tempo." Right?
Fujimoto, you can do it.
Why don't you sit and watch Fujimoto's
impression of Axel Hopper up close?
Here goes.
Stupid tempo
He's not laughing.
-He doesn't laugh.
-Not at all.
-It has to be Axel?
-You need the real deal?
-It's a little different.
-Of course!
-I wasn't just "a little different."
-He wasn't even close.
Why are you scolding me?
Tell us what makes you laugh.
We don't have a clue.
In daily life, what makes you laugh?
I like dirty jokes.
But you didn't laugh at him.
It was too realistic.
I just got surprised.
-Too realistic? It was 100% real.
-What dirty jokes?
Well, if there's a dick,
and you touch their balls,
I'll imagine how good it feels.
-What the hell?
-What?
Watching something like that
makes me laugh.
You laugh when someone touches
a guy's balls?
Then I'll touch someone's balls.
You'd better laugh.
-Exactly. You said it.
-If a senior show his balls,
you'd better laugh when I touch them.
-Whose balls will make you laugh?
-Yeah. Whose balls?
-Whose balls...
-Among us, whose?
Play "Choose the Balls."
Now it's time for "Choose the Balls!"
Me?
I simply want to see them.
-Jun's balls?
-Yes.
Showing my balls isn't...
-I don't want to touch his balls.
-Me neither.
They're nice and clean.
He simply wants to see them?
-Will Miyasako do it?
-Mine are biggest...
Why does he "simply want to see"
Itoda's balls?
Why so slow?
-He is clean.
-They're surprisingly cute balls.
-How do I...
-How should he do it?
How should I touch them?
-You'll touch them?
-Sure.
How should I touch them?
Between the sky and you
Another day of cold rain
In order to see you smile
I will even become evil
Between the sky and you
I find it quite funny.
Another day of cold rain
In order to see you smile
I will even become evil
-Your eyes met?
-They did.
It stinks already.
-Seriously?
-That's wrong, Jun.
-That's not right. Not right at all.
-What the hell!
-Jun, that's not right.
-Jun!
-Sorry.
-That was a surprise.
Clean it...
-Clean it up!
-Jun!
-Seriously?
-Kurochan, clean it up.
I finished.
-What were you thinking?
-I'm sorry.
-What an idiot.
He's an idiot.
-What were you thinking?
-Sorry. His touch was stimulating...
-The stimulation was...
-Hold this.
Poke it in here.
Why do I have to clean up your piss?
-Hold it yourself.
-I'm sorry.
No more is coming out?
You are still tinkling!
-Still a lot more coming.
-There is.
-What were you thinking?
-Piss is nasty.
I'm sorry.
Is this for real?
-For real?
-Don't just give me one sheet.
One sheet means I get piss on my hand.
That's a smile on your face!
You got him?
He was smiling just now.
I told you, I'm a sucker for dirty jokes.
-Your idea of a dirty joke goes beyond...
-Oh, my gosh!
What were you thinking?
The "Don't give me one sheet" line
was sly.
It's because you gave me only one sheet.
You only handed me one sheet.
That was gross. I don't want to walk here.
-Mr. Matsumoto, you have to tell him off.
-What is this?
I know that "anything goes,"
but that was...
Someone will dispose of it.
-Being sorry isn't enough.
-You can't do that.
But we're laughing our asses off
in the back.
I hadn't seen the tip of a guy's dick
open to piss in ages.
In order to see you smile
I will even become evil
-Your eyes met?
-They did.
-What were you thinking?
-Sorry. His touch was stimulating...
Why do I have to clean up your piss?
-Hold it yourself.
-I'm sorry.
Is this for real?
-For real?
-Don't just give me one sheet.
One sheet means I get piss on my hand.
That's a smile on your face!
You got him?
-Kurochan, yellow.
-Okay.
It's a yellow card. That was worth yellow.
-Kurochan, finally...
-He finally crumbled.
The last stronghold.
I was able to keep a straight face
with Jun.
But Kukky was...
When I handed him the paper he said,
"Don't give me just one sheet."
I thought, "Yeah, he will get pee on him."
Of course I would.
What kind of genre does he find funny?
I can't understand why
you'd laugh at that.
NEXT EPISODE
-Take it off!
-Take which clothespin off?
The one attached to the bottle?
He's insane.
He's absolutely insane.
I knew he was crazy.