THIS PROGRAM INCLUDES CONTENT THAT
MAY BE INAPPROPRIATE FOR SOME VIEWERS.
PLEASE ENJOY THE SHOW
AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION.
GAMES PLAYED AMONG CONTESTANTS ARE FILMED
WITH GREAT CARE FOR THEIR SAFETY.
PLEASE DO NOT TRY THEM AT HOME.
For once in my life,
for this one time only,
I want to focus on winning.
I think I have quite a strong defense.
I really do.
I'm pretty sure I can defend myself
against those who do high-level jokes.
This will be the one.
I think I'm getting closer to winning
each time.
I want to go home and slam it down.
10 million yen, right in front of my wife.
Always humble
Teddy Bear
Cute bear
-I've already got an orange card.
-He already has.
-That means...
-Right. He is eliminated.
Who left a porn magazine here?
Of course I got a hard-on.
What were you thinking?
You're eliminated!
-For real?
-Don't just give me one sheet.
One sheet means I get piss on my hand.
That's a smile on your face!
You got him?
He was smiling just now.
ATTACK POINTS
KUKKY = 4, MIYASAKO = 3, FUJIMOTO = 2,
KUROCHAN = 2, KUROSAWA = 1,
NISHIZAWA = 1, ITODA = 0
-Let's go.
-Why is that piss still there?
It's proof that he's working here.
We don't need the smell of piss
as proof he's working.
-I apologize for the inconvenience.
-Not at all.
-You were quick to start cleaning up.
-You showed no hesitation.
Did you do that as a part-time job?
What kind of part-time job is
"piss wiping"?
-How would I find it?
-Like a cleaner.
Yeah, yeah.
But nobody specializes in piss.
-Did you work full-time?
-Who works full-time?
A full-time piss wiper?
I've never heard of that.
-Did he smile a bit?
-I didn't.
-You did smile.
You did.
I look like I'm showing off my muscles,
but I'm checking the smell of my armpit.
That's funny.
Really?
Keep it coming.
-Keep it coming?
-I think I'll laugh.
It's carnival time!
Yay, yay
Shave, shave
My bikini line is so clean
Take this!
That's...
So small!
It's not small. It's an anaconda.
It's nothing like an anaconda.
It's as small as a turtle's tongue.
No, it's not. It's huge.
But Miyasako's was bigger.
That's because he had an erection.
It's so small. I want to see it.
That's small.
You've been targeted.
Why? Why?
Maybe she wants to fight.
Look. She's got her weapon...
Ouch! It really does hurt.
Bring it on!
Ouch!
Ouch! Ouch!
Get possessed by the devil!
Ouch!
My urethra hole opened up.
-That's enough.
-Really, that's enough.
-Stop it.
-We don't need that.
-Did you try to do it?
-What?
Did you try to pee?
Peeing is my thing.
-Your thing?
-It's mine.
-"The Art of Peeing" is his.
-Peeing is an art?
"The Art of Erections" is mine.
Trying to do any Pee Art here
won't lead to anything.
No one will laugh.
I want to eat that meat again.
It was delicious.
-It was?
-Yes.
It was super delicious.
Do you want to order food? Something?
But the zombies will come pretty soon.
-That's right. The zombies.
-Any minute now.
-Yeah. We have three zombies now.
-Once they start, they'll keep coming.
-We can't kill zombies, right?
-That's right.
-They're allowed to laugh.
-Yeah.
Their laughing won't end it.
The zombies...
All we can do is endure them.
We'll just have to hang in there.
-We're beyond a staring contest, right?
-No way.
-Not now.
-That would be brutal.
Zombie Time!
That scared me.
It's been a while.
Yes.
-That came suddenly.
-I'm cold.
-At long last.
-I think we should...
-Hello!
We're Chidori. Thanks for coming.
You know what?
Tokyo has the best sushi bars.
-Indeed. It's the home of Edo-style sushi.
-Let me play a sushi master.
-Okay. I'll be a customer.
-At an authentic bar.
Excuse me. Do you have room for one?
Velcome.
-Welcome?
-Blease.
-Please?
A few side dishes for starters?
Okay. I'll leave it up to you, thanks.
And for you.
It's a very small and cold egg custard.
Who wants it like that?
Give us a big warm one!
And for you.
It's fatty saury. I removed the entrails,
then I put them back in.
Why would you do that?
There's no point in removing them
in the first place.
-And for you.
-Here we go.
-It's fried chicken.
-Fried chicken?
Fried chicken at a sushi bar?
-That's wrong.
-Next dish.
Yellowtail filet.
To cook it evenly, I slashed it 800 times.
That's too many.
-I put curry on top, too.
-Curry!
Curry on top of yellowtail?
Eat up.
Now it's time for nigiri-zushi.
There you go.
-Try guessing what it is.
-Mystery sushi?
Yes, it's tuna.
But to be specific, it's cheek meat.
I see. You use unusual parts.
-Are you ready for nigiri-zushi?
-Please.
-Try guessing what it is.
-I wonder if I can.
I can't tell.
-It's dolphin. This part.
-Don't give me that!
-Next.
-What's this?
-It's hammerhead shark. This part.
-Gross!
-Next.
-What's this?
-Atlantic footballfish. This part.
-Gross!
-Next.
-What is it this time?
-Two pieces of squid.
-Two pieces of squid!
After all that,
I get two normal pieces of squid?
Please be quiet!
-Says who?
-There are other customers.
The customer over there is Mr. Kakuei.
-Tanaka?
-Tanaka.
He's dead.
He's alive!
There are many such cases in Japan.
-Mr. Kakuei Tanaka is actually alive?
-Yes.
The customer behind him is...
Mr. Ken.
Takakura?
-Shimura.
The Shimura who's still alive.
The customer behind him is...
Yu.
Yu?
Mr. Yujiro Ishihara?
-Gida.
-Gida?
Great Gidayu?
Who calls Great Gidayu "Yu"?
Mr. Gidayu, ready for the check?
Now we have Gidayu's payment scene!
For the first time
in the history of comedy!
Great Gidayu's payment scene!
-That'll be 180,000 yen.
-180,000 yen!
What did he order?
-Whelk shells.
-Whelk shells?
-Two thousand pieces.
-Two thousand!
To go.
I've had enough.
Give me the check, please.
-That's 3,800 yen.
-That's kind of reasonable.
That's it. Thank you very much!
Get hard!
I used sex lube.
It's still limp!
Get hard!
No matter what I do, it's limp!
He was like this the whole time.
Behind that door. Like this.
We waited forever, but it's limp.
I borrowed sex lube, but it's limp.
In the end,
they told me to put on a condom.
Because it's limp.
I even tried a new way of doing it.
-But even then...
-It stayed limp.
I'd never seen that.
Usually it's like this.
But he did it like this.
It was like a trap for eels.
I considered giving him a blowjob.
Everyone was waiting for me to get hard.
They all wanted me to get hard.
The staff kept coming in to check.
Then they'd report how hard I was.
To their boss.
"It just got slightly bigger."
That's tough.
When that happens, it stays limp.
It won't get hard?
It's not easy to get a hard-on.
I thought that he might end up
peeing with that on.
-Inside the condom?
-And the condom would get full of pee.
I was afraid he'd do that.
I can't piss either.
-I thought about it.
-Huh?
-Now?
-Now he pees.
Damn!
-No way.
-Wait a minute!
It was me who ended up peeing.
-Hey!
-Nobu made his move.
-I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry! I'm sorry!
What were you thinking?
Damn it!
He caught me off guard!
Be careful,
or you'll really be in trouble.
What kind of competition is this?
Really.
And your underwear are scattered
all over the place outside that door.
You had them on until the last minute?
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
-Pee...
-Damn.
-Miyasako!
-Yes.
You laughed, right?
I did.
And...
Itoda.
You laughed too, right?
I did.
Let's take a look.
I can't piss either.
-I thought about it.
-Huh?
-Now?
-Now he pees.
Hey!
Itoda joined in there as well.
We had a complete laugh from Itoda, too.
-That was insane.
-"The Pissing Zombie."
They put up a good fight, but Itoda
and Miyasako,
you're eliminated.
You did exactly the same skit
yesterday at Lumine.
That's right.
My daughter laughed so hard at that skit.
-I didn't expect a reenactment like that.
-That was too much.
I wanted to make you laugh
the orthodox way.
I wanted to make you laugh with my quips.
You stopped being orthodox
the moment you got naked.
We stopped being manzai artists
the moment we got naked.
You're right.
There's not much time left. Let's go!
Ah, damn it!
Damn it, they got me.
-There's nothing you can do.
-There's so much piss.
Piss!
What will happen now?
Let's go.
-Good luck guys.
-Thank you.
Which way? Oh, this one.
I deserve it. I laughed my ass off.
Huh?
-Now?
-Now he pees.
I haven't laughed like that in ages.
I hadn't burst into laughter
like that in ages.
However, I was definitely
going to get a hard-on.
I was determined the moment
I received this offer.
Who left a porn magazine here?
Of course I got a hard-on.
I did get a hard-on.
So, in that respect,
as far as I'm concerned, I won.
Well, I did a few things that
I had planned to do,
but that lead to nothing at all.
It's me.
I'm Master Hamburg!
Now, I'll offer you hungry...
I feel no sense of achievement.
After all, all I did was pee.
In order to see you smile
I will even become evil
-Your eyes met?
-They did.
So, I have no idea what's funny,
or how you can make them laugh.
When they're in that space,
I have no idea at all.
We don't know who has
how many points, right?
-You've been getting a lot, Kurochan.
-Here we go.
-You're in the lead.
-No, I'm just...
No, no. I think you have
quite a few points, Kurochan.
Maybe I should do something.
-Shall we?
-I think we should.
Right? Let's do it.
All this muddling around...
I should just kill you all.
This is just...
But I'm running out of stuff.
Me, too.
I've run out.
"The Run-Out Family."
-I've only got Tenga eggs left.
-How many times are you going to use them?
You're right.
Where did it go?
-Do I have anything left?
-It's cold. I'll put some pants on.
-This totally sucks.
-It's cold.
Wow, it's cold.
Yeah, it is.
Isn't this amazing? This scene is amazing.
-It's out of a movie.
-Yeah, this scene is amazing.
It's hard to make people laugh.
Scary, scary, scary.
Think what Nishizawa is feeling
hearing that comment.
-What?
-All of my glasses have gone somewhere.
It's so cold.
Yes?
These...
Do you buy them one at a time?
-I buy them in bundles, actually.
-Really.
It looks like a Pietro dressing.
-Do you use it yourself?
-Never.
How do you use it?
How do I use it?
It makes things more slippery.
And...
The way I like to use it is,
I get someone to apply
the lube on my balls,
then I have them scrape their nails.
I see.
It contains paraben.
Shall we do kendo?
Okay.
You'll hold it there?
With one swing.
I used to play softball.
-You are quite strong.
-Yes.
What should I do?
-May I?
-What?
-May I go for it?
-Of course.
Thank you.
Your outfits are similar.
In the end,
everyone is wearing a similar color.
You're Wada, from the faculty of commerce?
-Masaki?
-Masaki Wada.
What?
It's the crash test thing.
The crash test thing.
What was that? Do they sell that? Scary.
What was that?
Will you look at a photo of me from
elementary school?
My T-shirt...
"Family Computer."
-Wow. The "Famicom."
-How nostalgic.
-A Famicom T-shirt.
-Wow!
-Wow.
-Do Famicom T-shirts even exist?
Right.
"Family Computer."
I grew up with a Famicom T-shirt.
This is from our family trip.
My father took the photo.
My sister is biting my mom's hand.
Who develops this kind of photo?
-She's biting hard.
-Look. We're holding both hands.
In front of a phone booth.
It must have been the only sign.
Holding hands. We were so close.
My sister is biting Mom's hand,
but her face is totally deadpan.
-Her face is totally...
-Here we go.
Zombie Time!
-Bring it on. We'll never lose.
-We'll never lose!
-Come on.
-Huh?
We're going to beat you!
-That's our line!
-It sure is!
How many times do you think
our team has won?
-The number of times you won is...
-It makes no difference.
They call this guy "The Iron Anus."
He will never let one out!
Let's do this.
Let's go.
-Stick it in.
-Here I go!
Hang on. Wait a minute...
Can you moisten it first?
-I'll use the narrow one.
-Okay.
-He licked it.
-You should change the adapter...
The bigger adapter...
-I didn't think Iio did these things.
-Yes, I'm surprised.
He has really old-looking balls.
-Like a grandpa.
-Yeah.
I'm 48, you know.
-Let's go.
-Okay!
-Can you hold this for me? Okay!
-Go for it.
-He really put it in.
-Slowly!
-Slowly, okay?
-Take it slow.
Three, two, one...
Brother.
Brother...
-It's halfway in.
-Smell it?
Brother.
It's not in yet.
-I can't smell it.
-Really? I can.
Want to use the lube?
-Oh, that's right.
-There's some here.
-Give them some of your lube.
-Sure.
-Is this lube, too?
-Yes.
Mine's in quite deep.
-Want to put in on yourself?
-Put it directly on his anus.
-You're applying it directly?
-No.
The anus is better.
-Thank you.
-Wow.
-I'll move your balls a bit.
-Sure.
You move them like that?
-Maybe you should let it drip down.
-Relax.
Wow, that's...
This lube is stiff.
Nobu's balls
look like the back of a kid's head.
Be careful.
-Is it in?
-It's inside.
-It's really inside.
-Enough.
-Be careful!
-Jun, that's enough.
Be careful. It's inside.
Here we go.
Hold it in place yourself, Iio.
-Push on my cue.
-What a foreign object!
It's leaking...
-Nothing's coming out of Nobu.
-Nothing.
Okay, okay! I'm full!
Okay!
You're full?
That was close.
That stunk.
-A lot came out.
-A lot indeed.
-Yay, yay, yay, yay.
-So, he's out.
I can't take Iio's farts.
What the hell was that game?
Okay.
-Fujimoto.
-Yes?
You're eliminated!
Yay! We did it.
You were so close.
So close.
-Nothing's coming out of Nobu.
-Nothing.
Okay, okay! I'm full!
Okay!
You're full?
I thought,
"If Nobu can piss, why can't he fart?"
Nothing came out at all.
-We took one down, so all's good.
-We're good.
How could he do something like that?
-Okay, okay! I'm full!
-That was...
I was thinking,
"After all these years as a pro..."
All that added up in my head,
and I burst into laughter.
The most dangerous one in there was...
Kurosawa.
She was like...
She kept mumbling,
like she was chanting a Buddhist sutra.
"This is wrong. I'm almost 39.
I can't be doing this.
"No way. I'm 39. Should I quit?
Maybe I should I quit."
She kept on going, and it was like...
She was really losing it.
Look at what this can do to a person.
What kind of show is Documental?
-10 million yen is just around the corner.
-But we're...
What should I do?
But you're right. It is.
Here we go.
This will probably be your last chance.
-Let's go!
-Who'll play the straight guy?
What should we do?
It will be one of us, right?
One of us will get it, right?
As things stand.
If we don't laugh.
But which of us will
keep the ball rolling? Me?
I'm not sure about this,
but I'll give it a try.
-Try what?
-That game.
-What? You'll do that?
-Yes.
-Really? In your anus?
-You can't!
-Think I shouldn't? Nobody would marry me?
-I couldn't watch it.
If you went out of sight and
did it yourself, that may be better.
-I don't want to see your anus in person.
-Then I'll go somewhere else.
I wouldn't be able to unsee it.
I need to turn things around...
Nishizawa, did you know about my sweater?
-This sweater.
-What is it?
You'll be really surprised.
It's super small.
What? You were wearing that?
-It's actually this small.
-Super small.
-Wow, that's some amazing material.
-Yeah, it stretches.
Isn't it small?
-How did you wear it?
-It's so small!
-Right? Look.
-No way!
-I was wearing that.
-It's super small.
It's gotten even smaller.
Yeah, it keeps shrinking.
-As time passes?
-Yeah, it ends up becoming this small.
That's tiny!
That's too small.
-What a liar.
-Honestly.
-Ouch! Ouch!
-How did you go?
-Actually...
-Ready?
I don't know how to put it in.
Is it in your anus?
-Is it in your anus?
-Yes.
-Is it really your anus?
-Of course it is.
-Do you mean her vagina?
She doesn't know much yet. I mean...
It's a delicate subject.
She doesn't know everything.
Okay.
-And she's a lady. Stop saying "vagina."
-I didn't.
-You did.
-If she didn't put it in her anus...
"Is it really your anus?"
He mimicked me.
What?
-It's over?
-Like that?
-Wait, wait!
-I wasn't looking at all.
It's finished!
-What?
-What a relief.
That last buzzer...
I was afraid you'd mistake it for
Kurosawa's fart and start laughing.
This time we do have a winner!
There is?
We employed a point system.
The winner is...
Kukky!
I did it! Wow!
Really? Seriously?
Seriously.
It really was close. Just one point.
Kukky won by one point.
Really?
No way. No way.
For the first time in my life!
Here's 10 million, plus my one million.
That means Kukky won 10 million.
You may put it in the bag.
Kukky is the winner!
Congratulations!
Wow!
My first win ever! Thank you!
You were scary. You were amazing.
Wow! You were amazing, Kukky.
I got a shitload of money.
This is nasty.
-Really nasty.
-It's for real.
-Nasty.
-It's all true.
After a three million yen investment,
you got a return.
-You're right!
-Wow!
But that was close!
That's what you call guts.
Really? Really? I won?
It's the first time in my life.
I've never been number one
in anything before.
My first time ever.
We thought you had scored
quite a lot of points.
-Really?
-It was a clean sweep.
-That's so nice to hear.
-However,
you had no idea until the end?
No, I didn't.
I knew I was slowing down towards the end.
I sensed I was getting weaker.
I was wondering what I should do.
I tried to make a conscious effort.
After all,
I was dishing out my three millionth yen.
Ready, go!
I couldn't just let them
keep on taking my money like an idiot.
Boobs, boobs!
That may have been in the back of my mind.
It helped tighten my belt.
Where's the money now?
I don't have it. They took it.
They took it away...
Do you think it's safe?
Someone said, "I'll look after this."
Then it was gone.
-Will I get it back?
-Who took it?
It was some kind of assistant.
Wearing a uniform.
I've never seen them before.
Never in my life.
I don't even think they were from Amazon.
I think the right person won.
He's been a great contributor to the show.
I didn't want him to end as a contributor.
He went from being a contributor
to becoming a winner.
There was a scene where Miyasako
came in quite aroused...
Of course I got a hard-on.
What were you thinking?
I don't know how much I should say,
but in Miyasako's case...
He gets more excited
when there are lots of people around.
Last season, Kasuga was quite sensational.
This season, there was urination...
I really think that was
quite an amazing feat.
When you consider the fact
he was trying to make people laugh...
Usually, people can't pee like that.
Even if you want to,
it just doesn't come out.
Nothing happens.
Like when you're at the hospital.
It just doesn't come out
when you need it to.
So in that situation,
with all those people around,
being able to pee at that timing...
I knew it, but yeah.
Itoda really is insane.
He's absolutely insane.
He sure is crazy.