THIS PROGRAM INCLUDES CONTENT THAT
MAY BE INAPPROPRIATE FOR SOME VIEWERS.
PLEASE ENJOY THE SHOW
AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION.
-Hello.
-Hello there.
-Today's the day.
-Yes.
HITOSHI MATSUMOTO
Let go.
I thought Season Three turned out
really well.
But, surprisingly, some people say
they preferred Season Two.
It's interesting to see how viewers
gradually develop different tastes.
WHICH IS YOUR FAVORITE DOCUMENTAL?
SEASON THREE'S NEW SYSTEM
"THE ZOMBIE SYSTEM"
I guess you could say
it was chaos in there.
A chaotic environment is one of the things
I wanted to create.
As the show progresses,
the muddle becomes less chaotic.
It becomes a lot easier to watch.
MAKING THE FINAL STAGES MORE DYNAMIC
Come in, Teddy Bear.
But if you do a good job as a zombie,
you can leave a good impression.
In the case of some players,
the quicker they become a zombie,
the better it turns out for them.
There's a possibility
their ulterior motive is to be a zombie.
But that would beg the question,
"Why did you even come?"
IT'S AN EVER-EVOLVING EXPERIMENT
HOW SHOULD WE ENJOY DOCUMENTAL?
Some viewers really get into the show,
and get excited about seeing who wins it.
I understand where they're coming from.
But aside from seeing who wins,
I wish our viewers were equally concerned
with seeing how funny the others are too.
THERE'S MORE FUN TO DOCUMENTAL
THAN JUST SEEING WHO WINS
Each episode provides an opportunity
to witness a miracle,
like when "Nyanko Star" first came out.
Don't forget.
They got the attention without winning.
Many people say this show has
too many dirty jokes.
Ow!
As far as I'm concerned,
there are no dirty jokes at all.
Not on this show.
They're not dirty jokes.
They're art.
ART?
We need to have
a deeper understanding of art.
While taking a walk this morning,
I saw a beautiful spider lily
outside a house down an alleyway.
Have you visited your family grave
this year?
I send you this invitation
with my best intentions.
I sincerely hope you will join me
with one million yen on your person.
I am hosting a Documental.
I have prepared 10 million yen
as the champion's prize.
Whether to participate or not,
the decision is yours.
If you are willing to participate,
I will contact you again
about the time and venue.
I look forward to your reply.
May this harvest season
bring you plenty of fruit.
Sincerely, Hitoshi Matsumoto.
THE COMEDIANS ARRIVE AT THE BATTLEFIELD
Someone is here.
Eh?
I'm the first one?
That's right.
-Why do I have to be first?
-This is Nobu.
Yeah, you wouldn't want to be
the first one to arrive.
Hi, I'm Nobu from Chidori.
What's this?
I got one!
I'm not the one you want.
I think Nobu is at the peak of his career.
IN HIS PRIME
He's quick to respond, and he's witty.
Nobu is able to create laughter
in his own right,
but I think his role here will be
to manipulate the others.
He'll use the actions of others
to create laughter.
THE TRICKY STRAIGHT MAN
I don't expect him to go on the offensive
very often.
THE COUNTERATTACK STRATEGY
If Nobu becomes a zombie,
he may not be funny at all.
"ZOMBIE NOBU" WON'T BE FUNNY?
After all,
I don't do the funny guy role.
It won't be funny.
HOW WILL THE STRAIGHT MAN FIGHT?
I wouldn't say I've neglected my comedy,
or just stayed in my comfort zone,
but lately I've done too many reports
about pancakes in Shibuya and Harajuku.
This coincides with my having doubts about
whether that's really what comedians do.
I think it's about time I started
acting like a comedian again. Yeah...
I have to play a game
where the stakes are big,
or I'll be finished.
How come I'm the first? Who are the rest?
-Who's coming?
-This situation...
Everything is a first for him.
Here comes another one.
He's brought quite a lot of stuff.
You'd take that much if you were
going to Spain.
It's Itoda!
I'm Jun Itoda from Speed Wagon.
Let me do it!
Excuse me.
Hello.
When I'm up against comedians,
I think my abilities to defend
and attack would be...
I think my stats would say I'm a bit
weaker than average in both categories.
THE WEAKER-THAN-AVERAGE COMEDIAN
He destroys the general vibe
without any qualm.
He's mentally strong, too.
Have you forgotten?
It's me!
I'm Master Hamburg!
IF YOU FEEL SORRY FOR ME, LAUGH
His mental strength can be scary.
Having a guy like this in the room
really is scary.
I'm sure he'll go on the offensive.
But his idea of an attack
won't be an attack at all.
HIS ATTACKS WON'T HAVE
THEIR DESIRED EFFECT
But what he doesn't mean as an attack
may, in fact, become one.
THE ACCIDENTAL ATTACKER
I'm not happy to see Jun here.
Not happy at all.
I could try mapping out
a bunch of different scenarios,
but it won't go as planned anyway.
So, whatever happens inside,
I hope I'll find something to work with.
LEAVING IT TO INSPIRATION
I have to bring something
they've never seen before.
A NEVER-BEFORE-SEEN ITODA
-I didn't even tell my partner.
-Neither did I.
They told me not to tell anyone.
Who is it?
-It's your second time.
-He never learns.
-It's my third time!
-Your third?
This is my third try.
I didn't expect you to come, Fujimoto.
-Lookee here, it's Nobu and Jun.
-Hey.
Hi! I'm Fujimoto from Fujiwara.
This time, I want to grab the title.
HE WANTS TO GRAB THE TITLE
Oh, no! Really?
I keep getting these invitations!
We could say he's like a semi-regular
on this show.
SEMI-REGULAR
He's good at setting various moods.
THE MOOD MAKER
Some fans claim I'm too soft on him.
"MATSUMOTO IS TOO SOFT ON FUJIMOTO"
It's not that I'm soft on him.
It's simply good to have someone in there
who's apt at setting the mood.
THE PERENNIAL SUPPORTING COMEDIAN
For the first time
in my 29-year-long career,
I've finally found the battlefield
that's perfect for me.
Well, it is in my opinion.
-You'll tear them.
-What are you doing?
What is that?
IN THE PREVIOUS SEASON,
HE ADVANCED TO THE FINAL FOUR
Last time, I started thinking I might win.
I really thought I might make it.
Yeah.
THE MOMENT OF CARELESSNESS
THAT HAUNTS HIM
I'm going to pounce on the little things,
one after the other.
I think that's how I should fight.
AIMING TO WIN BY POUNCING
ON THE LITTLE THINGS
-We all play the straight man.
-You're right.
All three of us so far.
I'll sit over there.
-Your bag is so small.
-I always only bring this much.
-It's so small.
-I didn't have much to bring.
-I'm not the type who uses props.
-You're right.
Here's another one.
Again?
Why are you here?
You come here so often!
Don't be like that.
Fujimoto's here all the time too!
So are you.
"SORRY ABOUT THE FUSS"
Hi, I'm Kukky from Yaseibakudan.
You're here!
Again?
She's just my manager.
Kukky is prone to laugh easily.
But his attack level is high enough
to overcome that weakness.
THE COMEDIAN KILLER
The most formidable player was Kukky.
Take a look.
That's a shrunken head.
He is totally off the wall.
You never know what he'll do next.
It's when Kukky turns into a zombie
that he becomes truly terrifying.
-Look how small it is.
-Your sweater's that small?
Yoshimoto opened their doors
to a most formidable creature.
A MOST FORMIDABLE CREATURE
It's a cliché,
but third time's the charm, right?
THIRD TIME'S THE CHARM
I'll seriously try to win this time.
SERIOUSLY AIMING TO WIN
Honestly, it's like,
I'll rupture eardrums if I have to.
Whatever it takes to win.
I'll thread fishing line through their
cheeks and keep pulling until they smile.
I'll go all-out to win, just for a change.
THE MONSTER WANTS TO WIN
-You have to do it.
-No, I don't.
You're wearing the same watch as me.
Cut it out!
-Get over it.
-Let's use this later.
-Look at that.
-They're exactly the same.
We're lucky you didn't notice
after play had started.
-What good luck.
-That's scary.
-What's with that?
-How could this happen?
No more freaky things like that.
And damn Kukky...
You'll definitely do that thing, right?
-Probably.
-Definitely.
What about...
No way. She's a tough one.
We have a girl?
Wow.
-Women compete too?
-We have a girl.
-What did you bring?
-She means business!
-Sorry for bringing so much.
-What is that?
I'm Kazuko Kurosawa from Morisanchu.
I'm 39 years old, and I'm single.
Oh, now I'm fumbling. I'm losing it.
As the only female contestant,
she'll be a rose among weeds.
Adding a woman into the mix
can make things interesting.
Her partner Oshima was here before.
Just pour vinegar on it.
How dare you pour vinegar on my panties?
As a trio, Morisanchu has great potential.
When Kurosawa snaps and lets loose,
I don't think anybody can stop her.
That might happen here today.
SHE SINGS, SHE DANCES
AND SHE'S CHUBBY
If there is to be a female winner,
it could very well be her.
THE COMEDIENNE CLOSEST TO THE TITLE
But she has one weakness.
KUROSAWA'S WEAKNESS?
She's on her period today.
Let's see if that works out
for the better.
Right.
What should I do?
She scares me.
Why sit next to me?
I've never won any of the major contests,
like M-1 or King of Conte.
But if I can win Documental...
THE UNCROWNED QUEEN
SHALL FIND HER KINGDOM
I want to make sure other comediennes
get a chance here.
I'll have to do my best
among all these men.
-Are you going to be okay in here?
-Actually, I'm nearly 40 now.
So I've stopped making
adult-themed references.
-Oh, really.
-Yes.
-I'm not in my 20s anymore.
-"Adult-themed references"?
-Nobody wants you to talk about sex.
-No sexy stuff?
Someone's here.
No way!
-Why?
-Both of you?
-Hang on...
-We know. But this is one of our points.
Why are you here?
They're the first duo, right?
No way. Nobu's here!
Oh, my.
This is a new thing we'll be trying
this season.
You might call it a device of ours.
We're throwing in both members
of a comedic duo.
I'm Daigo from Chidori.
I will not laugh.
Did Mr. Matsumoto pick me himself?
We'll throw in both Nobu and Daigo. A duo.
This is actually a first for this program.
A FIRST-TIME EXPERIMENT IN SEASON 4
I wonder how this will turn out.
It's one new idea we'll be
putting on trial.
Chidori are interesting for the fact that
I think both of them
are suitable for this show.
Probably.
They're funny.
Of course,
I have high expectations for them.
But there's one thing.
I think they laugh too easily.
THE BASHFUL RUFFIAN
Doing things in a matter-of-fact manner,
without laughing,
that's one thing I'm not good at.
I'm the type of guy who laughs
as he makes the others laugh.
It may end up being a day I regret.
I won't have any idea how I should behave
until it starts.
For example, if Nobu was there,
I could just say something funny.
He would jump in with the right quip.
We have the trusted pattern.
But since I won't have that,
I'll have to figure out what to do.
-This is an amazing twist.
-What should we do?
Why is Chidori here as a duo?
Yoshimoto sure wants to promote you.
Don't say it like that.
Everyone's from Yoshimoto.
Here's another one.
I'm done for!
This one's tough!
I'll definitely laugh!
-Damn.
-You're wearing different glasses today.
I forgot my real ones.
I was going to use these for a joke today.
I'm already laughing.
I was so nervous, I left them at home.
I'm Kazuki Iio from Zun.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I'm so nervous,
I developed an irregular heartbeat.
Excuse me.
Wow!
I got one of these. Wow!
WHAT KIND OF GAG WILL WORK ON DOCUMENTAL?
I'm doing one already.
Mr. Cameraman, can you pan in on my feet?
I call this gag "Seven or eight minutes
of keeping my feet like a model."
I have dozens of gags.
But if you ask how many will help
when my back's against the wall,
I could count them on one hand.
Iio makes jokes that come from
a totally different angle than ours.
THE UNEXPECTED AMBUSH
He sets his comedic sights on niches
that we don't even bother looking at.
THE LEGITIMATE SUCCESSOR
OF THE SEKINE STYLE
He will survey the situation,
and instead of fighting all-out
in all the rounds,
he'll go on a spurt
in rounds five and eight.
I think that's how he'll play it.
If I was the sprinter type,
I would've been popular in my 20s.
I'm more like Chinese medicine.
I exert my effects gradually.
What do you guys think?
Summers described me perfectly
about 15 years ago.
They said, "You're a staff meal."
"You're a sushi chef's curry."
I'm never on the menu.
If I get beaten to a pulp in there,
I'll walk home.
Then I'll pat myself on the back
and go to bed.
At least I did some exercise.
It would be funny
if your partner comes next.
He told me he had the day off.
-What if it's him?
-I don't like this.
Fujimoto is the most experienced...
Not him!
-He'll definitely make me laugh!
-For real?
His face definitely gives him
an unfair advantage.
He looks like he's been
preserved in formaldehyde.
I'm Yusuke Nishizawa from Daian.
I'll do my best.
Hello.
Again?
Huh? It's not for me?
Shut up for a second.
It's not for Mr. Tsuda.
Sure it's not mine?
I quite like Daian's comedy routines.
I watched them a lot.
They're funny.
I was always impressed with them.
This is your chance.
It will get you on first base.
Your partner approves.
-A big chance!
-Yeah.
But I don't remember
ever seeing him laugh.
In that respect, he may do well.
People often say that I have a poker face.
But the truth is, I laugh quite easily.
I'll have to be careful about that.
When you're in that room,
everyone's on equal footing.
A junior can beat a senior.
SHOOTING FOR REAL
That idea excites me too.
I think you'll see how hungry I am
to topple the big guys.
He makes people laugh
just by looking their way.
-This is scary.
-Is he a bit of an airhead?
He's not an airhead.
I'm not an airhead, but one thing is,
despite this poker face of mine,
-I laugh really easily.
-Exactly.
-Really?
-That's why I'm scared.
I've never seen him laughing hard.
-Nishizawa laughs a lot.
-He sure does.
Our ninth player? Yeah.
-How many to come?
-Two more.
One's here.
-Hello.
-Whoa!
No way.
I'm done for. He's my type of comedian.
He's a monster.
I know you guys.
-Of course you do.
-So what?
-What would you expect?
-Damn.
I have no idea how this will turn out.
I'm Kurochan from Yasuda Dai Circus.
I really want the 10 million yen.
What's this?
A letter?
Is this...
He's an unknown quantity.
I have no idea.
Usually, everyone would play with him,
but I'm not sure here.
If Fujimoto starts toying with him,
there'll be trouble.
FUJIMOTO X KUROCHAN
-Cut it out.
-But I'm...
Just act normally. Look where we are.
THE MOST-PRANKED COMEDIAN IN JAPAN
Depending on how the others toy with him,
he may enter a completely unexpected
"bonus stage."
It's like everyone says.
I'm just one of television's puppets.
I never initiate anything.
I don't know much about comedy,
but that means
I'm not scared of high-level
comedy techniques.
I won't get them anyway.
I think I have strong defensive skills.
I really do.
This might be the perfect opportunity.
If I can show people that I'm able
to make people laugh here,
I might finally get other jobs,
besides all of those candid camera ones.
I'm going to change.
This really will change things.
I'll move onto the next level.
I'll do it!
My parents will pay for it!
HIS PARENTS ARE PAYING FOR IT
One more to go.
Who's coming?
The last may be the nastiest.
As for the last person, well...
I'm sure they won't be expecting
this last player.
No, Watabe would never laugh.
-What if we guessed right?
-Here's our last player.
It can't be!
What a surprise!
-Are you competing?
-You accepted?
What kind of opponents are you?
Straight back at you.
-You don't need any more money.
-Ten million is pocket money to you.
Hello.
I'm Miyasako from Ameagari-Kesshitai.
Excuse me.
Whoa.
For real?
I've been...
I've been through a lot lately.
I'm not emotionally stable enough
for this.
The only time I'm allowed to smile is
when I'm working, actually.
As things stand.
Before that thing happened...
Stop saying "that thing."
What does "that thing" even mean?
If I compete in this state of mind,
I may have a chance of winning.
HE'S IN NO MOOD TO LAUGH
I really didn't think Miyasako
would accept this offer.
Maybe "that thing" changed him.
THE NOT-SO-FAITHFUL
DO-OR-DIE COMEDIAN
He really is more insane
than people think.
When he snaps, it's really a sight to see.
The way he can explode is
quite formidable.
I'm the type of guy who can step over
the line, regardless of who's involved.
If I find any of the guys in there a bit
bothersome, I will step on their necks.
HE STEPS ON THE NECKS
OF THOSE HE DISLIKES
Recently, I've had a lot of jobs
as a show host.
I don't get many chances to fool around.
WANTS TO FOOL AROUND FOR A CHANGE
I'd like to go all the way.
Miyasako is here?
This is real bad.
We'll have to look after him.
It won't be fair if the duo
does something as a team.
We've been discussing that already.
There's nothing in the rules against it.
-Really.
-Anything goes in here.
-That's quick.
-He's trotting.
-Why?
-He looks nice and chirpy.
Nice and chirpy, but a bit like Takeshi.
-Like Takeshi.
-Bursting in like that.
Know what? You guys are funny already.
-I've been watching backstage.
-Really?
This may not even last for six hours.
-You're right.
-It's possible.
-This is seriously bad.
-I had a feeling that might happen.
-Many of us laugh easily.
-Yeah.
Has it ever not lasted six hours?
-Never.
-Thought so.
But on the other hand,
-we always see people laugh at Kurochan.
-That's right.
-But I've never seen him laugh.
-Yeah.
-I'm yet to see Kurochan smile.
-Exactly my point.
I've only ever seen his troubled look.
That's because prr...
Because I'm always being pranked.
He said, "Prr..."
No, I just made a weird noise.
I beg your pardon.
You'll have to cut that out.
And what's even worse,
Fujimoto always chips in with
the perfect quip at moments like that.
Your comment is what makes us laugh.
I really don't like this.
It's just a knee-jerk reaction.
-Try delaying your timing.
-It will be funny for a different reason.
Your quips are too good. You too, Nobu.
-He comes to life. We breathe it into him.
-Exactly.
You pour a heart and soul into him.
-He's right.
-We don't pour anything in!
-And Miyasako...
-Yes.
-It's brave of him to come.
-Yeah.
This is such a surprise.
-Well, he's here thanks to "that thing."
-Yeah.
My wife told me to keep that off limits.
That's impossible.
It's up to you. I won't touch on it.
No, no, no.
And you two, Chidori.
I saw your show yesterday at Lumine.
For real?
-Seriously?
-I saw your manzai act.
That's scary!
Were you up in the booth?
No, I watched from a seat in the last row.
Really?
-Why?
-I wanted to check Lumine out.
-That's scary.
-Don't do that.
The crowd went wild when they came out.
Well, we get a few cheers.
With a crowd that wild,
I expected more laughter.
If you call that bombing, I can't imagine
what you've done to crowds.
No, your crowd laughed.
You didn't bomb.
They were laughing, but...
-I was highlighting how much they cheered.
-You made them go too wild.
-Iio is here as well.
-Yes, he means trouble too.
-Did you come from a jar of formaldehyde?
-No, I didn't.
-Were you soaked in formaldehyde?
-No, I wasn't.
I wasn't put in anything.
-You're fresh from the seabed?
-No, I'm not.
I was in Osaka all this time.
Did you gnaw on rock salt?
Does rock salt do this to your face?
-The sodium made him puffy.
-Too much salt.
You're way too puffy.
You're a merman.
A merman's carcass, right?
I'm not a merman's carcass.
-Really?
-Yeah.
-Half-way through an experiment?
-No.
-Metamorphosing?
-No, I'm not.
Been immersed in amniotic fluid?
-I wasn't immersed in amniotic fluid.
-I see.
Hey, that's enough.
I'll be stuck with those in my mind.
Sorry. I really am. I'll stop.
-I think he'll be a strong contender.
-Definitely.
-He's been through a lot.
-Exactly.
He's mentally strong.
Absolutely.
I bet he is. He's overcome a lot.
-I've never seen him laugh really hard.
-That's right.
-He only makes people laugh.
-Yeah.
No, I do laugh. Really. So, for today,
let me do it!
He has many characters up his sleeve.
And he's another monster, too.
He sure is. He just keeps on coming.
But I have zero defensive power.
No defensive power.
You have that character... Pooh?
-Winnie the Pooh, right?
-Yeah.
-Teddy Bear.
-It's "Teddy Bear"?
Teddy Bear.
When I was at my lowest,
it made me laugh my ass off.
-You saved him.
-He saved you.
The power of laughter.
It saved me. It really did,
but if he does anything like that today...
It would mean danger here.
-He is insane.
-That's true.
-He really is nuts.
-He's created a few series here.
He lays cards on the table...
-No, I wouldn't do that.
-Please don't.
And Kurosawa is on her period today.
So don't be too harsh on her.
You might hear a ripping sound later on.
It's 40-centimeters long.
-It's a 40-centimeter nighttime pad.
-It's your heaviest day?
-Forty centimeters!
-Enough!
That sounds tough.
-Really, 40 centimeters?
-Leave her alone.
-It's the biggest one.
-This long?
It must cover your navel.
All the way from the back.
-Like seaweed.
-That's enough.
-Seaweed in your pants.
-It won't absorb a thing.
WHOEVER DOESN'T LAUGH GETS 10 MILLION,
PLUS MATSUMOTO'S MILLION YEN
I'll skip over most of the rules.
Fujimoto knows them well, right?
Yes, it's my third try.
THOSE WHO LAUGH GET
A YELLOW, ORANGE OR RED CARD
We'll implement the Zombie Rule again.
A RED CARD MEANS ELIMINATION
FROM THE GAME
-You can come back as zombies.
-And make the others laugh.
IF THE ZOMBIES MAKE EVERYONE LAUGH
IT'S A NO-CONTEST
-Let's say we're down to two players left.
-Okay.
With only two players in the room,
the zombies come in.
Let's say that the zombies make
this person laugh.
This person doesn't win yet.
THE LAST PLAYER MUSTN'T LAUGH
UNTIL SIX HOURS PASS
If you're the last player left,
but there's another hour to go,
you must endure the zombies for that hour.
Now I get it.
That's impossible.
Only then do you win.
-We have to last the entire six hours.
-That's right.
There's no way I'd survive that.
If the zombies get everyone...
-It's no longer a contest.
-Seriously?
It will be as if this never happened
in the first place.
But it will mean this series was
that funny.
And it should be remembered as such.
It's also possible
that both members of Chidori remain.
That's right.
As far as the rules are concerned,
could the two of us do something...
Does anything go?
-In front of everyone?
-Like this.
-As a pair?
-As a pair.
-I don't have a problem with that.
-I see.
-So, anything goes.
-Are you sure?
So, everyone,
it's time to collect the money.
Ugh, this'll hurt!
I don't know if we need the yellow...
I mean, maybe we don't need
the orange card this time.
Really?
-We'll have the zombies too.
-Right.
If you get two of these,
you'll be getting a red next.
Actually, I mean that yellow
will be followed by red.
This brings my total to three million yen.
-Three million?
-It goes out as fast as it comes in.
Three million yen?
What the hell are you doing?
-Try rejecting the offer.
-You lose each time.
I don't have any good reason to refuse.
-Kukky too.
-I've paid three million too.
-Six million between us.
-Your wives will beat you up.
-You only earn 16,000 per show at Lumine.
-Don't tell them.
You earn that much?
Do you get less?
But people,
this all really makes me so happy.
Think about it.
The fact you can all bring
one million yen.
That really touches me.
I've watched the series and...
Sorry.
-What's with you?
-I lost my timing.
Is that money legit?
It is... Eh?
It's not dirty money. I washed it.
-Don't bring the bills all loose.
-He didn't wrap them.
Wrap them in a bundle, idiot.
I had to make five withdrawals
at the convenience store ATM.
You can only withdraw 200 at a time.
-All you needed was some rubber.
-You have rubbers, don't you?
-"Rubber"?
-A rubber band!
-Oh, that rubber?
-Don't slip in dirty jokes.
-He's gonna get me.
-Don't start already.
Don't start yet.
-And here is my...
-There it is!
Thank you!
I have to pay one million yen
for no good reason.
-Every time.
-Seriously.
Seriously, this gets deducted each time!
This money! From my pay slip!
That's what you call shocking!
-We can imagine.
-Mr. Matsumoto...
Seriously!
He says this every time, right?
I know how much he has in the bank.
It's like, "What's the big deal?"
It doesn't matter how much I have.
I lose one million yen for hosting a show.
Doesn't that sound wrong?
But there are those
who can afford to lose it,
-And those who...
-No, that's not how it works.
For Kukky, losing three million
must have been hell.
It really is hell.
Losing one million hurts the same for all.
It's the same pain.
-It's the same.
-More or less.
-It all adds up to this.
-Whoa!
-Wow.
-This is it.
Awesome!
-May I touch it?
-This really is awesome.
-Wow.
-It's amazing.
Both piles are worth the same,
but crisp new bills sure have their charm.
You're strict about facial expressions.
Like when our faces loosen.
How much of a smirk
are we allowed to make?
I would really like for you guys to have
firmer faces.
That's all.
Last season, Yamamoto had
a bit of a grin the whole time.
-He was nearly giggling.
-He was.
-Ohchi was terrible, too.
-Yeah. So be careful there.
I mean,
you don't need a look of determination...
-But that's out, right there.
-Nobu has a smiley face.
-Yeah, I do.
-He's right.
You'll have to frown.
-Like that.
-Yeah.
Right. That's the face.
That's wrong for another reason.
That's better. That is a good face.
That's wrong! Stop it!
Can you keep that for six hours?
"Mr. Serious."
-I'll laugh at myself.
-The rookie comedian look.
Of course,
it's important to try and win this.
But if you follow Kukky's example
and make things funny as a zombie...
That's what comedy fans will
really appreciate.
-Keep that in mind.
-Be funny till the end.
It's not all about winning.
-Are we starting?
-Yeah.
No way!
-Not so fast. Give me a moment.
-That was rather abrupt.
And one more thing...
As a new thing this season,
you can order food.
You can call...
This one's an internal line.
Use the external line to call them.
You can have food delivered here.
If anything else pops up,
I'll let you know as we go.
Is that all I needed to say?
Well, you have this stuff here too.
If you think you can play with anything,
feel free to do so.
-He's going.
-Bye.
-Does it start when you leave?
-After I leave,
the lights will change,
and then it starts.
-Okay.
-I'm scared.
-Have a good one.
-Okay.
Thank you.
I'll have a smoke.
-We can smoke, right?
-You can.
I'll put my bags away in there.
-Laughing while you still can?
-If we don't laugh now...
"I'm Kurochan."
I have to get used to Kurochan.
Don't look at me like that.
What the hell is this?
Where do my things go? Okay.
Shall we get started?
Start!
Has it started?
Yes, we've started.
-The air horn went "farrrp."
-We're on.
Got it.
-We're on!
-Okay.
-I'm going to the toilet.
-I don't like this atmosphere.
-It's incredible.
-The start caught us off guard.
When I was peeing just now,
just as the last drop was coming out,
it went "farrrp."
That was a good one.
That was a nice "farrrp." Timing and all.
Daigo's been smirking a bit already.
Huh?
When we said this had started, you smiled.
Are you an idiot? You're smiling already.
-This face?
-That's what we mean. That's out.
If this is a smile...
Let him know he's wrong, guys.
I agree with you.
-You're smiling.
-Wait. Which face?
-Go back.
-You smiled halfway through.
You're saying this is out?
That's out. You can't do that.
All smiles are out.
Even when you asked just now...
Making a face to ask whether
it's out or not is out.
-That's out too?
-Right. Be careful.
We'll let that one go as an explanation...
What's that sound?
-That could've gotten you a red card.
-Why can I hear water?
-Is that how it goes?
-Yeah.
-That's out.
-I need to pee.
It's the sound of the toilet.
What did you think of Nobu's pee?
Is this dry ice?
-Someone's making a noise.
-There's no trash can.
-What's this?
-Can I drink some water?
Nobu said something about his pee,
but I missed it.
Shut up! He needs to shut up.
-There was a mic in the bathroom.
-A mic?
More importantly,
can we talk about Nobu's pee?
Shut up! He keeps nagging me about that.
Come on. Nobody wants to see
childhood friends fighting.
-The last drop...
-Why talk about pee?
The last drop?
-I found the trash can.
-Stop talking about pee.
He said that, just as the last drop
fell into the bowl,
the siren went "farrrp."
Is that what Nobu said?
Yes, that's all I said.
Iio, how about doing
an opening gag for us?
-Shall I?
-Just one, to brighten things up.
To get things going.
-To mark the start.
-Good idea.
There's no water here.
-Could you do one for us?
-The water's here.
There's some here.
-Guys, you can't just not watch.
-What's happening?
We're going to have a little opening gag.
An opening gag?
-By Iio?
-Apparently.
Ready?
-But we have six hours, right?
-Yeah.
It's way too early.
It will only be one gag.
-Where's Miyasako?
-He's in the bathroom.
-We should wait so Miyasako sees it too.
-Of course.
-Are we ready?
-Don't we have to flush?
It flushes by itself.
There weren't any buttons.
What happens when we take a crap?
Is that why Nobu was talking about pee?
Will you lay off that already?
All you talk about is pee!
It smelled sweet in there.
Is someone diabetic?
Who's diabetic?
-So, what about that opening gag?
-Oh, that's right.
-I turned my ignition on twice.
-Opening gag?
-I think we can go without.
-Yeah, sorry.
I should abort?
-I turned my ignition on. Twice.
-Sorry.
I'll give you another chance.
In four hours' time.
Wouldn't that be too soon?
Four hours' time?
With the current mood...
-Now would be the worst timing.
-You'd take out three players.
I can't hold it anymore.
Can I go to the bathroom?
-Go ahead.
-Uh-oh.
The mic...
-Will we hear her pee?
-Maybe we should talk or sing.
Kurosawa, we'll hear you.
He's right.
We'll be able to hear you!
Okay.
-And it doesn't flush properly.
-I don't like this.
Why don't we all go hear and her pee?
-Why would we?
-No, thanks.
I wonder if it's a thin pee or a fat pee.
What's a "fat pee"?
Does it vary day to day?
These guys hide too much
behind all that drinking and smoking.
-An elephant pee? A Naumann pee.
-I'll warn them.
-Lose the "Naumann."
-Naumann's elephant.
They're extinct.
Is he listening?
Kurochan, that really is creepy.
What is?
-You're listening to her pee.
-No, I'm not.
-What are you doing?
-I'm using the fan.
-Why?
-I need a fan because I'm hot.
-It's not hot.
-Don't stare into the distance by the fan.
Seriously, you'd better stop it.
Seriously. You're really creepy.
I'm not. Freaks love me.
I beg your pardon.
-We don't need that.
-Huh?
-Should I kill him?
-Trying to popularize "I beg your pardon"?
I don't mind his
"I beg your pardon" thing,
but could you stop coming back
with those quips?
The thing about Fujimoto is...
-He makes a contribution.
-He adds a nice sauce.
Yes, it's like a nice sauce.
You make it tasty.
A.1...
A.1. Sauce.
It's a sauce they have in Okinawa.
The steak sauce? What's your point?
He was talking about a yummy sauce.
What's that?
-Was that Kurosawa?
-What's he doing?
-Did Kurochan say something?
-What?
Why are you on an angle?
You're listening to Kurosawa peeing.
No, I'm not.
-Seriously. Stop it.
-Wait, wait.
Kurosawa and Kurochan make "Double Kuro."
-Can I listen?
-What crap!
Why did you slap me?
He's angry because you seriously thought
we would laugh at something like that.
It meant, "Don't take us lightly."
-Is somebody going "ahh"?
-That's scary. They're saying "ahh."
She's drowning out the sound of pee.
But the sound of pee...
-I heard it tinkling before.
-Me too.
It sounded like sparking.
Like she was cutting metal.
Who cuts metal in the bathroom?
Stop using that accent.
It will make me laugh.
-Isn't that a long pee?
-Yeah.
-He should be accent-free by now.
-Right?
When I first met Bunta Sugawara...
-We were in the film The Great Yokai War.
-I remember that.
He was playing the role
of Ryunosuke Kamiki's grandfather.
We met at a press conference.
I had second billing.
As the second-biggest star, I greeted him.
He came right up to my face and said,
"Who ur ya?"
-That's scary.
-I had second billing.
-He said that all the time.
-"Who ur ya?"
All the time?
Time and time again?
"Who ur ya?"
Bunta Sugawara said that?
How did you reply to his "Who ur ya?"
-I said, "I'm Miyasako."
-I'm feeling for you, guys.
Ouch.
Did he just hit you? Why?
-Why did you hit me?
-Those stories always get me.
-Because your senior was speaking.
-I'm sorry.
-Listen when your seniors speak.
-Sorry.
-Forget about it.
The timing's gone. Forget about it.
I don't feel like talking anymore.
He's super mad.
You missed out on Miyasako's story
about Sugawara.
-The "ur ya" story?
-It was "Who ur ya?"
Is there a more precious story
than Miyasako's tale about Sugawara?
Right. Bunta's deceased.
His hairdo was super cool
during his final years.
-It was like Juza of the Clouds'.
-It was cool. Airy and combed back.
-Eiko Segawa's hairstyle is cool too.
-She just combs it back.
It's way too long.
If she spiked her hair,
she'd be like Naoki from Laughin' Nose.
-Shut up!
-That's Eiko Segawa.
-It's all the same length?
-That's right.
Shut up!
You mean Michizane?
Michizane? Who's that?
We're talking about Bunta.
-He's in trouble.
-Not Sugawara Michizane.
Fujimoto's losing it.
Can we cut that out?
Yeah, cut it out.
Building on a joke like that.
Shall we get that opening gag?
-No, let's not.
-Not now.
We don't need it?
-But his switch is on, right?
-It would feel wrong not to do it.
I wanted him to do it back then.
It's not the right time now.
Maybe later?
Well, if you really want to.
Yeah. We're okay either way.
I see.
-Later...
-For...
-Why do you sound like Darth Vader?
-I can't breathe...
-You laughed.
-The air's too thin.
-He laughed.
-Right?
That was definitely a laugh.
-You're like Darth Vader.
-No, I'm not. Who's Darth Vader?
Who ur he?
Who ur Darth Vader?
You're not Bunta Sugawara.
Sitting down and Sharon Stone-ing.
Right?
Hang on. Did Nobu just laugh?
-Are you sure he didn't?
-Shut up.
-Are you sure?
-We told you not to perform any gags.
-I'm not allowed?
-We told you.
We said do it later.
-And you agreed.
-I'll give...
-Was that a rehearsal?
-I'll give you a cue.
Don't start by yourself.
Well, there were problems with the timing.
Just now?
Bad timing?
What was that Michizane thing?
-Sugawara...
-Who's laughing? Who?
-Enough already.
-Nobu?
Was it Yoshizane?
-Who's Yoshizane?
-Was that a laugh?
Sugawara Yoshizane?
That's nobody.
That's not your kind of joke.
But that's...
I found that interesting.
-That aspect.
-Michizane...
Does that "Michizane" deserve
so much anger?
He's not angry, just mystified.
It's not like I'm angry.
The joke just didn't feel like you.
I found that interesting.
Can you do Sharon Stone again?
An encore?
-Why are you drinking milk?
-We ran out of water.
-Liar.
-We have plenty of water.
It's gone. Honestly.
-But...
-There was cabbage and...
-Lower.
At the very bottom.
Sitting down and Sharon Stone-ing.
Nothing.
No...
I'm not concerned about my calcium.
You're past your growth spurt.
Growssspu?
-Your growth spurt!
-What's a "Growssspu"?
Nobu's in danger.
-He's been close the whole time.
-We have water.
Nobu and Fujimoto...
Kukky's face is lacking tension today too.
We have cold water
and room-temperature water.
Down below.
It will stick to your mustache.
No, it won't stick to my mustache.
Drink some.
Bottoms up.
He drank it in one gulp.
It stuck.
-It was your own setup.
-Exactly.
-We can laugh now, right?
-It's okay now.
We can laugh?
-That was quick.
-You set it up yourself.
-Wait, wait!
-It was your fault.
-Wait just a second!
-Daigo's out!
-Wait, wait!
-How weak!
-Daigo made a full-on laugh!
-That should be a red card.
No, no!
Wait, wait!
-It wasn't just a smile.
-No!
-You erupted into laughter.
-But...
It really didn't stick to his mustache!
That's not the point.
You blurted out a laugh.
-You're right. It didn't stick.
-But...
-I said it would stick...
-Wait. Just a minute.
Seriously, you're all too loose.
Really?
-Nobu is too loose.
-Okay.
-You're too loose too, Fujimoto.
-Me?
This time, Kukky is too relaxed, too.
Sorry, sorry.
You're all light and fluffy.
-The atmosphere in here is crazy.
-It is. It really is. It's like...
Yeah, the atmosphere is bad. I know.
-It's definitely a bad one.
-I know.
That Sharon Stone series
was pretty dangerous, too.
He commended me. Yippee.
Your saying that means a lot to me.
Thank you.
-Anyway...
-Back to Daigo.
-Daigo.
-Is it a red?
-Yellow.
-Yes, I know.
Let's take a look.
-He gave you a break.
-It really is a break.
-Yeah, but...
-That was a total laugh.
It could've been orange.
I said, "It will stick."
He said, "It won't."
It didn't stick!
That's not my problem.
That's what we have to fight.
It will stick to your mustache.
No, it won't stick to my mustache.
Drink some.
Bottoms up.
He drank it in one gulp.
It stuck.
-It was your own setup.
-Exactly.
-We can laugh now, right?
-It's okay now.
-See that?
-Wait!
-Nobu?
-That was just... Mr. Matsumoto...
-That was a laugh!
That was just, when Daigo...
When Daigo burst into laughter,
I made a triumphant gesture. That's all.
It was after the fact.
-I had seen Daigo erupt.
-You thought, "He laughed."
-I knew he was out.
-I'll judge that one as safe this time.
Anyway, Daigo gets a yellow.
-Okay.
The thing is,
if Daigo hadn't burst into laughter,
probably three more would have.
-Right?
-If you hadn't...
What's wrong, Kurosawa?
-She's crying.
-What's wrong?
She's crying?
-What is it?
-We can't let people like that in here.
-I can't tell her emotional state.
What's up, Kurosawa?
-What is it?
-What's wrong?
We were having fun.
-Are you crying with joy?
-Does that actually happen?
-What is it?
-Really, what is it? Seriously.
It's a man's world.
-"It's a man's world."
-It's a man's world?
But that's not true.
-Sorry for being emotionally unstable.
-It's okay.
If we'd said a lot of dirty jokes,
I could understand, but...
I can't join in the conversation.
I'm an only child. I don't have brothers.
It's no easy feat.
You don't have to force your way in.
Hamburg!
He's so noisy.
-He's too loud.
-He sure has a big voice.
Evil spirit!
I'll drive the evil spirit out of you!
Evil spirits follow you.
Why, oh why? Fruity why.
Bonk my eyeball.
-That's scary.
-It's not good.
It's too scary. Do one more.