4th Time on Gaki No Tsukai!
The 4th time huh?
"Are their hearts connected?" No Smartphone Meetup!
This is the 4th time?
I was speaking
The 4th time
What do you guys think?
It takes us 3 hours on average to meet up
Yeah...
It does take time
The 4th installment of a series designed to test the bonds between these 5
The Rule: The head to a location using the theme on the card. If they all meetup then they succeed
Looking at the past 3 episodes, it seems one man is always dragging everyone behind
Well I didn't wanna say this, but in the end,
Things would go better if Tanaka wasn't here
No come on, maybe for the first one I'm slow,
- Is what I said when I entered Yoshimoto
If this asshole wasn't with us, Yoshimoto wouldn't be in such a state
It wouldn't, it would improve immediately
It's just my recent performance!
The conducter gets pissed off when this guy boards the bullet train
Right away, the first theme is announced
Here I go, ready ... go
A famous bridge intersection
This one is hard
SomethingOrOther-Bridge?
There is one! There is one!
Well starting from here, I don't think it's that far away
Well, we do have a 30 minute limit
Why do you have such a troubled face?!
You went to Numazu in your head right?
TN: Numazu is 1.5 hours away from Tokyo
A bridge intersection; Near NTV in Kojimachi, there are around 150 examples
Do you think you'll meet anyone, at this point?
I think Matsumoto-san might come to this one place
Matsumoto-san and I do have a memory of there
Oh really? A memory about an intersection?
There is!
Sorry! I don't have a single memory with Endo
It was from over 20 years ago
Let's not do that kind of thing
Endo is the first to head off
I wonder if they'll come
Alright
No memories with Endo
On New Year's, he sends a text with some message like "I'll follow you!" right?
He does!
It's so fake right?
Exactly!
He also sent me something like "Senpai, I'll always follow you!", so passionate
What a liar!
Really, he's lying?
He's lying!
They have 30 minutes,
They start heading off to the places they came up with
And Endo, who's relying on a memory with Matsumoto?
Yamate-dori
The intersection ... It wasn't Miyamae-bashi... (Miyamae-bridge)
Nope! I got it wrong, it was Matsumi-zaka (a hill)
It was an intersection with Matsumi-zaka?
I got it wrong, it wasn't a bridge
I'm definitely not meeting Matsumoto-san
Endo mistook a hill for a bridge
Matsumoto-san used to live near there right?
Yeah, and also near there...
There was an intersection with Matsumi-zaka, and he dropped me off there
That place in front of Komaba Campus with the air conditioner?
Yes, yes
Just where is Endo heading?
And what about Matsumoto, who usually meets up first?
Y'know, let's try out Akabono-bashi
There's also Suido-bashi right?
Yes indeed
And we've recorded there a lot right?
I got it, Mr. Driver excuse me,
Suidobashi please
Yes, Suidobashi Intersection
I think at least one person?
I think Hamada might head to Akebonobashi....
That time we met at Akebonobashi, in front of Fuji TV,
I think there might be a memory of that
And that Hamada was still deliberating
I hate this....
I hate this series...
Meanwhile, Tanaka, who always makes everyone wait for him...
I have no idea, honestly
I have a bad feeling about my idea
For now, he gets into the Taxi and plans his destination
The first one that came to mind ... It's that one, uh,
Secret
Ah, I see
I feel like there's a more prevalent intersection with a bridge
In Shibuya, they have that ... "Scrambled Egg" I think it's called
Wait no, what was it called again?
C'mon stop that
And the distance too, I want to pick a place that's not too far away
That's true
Taking distance into consideration, what place did Tanaka come up with?
I'm getting in
And what about Hosei, who's not lived in Tokyo for 4 years?
Eh? Hold on, was that place in Shibuya called Miaymasu-bashi?
I think it's Miyamasu-Zaka
Zaka huh?
There's no Miyamasu-bashi
Eh hold on- Namiki-bashi! Namiki-bashi intersection
There's the JRA, the Ramen store,
A ramen place on Meiji-dori, I think it was called Fumaibo?
That person, I can't remember his name, that guy from Hollywood
It's a ramen place that actor guy likes
Alright, the ramen store that guy likes
Let's head right here
I got a good one! A really good one!
Hosei heads towards Namiki-bashi intersection
Matsumoto, heading towards Suidobashi, remembers something from his youth
Do you remember Korakuen Hall?
They shot the show "Owarai Star Tanjou!!" there
So we'd get off at the station, walk to Korakuen Hall, and practice our material
If anyone comes, it would be Hamada I think
But for Hamada, things like "Owarai Star Tanjou!!", and other stuff that's from the past,
He really doesn't remember them
Hamada, a man with poor memory, heads off without deciding a destination
Nothing at all?
Ah!
I got it!
There's gotta be only one answer for this,
Where is Hamada headed?
This one, I got it - What's the first place that comes to mind when you think of Japan?
Please head to Nihon-bashi (Japan-bridge)
Understood
The "Wings of a Qilin"
This is the only answer! Everyone will head there!
Makes sense
Right?!
What other options could there possibly be? What if they complain...
With 3 people likely to meet, all 5 have decided their destinations
Will anyone be able to meet up?
Timed and Typeset by Kedomas
Translation by senor_wristband
Downtown no Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
Matsumoto screams for some reason
Are their hearts connected?
Are their hearts connected? No Smartphone Meetup!
The theme; a typical bridge intersection
Endo, the first one to head off, arrives at his chosen intersection
It's huge!
Where should I stand?
Iidabashi intersection
Suidobashi is over there right?
You know, I did consider Suidobashi
But I picked Iidabashi over Suidobashi
And right in front of Endo...
Well certainly, that is true
He encounters Matsumoto, heading towards Suidobashi
This is the Iidabashi intersection
Right
I don;t think have any memories at Iidabashi intersection
However Endo once again misses...
And doesn't notice Matsumoto passing by him to Suidobashi
Oh right, Iidabashi could've been an option
Then Hosei arrives at his chosen intersection in Shibuya; Namikibashi Intesection
Ah, wow! Look how clearly you can see the name
Namikibashi~
Ah, Santouka! The place I was talking about before
I remember everything now! Keanu Reeves loves that place
Yeah, Keanu Reeves loves that place
Matsumoto gets off at Suidobashi intersection
Surely they won't come out of the water, right?
Just zipping down there
They're not coming!
Idiots!
Meanwhile, Hamada arrives at Nihonbashi
It's written very clearly "The First Bridge In Japan"
This is the start isn't it?
Oi, they're not here! What's the meaning of this?
That's where Nakai Kiichi fainted isn't it?!
Eh? you gotta be kidding me....
Everyone but Tanaka has arrived at their location
Matsumoto has already been waiting for 10 minutes
This is hopeless!
Tanaka is the only one still in transit
COME ON!
DAMMIT~!!
DId you hear that? Tanaka is still driving!
Well, it would be nice to end this early
Before the mood drops?
Right, yes
Everyone will be happy, the cast, the staff, everyone
That guy really is a pain
Cause it's fine if he had the wrong idea...
But I mean, making your senior wait for this long?
Tanaka arrives to his destination, and obviously nobody else is there
Time Up
No way...
The 5 call each other to confirm their locations
Hamada where are you?
The start of Japan! Nihonbashi of course!
"The start of Japan"?
NIHONBASHI?!
SO FAR!
It's not far! It's right ahead of Ginza, it's right there
Also, Nihonbashi is a pretty high-end district,
Yeah it's a high-end district
I think they wouldn't want Hamada there
Why wouldn't they want me here?
It's gotta be Suidobashi intersection!
Ah! He said Suidobashi, it's right there!
Come on!
Hamada-san! Hamada-san
If you remember the auditions for "Owarai Star Tanjou", and the filiming as well, you'd come here
Korakuen Hall, right?!
Let's not use reasons like that. I mean, even if you say that...
Hosei-san, Hosei-san where are you?
Namikibashi
I aplogise, to the people involved with Naimikibashi I apologise,
Naimikibashi, is pathetic
Hold on, it's not pathetic!
I am at Iidabashi
Iidabashi?
I get it Endo! You're really close by
What was that memory with Matsumoto-san?
It wasn't a bridge, it was a hill, it was Matsumi-zaka. I got it mixed up, sorry
Enough! It's cold so hurry up Tanaka! Idiot!
Ike- ikejiri-ohashi - Oh -
Ikejiri-ohashi!
Ikejiri-ohashi?!
Seriously??
No no no no no no no no no Enough!
Tanaka has the worst idea, after all
Tanaka was the only one who thought of an overhead bridge crossing; Ikejiri-ohashi
Enough of that area of yours
No no no it's a huge intersection!
Let's meet up at the next one!
Let's meet up!
Tanaka is at Ohashi...
Ohashi?!
Right?
Tanaka really is different
But it should'be been here!
If you think about the metro area, and the distance as well
Is it really possible nobody came to this major intersection?
Nobody met up with the first theme!
Starting over, time for the 2nd theme
Oi! What the hell is this?
A place with a lot of autograph plaques?
You can find autograph plaques of celebrities on the walls of restaurants,
The 5 think of a place that fits this desciption best
I can only think of that one place
That's the only place I can associate with famous people
There's one that I though of immediately, it's in Asakusa
But I think distance-wise, that's a difficult choice
This is so hard
Have you ever put up your autograph?
I can't really remember, what stores I've done that in
The only place I can remember being asked for my autograph is the Hihokan in Atami
TN: Hihokan is a sex museum
Ah, there's one place I went to on a shoot, I just remembered
I was on a shoot with Shimura-san
A Blowfish restaurant in Azabujunban
"The Earth was Blue" - Gagarin! They had Gagarin's autograph
On different TV shows I've done segments on this topic,
About stores that have lots of autographs
I know a lot of places, I can't really narrow it down right now
Endo has so many options he can't narrow them down
Will we really meet up for this one?
There's one place...
Ah no, that's not it
Kamukura, right?
Yeah Kamukura, let's go to Kamukura
Matsumoto heads to Kamukura, a ramen place in Shibuya
Where should we wait?
Will they let us in?
If they let us in, we'll be lucky
I think they will, I have a Black Card for Kamukura
There's a lot more shops like that in Osaka
But we would never meet up in Osaka
How would this turn out if we were in Osaka?
If this was in Osaka ... We could do it
It would be impossible in Nagoya
DownTown have no chance of meeting, but the other 3 just might
Wasn't there that one steak place?
Ribera?
Ribera!
They have Pro-wrestler's autographs
Yes yes
Yamasaki might go there, to that Ribera
But I think Yamasaki wouldn't really think about eating meat, he's a herbivore after all
Yamasaki chose a meat specialty restaurant, Jojoen Yugentei
Just in case, he goes inside to check there are autographs on the walls
Hello
But then!
A lot of entertainers come here on their private time,
So this store doesn't really ask for autographs
Ah, you don't ask for autographs?
Yes
We have this here
Ah right, right
I saw this before, and that made me think this place has a lot of autographs
But still look at it please, there are so many autographs on there
Hold on
Hold on!
This is not autograph plaque, but a single Golf Competition's signboard!
Oh crap
Oh no
A place with a lot of autograph plaques!
This is bad
Meanwhile Hamada arrives at the store in Azabujuban
Excuse me
Hello!
Ah, welcome
Manager, is Gagarin's autograph here?
Ah, this one
This... This is...
See! They had it!
Look!
The storeperson researched this, and it might be the autograph of Gagarin's junior
I didn't make a mistake with this place then
That's mine!
Who is this?
I don't remember at all, I can't even tell from the writing
Meanwhile, Matusmoto arrives at Kamukura ramen store in Shinjiku
He claims to be a black card member, and gets in right away
It's time to confirm there are autograph plaques here
But then!
An unexpected surprise! Just what in the diggity doggone goddamned hell just happened?!!?!?!?!?!
Matsumoto is at Kamukura in Shinjiku, looking for autograph plaques,
But then,
We don't have any of the plaques right now actually...
We took them down
We renovated
There were a ton of them in the past right?
Eh? Not anymore?
Yeah, we renovated
When?
We renovated June last year
Indeed, up until last year there was a wall with a ton of plaques,
But not they've renovated, and not one remains
I think I had my autograph up there too, what happened to it?
I think they have it at the headquarters
Time Up here!
The 5 report their locations
We're all alone
Eh? We're all alone again?
Seriously?
Hamada, where are you?
I'm in Azabujuban
A blowfish restaurant, Fugu-take
Oh right! The first floor right?
Ah yeah, Fugu-take
There's no way we would all go there!!
Well, I did sort of give up on that part,
Where are you Endo?
Akasaka Ramen
Akasaka ramen?
Endo went to Akasaka ramen, where he ate often in his youth
Currently, they have 145 autograph plaques hung up
Also, our autograph is also there
See
That is something to be thankful for
That idea is no good
I'm at that place you associate with celebrities; The Jojoen Yugentei in Nishi-Azabu!
Too much Yugentei!
You went to Yugentei too once
Well yeah, isn't that a good thing?!
Tanaka, where are you?
In Nakame, the Torigoya, the Motsunabe restaurant
That was an option too
How many plaques are there?
They're closed so I can't see inside-
What the hell is that
Based on a memory from over 10 years ago, he decided on the Torigoya in Nakameguro
In fact, they have tons of plaques on their walls
That store is the one I'm most satisfied with out of the other ones
Matsumoto-san, where are you?
If you're from Kansai then you should know!
Ramen Kamukura
Ramen Kamukura?
Shibuya?
They had a 2 story store in Kabukicho,
There were an egregious amount of plaques on the second floor,
And I came here after a long time ... However they've renovated, there's not a single one left
See!
Then that's a bad location to pick
How the hell was I supposed know?!
Are we gonna meet today?
Horrible. This might be our worst one yet!
Next Week - No Smartphone Meetup Finale!
The theme; A large tennis court
There's 6 of them!
6!
Everyone is having so much fun!
Tanaka makes a series of unfathomable choices!
Odaiba, I'm in Odaiba
You don't go Odaiba on NTV!
And more; An encounter with a celebrity!
Will they be able to meet?!
Timed and Typeset by Kedomas
Translation by senor_wristband