Gaki no Tsukai presents- Risk it on this mouth full
Prize money worth 10,000 Yen- Potato Chips!!! (OR CRISPS!!)
Number 29!
Number 29!?
And we haven't done this one so far?..
No, we hadn't done this one yet.
Last time, on Kiki Apple Juice
Tanaka got it right (First time in 9 years!)
First time in 9 years
My god, Tanaka.
It took me 9 years..
You, with your nose illness.
Your ill nose finally..
It doesn't matter, I got it right finally!
But anyway, today, Yamazaki-san's confidence is just ridiculous
It really is.
Because seriously, I really love Potato Chips.
Ye, you are always eating it.
You do, you really do.
I eat like, so much!
Honestly, I literally like, never eat it.
Me neither..
But today, out of 24 people, 6 got it, so its a 1 in 4 chance of getting it.
So someone should get it right for sure.
No way...
Apparently all the people who got it right are 'gay'
For christs sake, stop that..
I don't get why only the 'homosexual's' got it right?..
But... Most of the Gaki no Tsukai are 'gay' you know?
Really?!
I don't think anyone is!
DOWNTOWN GAKI NO TSUKAI
Presented to you by MICKSTAR.
Follow me on Twitter @Mickstar_GNT for latest news on videos and PLEASE like my Facebook Page.
Kiki Potato Chips. Out of the 15 choices of them
You taste one whilst blindfolded, then have to taste and see which one is the one you ate. Get it right, 10,000 Yen, get it wrong, and a punishment awaits...
First off is Yamazaki, who has so much confidence in getting it right.
The answer to his 'selection' is the 'lightly salted Koikeya' Potato Chips
OH!
I've eaten this before!
He's gone for it.
Whenever he eats here, he always changes the way he bites and stuff.
Let me ask you something
Is it a new potato style?
Or a normal style potato?
Right, let's go.
Ok. Good luck.
Good luck!
Wait, let me just eat a bit more.
You know...
They're all the same you know?
I'm going for it!
Sure.
No seirously, just go for it.
I really eat this one like, loads!
Honestly..
Either Karbi, KOIKEYA,
One of these three.
Oh?
Or...
You're saying 'Or?'...
You said three...
I'm about 80% sure it's one of those three.
And..
This one.. This one or this one.
There's loads now...
This one will...
The numbers are seriously increasing...
They only sell this one in Family Mart.
There's a huge choice now...
No, at the beginning you sounded so sure...
Oh, that's how it is...
He couldn't even make me feel nervous or relaxed there at all...
I couldn't even make you laugh, nervous or relaxed??
You weren't intimidating, you weren't funny...
Let's have none of that...
Hold on a second...
God, he's taking ages..
Hurry up and pick the one you think it is.
He's not eating at all!
Let's go for it man!
Can I first eat this one? By eating this...
I will be able to tell the difference.
What do you mean, what do you mean?
You do know that now you're eating it, you're going to have to decide if it is the right one or not, right?
Of course, of course.
No, this is different, even from the scent, it's different.
That potato is really yellow...
It's SO different.
The potato chip I ate...
Was NOT
The Sant Cashio.
Go on, get it right.
Ye,
So what was so different?
First, the feeling
The smell
Even the feeling on my finger.
And when it was on my tongue.
So from the very start?
Yep, the very start.
All the 5 different senses said it was wrong.
It's that different, huh?
I've definitely eaten this before, I'm going to try this 'Boku no Oyatsu'
Hang on a second, this is dangerous.
What the hell
What the hell, man?!
What is it?
Whatever happens, you need a tempo
And your tempo... Has been
Shit from the first day you started on set.
How many years has he been in this industry again?..
Even though his tempo is shit,
He is able to spot the difference
And gets through 2 more bags.
I think I'm just going to go for it.
It can't be helped.
King?
King. It's these three.
It has to be one of these 3.
Ok, let's go for it. I'm going to try this one.
No, it's wrong.
The feeling on my finger is totally different.
It's totally wrong.
The potato chips I ate.
Was not the...
Lightly salted 'Koikeya'
You're so uncool..
What the hell, man!
Hurry up and come to the front.
You're kidding me!!!
I can't help you. You're really pathetic..
Here he comes!
God, he's ugly..
*&%(&$(*#$& (I think he says 'Motto Baito Shiroyo!' which means 'Bite it more!'
No idea what he just said..
&#$*#$&!*#&! (I think 'Kono Ringo yaro' meaning 'You apple shit..(?)'
That's why he's scary... That's exactly why...
That was really hard...
That looks so painful...
That has got to hurt..
It's this one.
No way!
It's not.
That man was so ugly!..
Aww, am I finished already?...
Yes, you're finished.
Please let me do it one more time...
No, the viewers don't want to see you anymore.
Next, is Endo, who says he hardly ever eats Potato Chips
The answer for his one will be one which they sell only at the supermarket store, Life.
Kurashimoa Potato Chips
Going to try the salt...
Well they are all salted....
They're all lightly salted.
There's like a thickness to it... And wow! It's really tastes of potatos.
Well, obviously it's going to be.
I know, but..
Did you think it wouldn't or something?..
It really felt like.. thick.
You were saying it felt thick.
I'm going to try this one. Housei-san went for it as well.
San Nicasio...
It's totally wrong.
It's so different!
I'm so sick and tired of hearing 'It's so different'
The potato chips I ate...
was not the..
San Nicasio...
Next, he got through the 2nd packet of crisps with no problem.
This is one I sometimes eat...
'Karbi' huh?
Karbi Potato Chips...
I'm going to try this one.
Karbi, huh?
The thickness is similar...
So far, you've said that the other ones..
Weren't thick enough to be the right one, right?
Yep, that's what he said.
It's thicker, right?
But unlike this one, which you eat from time to time...
Oh man....
Have I really already met the one?
He said that the potato taste was really thick..
He's literally got his back to us.
Why are you facing that way?
What the hell man?
What's wrong?
I can really taste the potato.
Like, I can really taste the potato fully.
When I licked the 'correct one' before,
I thought it was like...
Even though it's 'lightly salted'
It's literally stuck on your nose though, you know?
Oh man, this is like seriously...
Like, the salt is really thick and...
The thickness is the same, and that last feeling...
of the potato chip..
So why are you still taking the chip and walking over there to eat it then?!
Eat it over here..
He shouldn't turn his back to us...
This is like... It's come.
It came all of a sudden..
And when I told my daughter today 'I'm off to do Kiki' she was so happy...
You're daughter will be watching right now as well, right?
Ye for sure. She was asking me to put it on a DVD and everything...
So far, you know...
Even if a close relative was watching, they wouldn't be interested.
Sorry, I'm going to take the last one..
I've got nothing against how much you eat..
Oh man, seriously, today...
My daughter will definitely be watching as well...
This part is crucial, you know?
Daddy's going to do it!
He's really going to do it!
The one I ate..
IS the Karbi Potato Chips!
This is really...
terrible.
Stop going for..
the girls who like like potatos...
That's a very rude thing to say.
His daughter!!
Ye, my daughter's watching you know!
I wonder why this time, the guy was able to say it so well..
This is the one you ate before.
This is the one...
Oh... Ye, they're the same.
Third is the man who's got the right answer 5 times.
Hamada.
His answer is one that uses healthy products..
Soukensha Potato chips.
The piece that fell back into the plate was bigger...
How the hell do you manage to drop more than you actually eat?...
He's even moving weirdly from left to right...
You know, when Yama-chan and Endo said
the salt was quite strong?
Yes?
This ones quite weak.
I think it also has to do with your body condition.
Like salt intake...
My body is in its prime!
Ye, they're all salted aren't they..
But as I said before, this is quite strong on the salt right?
Of course
It would be totally weird if there was
consomme here, wouldn't it?
Right now, I'm looking at the ingredients.
But if you were to ask me, I wouldn't say it has much salt on it.
I feel sorry for the Potato Chips
They're being stared down...
From quite close range too..
I feel so sorry for them!
It must be horrible for them...
This one...
Soukensha..
Everyone sniff it huh?
I'm guessing the scent's strong
No, it definitely is important
Ok, he's gone for it now.
He certainly did
I have no idea at all
It's the first one!
I thought he was going to say 'It's totally wrong'
So it's a shock to me that he said 'I have no idea'
Well they're all potato chips!
Well ye, they are but..
But you were saying something about the salt?
When I compare it to before, this one has a little bit more..
Is the taste strong?
Ye.
But, if someone told me this was the correct one, I would say
Oh right..
But if it's totally different, it's totally different
WHAT?
Every time we do Kiki, your ears never seem to work...
No, he can never hear us...
I have no idea at all!
Who gives a shit!
This is where you got to try hard and work it out
That's the whole point of this corner..
I mean even the fat is like...
completely the same. They're all the same.
My god, he's looking at us..
What the hell is this?!
In a few years time
He will be doing this alone at home, you know?
While mumbling about it...
While mumbling about it?..
Oh, I have no idea but..
It had more salt than the one I had before so it must be wrong!
The Potato Chips I ate...
was NOT the lightly salted Soukensha..
IT'S THE FIRST ONE!
The first one!
Are you serious!?
You were lucky!
Ye, and then I thought he would get it right!
I really thought 'God, he's so lucky'
Ye..
Seriously
You've got to be kidding me!
Here he comes!
This really hurts...
Your sense of taste...
It's worse than...
No idea..
It sounded kind of philosophical..
What did I do wrong?!
He hit me even though I didn't really do anything wrong to him!
He said 'worse than'
You can't hit me without saying anything!
Are you serious!
Next is
Tanaka, who last time for the first time in 9 years, got the correct answer
Tanaka-san, you eat quite a bit right?
I really love the stuff.
However
But it's the Karbi
Which I'm crazy about and eat all the time
So I'm not really sure about the others...
His answer is Yamnoshi's
Okinawa's Umami Shio Aji'
Are you a French person?
It's crunchy!
All of them are!
You love the stuff though, right?
Ye, like seriously
I eat like, so many of these
How many bags do you get through a year?
In a week, I will definitely have eaten a packet at least.
I've eaten hundreds of packs of these, ever since I was a kid.
That's loads
That's more than Yamazaki.
But that's why I'm going to automatically compare everything to this now..
I haven't eaten..
Any of the others
So I need to find out the difference
Tarimono Shoukai
This uses Olive Oil
I see.
No, the olive oil is really strong
The olive oil's different?
No, it's wrong!
It's not this one!
The one I ate...
Was not Tanimoto Shoukai no Olive Oil Potato Chips!
Well that one was easy..
Now he's gained a bit of confidence from that one.
It was like really crunchy..
The Shizuoka-san Potato chips
His nose is buggered...
Ye, it's been like 20 years now..
Then why is he smelling it?
I think he wants to do the same thing as other people..
It's just to look good, huh?
Oh, he's posing?
No, the feeling is wrong.
The one I ate was crunchier.
The one I ate was
Not the Mikata Potato Chips
Hang on a second...
He's been doing a one man show for a while now...
Like a little play or something...
He's going to perform at the Aoyama Theatre (place were comedians trying to make it appear to make a name for themselves)
I want to know if there are other ones
which have this crunchiness, that's what I want to know
We were all the same..
But you should be able to get it since you eat it all the time.
I really felt it was crunchy
I really felt it was crispy and had a solid taste
The thing I'm scared about
If there is like another type
of crunchiness.
You said basically the same thing before!
We have no idea what you mean!
They're all crunchy!
I'm sure they're all crunchy.
They're made like that
I'm going for it
Oh please, I beg you.
I really want to get this one right.
The Potato Chips I ate..
WAS the Fukayayoshi no
Hokkaido Potato Chips!
This is too hard!
It's so difficult!
I don't want to do it anymore..
Shall I fry you in some oil as well!?
That one, we understood
I understood that one.
Umm, excuse me?
Can we please do it properly?
The guy today is just riduculous!
That was like un-heard of!
His understandings of shapes is just shit!
So far, this is the WORST the 4 members have ever done in a Kiki.
Can Matsumoto save the show..
And get the correct answer?
Who's got the eye mask?
The eye mask?
It's ok, seriously, no problem.
No no, just in case.
You'll definitely look
I will do it like this..
No, you'll look
And you wouldn't be able to eat it either with your hands there.
The answer to Matsumoto will be the same as it was to Yamazaki
Koikeya's Nishi Nihon Potato Chips
Hmmm... I see, I see
Shall I tell you something that you guys have missed out on?
The lighter ones.
The fat shapes too.
That's disgusting!
Wait, what, what, what is it?
Oi, you.
Don't say that it's disgusting so loudly..
I do have feelings too you know?..
You know this part which is a little different?
Some have it and some don't.
I think that's a big clue
I think most of them have that...
Ye, they do. They all do I think..
And plus, that could confuse you..
There's like no saltiness at all!
Ye, I felt exactly the same when I ate mine too.
Hang on, I'm pretty sure I've eaten this one before.
I've eaten this one before!
I... Have eaten this one before!
Right then, let's go.
Ok, good luck!
For someone like me, who doesn't eat potato chips much
to say he has eaten it before...
It's going to be around here.
I see.
Can I just go for Honmaru Karbi?..
Well ye, sure, why not.
I don't get why he's asking
But you know how I can be quite like, reckless sometimes?
I don't think you are that kind of guy to be honest, but ok...
I've never listened to like theories or rules or morales and I have always
crushed them throughout my life
That's not true at all!
It's got to be one of these three.
I've definitely eaten it before.
And to be honest, I think you would have chosen one of these three last.
I'm actually going to go for King Potato Chips now.
I'm going to tuck in.
With no breaks.
Well you've just got to decide on wether it's right or wrong.
Just in case, let's go for this one.
The one next to it?
The one next to it?..
He chose the one next to it..
After that speech, he went straight to the one next to it..
I get it..
This is totally different.
I could laugh...
I'm telling you, I could laugh at it..
It's so wrong that I don't even need a second one.
The potato chips I ate
Was not the Koikeya lightly salted Potato Chips
The Honmaru one is the scary one...
This one.
I really get it.
This one is too hard!
It wasn't like this, it wasn't like this!
God, I want to smack him
Please smack him.
It's totally different, I get it.
The Potato Chips I ate
was NOT the Koikeya Potato, hang on
Wasn't the one before the same?
That one is different.
Oh... It's NOT the Nishi Nihon Gentei.
No, no, no
It doesn't count, it doesn't count.
No, it does.
You can't do it again.
Let me do it once more.
No, you can't!
LET ME DO IT ONE MORE TIME, GODDAMN IT!
LET ME DO IT ONE MORE TIME!
No, that's not allowed!
Just bring him to the front.
How can we show this to the public?!
How can we put this on air!?
Let me do this once more!
You got it wrong..
Bring him to the front!
How can we air something so crap!
Let me do it once more!
Just hurry up!
You really were pathetic
That really was pathetic.
Why the hell is he getting so angry?!
You serious?!
You have a head like a...
Potato and...
................................
And?.. A potato and?
God, he forgets the words a lot..
He really does forget the words a lot..
Say something!
When he said at the beginning, because he was last
We might choose one of the ones we chose the near the beginning..
Ye I know..
You know, we chose the same one as we did for Yamazaki at the start/
I thought he was thinking like that as well.
I told you so!
Your voice went crazy there!
You're voice is like nearly gone.
No seriously, bring me the eye mask
Oh, who cares.
No seriously, seriously.
I'm mucking around now..
Let's go, let's go.
Ok, but I will leave him the eye mask anyway.
Ye, just leave him the eye mask
Actually, it's ok. I'll just do it like this..
Who's going to choose it and bring it to you?
Someone help him out.
Hurry up, hurry up.
It's not like I can see at all.
I'm really sad and lonely now..
Stop making me wait..
PRESENTED BY MICKSTAR. FOLLOW ME ON @Mickstar_GNT