Translation by ShibataBread
www.shibatabread.com
Edited by Mrs. ShibataBread
Follow her on twitter @tofupizza
First Annual Gaki No Tsukai Ya Arahende
I have always wanted to try this challenge
Absolutely Tasty
Tempura Tournament !!!!
Let's look back at our previous tournaments
Downtown
Hitoshi Matsumoto
Masatoshi Hamada
We've cooked with Rice, Pizza,
Cocorico
Shozo Endo
Naoki Tanaka
Taiyaki, Chawanmushi, and Mochi so far
By the way, Matsumoto-san,
Hosei Yamasaki
you scored a perfect 10
using wedding cake as an ingredient
Wedding Cake Mochi
A Perfect 10
Oh, did he ?
I confess I'm not really into this series...
How come ?
Today's Theme
Members prepare two "Absolutely Tasty Tempura" dishes
graded on a scale of 1 to 10
I just don't feel good about
satisfying my hunger this way
I'm with you
This ends up being your dinner for the night
Right, and to top it off,
I won't want to go out afterwards
Right
And I don't even get to eat something I like
Downtown Presents:
Gaki No Tsukai Ya Arahende
Sponsor
Eiffel
Narration By
Shinichi Yamada
Tempura by Tanaka
First up is Tanaka
What is his ingredient ?
Here's my first ingredient
I see
What's this ?
These are Strawberry Bean Rice Cakes
Ingredient
Strawberry Bean Rice Cake
There's strawberry in there
We all know
how well strawberry and mochi tastes together
There's no doubt this will turn out great
Frying Mochi itself would be good,
but you're taking the extra step with the strawberry
I'm going for it
I'm curious to see how this turns out
Here's my second ingredient
Here it is
A bundle of flowers
Ingredient
Bouquet of Edible Flowers
I don't get this
This is edible ?
Yes, it is
I'm using Chrysanthemum flowers
Why flowers ?
You are AGERU(To Fry) the AGERU(To Give a Gift)
I see your pun
Right, and I'm going to AGERU(To Fry) it even further
Because I'm frying this whole thing
We can eat it ?
Don't worry, these are edible flowers
Just so we're clear on that
Tanaka's 1st Dish
Strawberry Bean Mochi Tempura
Here's Tanaka's first ingredient
First, the strawberry bean mochi
are battered and then fried
Here we go
That scared me a little
That looks good
Tanaka's 2nd Dish
Flower Tempura
Incredible !
Here I go
Wach it, watch it
Shove that whole thing in there
There will only be crumbs left
You're right
Tanaka's 1st Dish:
"Strawberry Bean Mochi Tempura"
Here's Tanaka's strawberry bean mochi tempura
How will they fare ?
I'm seriously starving right now
This will be perfect then
Well, I just want something decent
They look good so far
Tanaka's 1st Dish
Strawberry Bean Mochi Tempura
Couldn't this show hire a real waitress ?
I agree
Hey, come back here
Seriously, this is where we can do better
It's insulting having this guy serve us
Yorihisa Ezure
I mean he would be my one millionth choice
from the bottom of the world population
Tanaka, your mochi looks different
You're right
You're the one who made it, so that's why
This dish has the potential to be a big hit
We'll see
This one looks great so far
Itadakimasu
I hate how it's dripping
This is tasty
Isn't this delicious ?
This is good
Right ?
Delicious
I admit this is good but...
not much changed from the original
I second that
This isn't THAT good
So, the breading is SATSUMA IMO (Sweet Potato)...
But why Sweet Potato ?
Huh ?
Hold on, we need to figure out what just happened
Wait, I meant to say SATSUMA AGE (Fried Fish)
You got those two words mixed up ?
But you get it, right ?
Tell your wife, Chiaki, about this
She needs to know about this
Tell her this wasn't sweet potato
Yes, just so she's clear on this
Chiaki !
This wasn't sweet potato !
What's this all about ?
Tanaka's 1st Dish:
"Strawberry and Bean Mochi Tempura"
The flavor didn't live up to its appearance and receives 5 points
Tanaka's 2nd Dish: "Flower Tempura"
His second ingredient is a bouquet of flowers
How does this taste ?
Tanaka's 2nd Dish
Flower Tempura
Great first impression for sure
Will you take a look at this ?
Amazing !
This serves how many people ?
Can you hold that up ?
Yeah, you got it
So far, the presentation is awesome
It's grand
Itadakimasu
This isn't so bad, is it ?
Is this really edible ?
Not good
No can do
It tastes like
I'm rolling around on the grassy lawn
3 points...
2 or 3 points...
2 or 3 points ?
You scored 5 points with your first one so...
You'd give me 3 points for this ?
Tanaka's 2nd Dish:"Flower Tempura"
The flavor didn't live up to its appearance and receives 3 points
Next up is Endo
Tempura by Endo
What are his ingredients ?
Here's my first ingredient !!!!
Seedless grapes !
Let me just eat them as is !!
Ingredient
Grapes (Kyoho)
Let me eat them now !
They're so good on their own
I understand they're good right now
but today I'm frying these as Tempura !
Then, I'm hoping this item will finally work wonders this time
Here it is !
FRISK mints !
Ingredient
Frisk
Cut it out !
Please....Frisk ?!!
I'm begging you !
Did anyone from Frisk ever contact you ?
No, zero, nada
Will Endo's passionate plea be answered ?
Endo's 1st Dish
Grape Tempura
Imagine if you were the grapes right now...
Well, grapes are never subjected to this treatment
I'm not kidding
It's like Yosuke Eguchi doused in flour
Here I go
What the heck...?
Chef, won't it explode ?
No, it shouldn't
Grapes, I'm counting on you
The Frisk mints get fried like a "mixed tempura"
Endo's 2nd Dish
Frisk Tempura
I see
So that how this would look fried
Man, I can tell it's a failure already
I don't even have to eat that
So here's my Frisk in mixed tempura form
Endo's 1st Dish: "Grape Tempura"
Endo's first dish is grape tempura
How does it taste ?
Endo's 1st Dish
Grape Tempura
They look amazing
I don't know what to say...
It smells good
It's like a work of art
Yeah, it looks like that
They're straight out of the fryer
Itadakimasu !
Hot !
This is way too hot, moron !
Hot !!!
It's too hot to eat
Hot !!
I've never had such hot grapes before..
Hot !
It's good !
No way
Not for me
I wouldn't say this is "good"
But...
Considering how low your expectation was,
I think it deserves a good score
Well then, how many points would you give ?
Because this faced a tough obstacle,
I'd say at least 8 points...
Not any lower than that
Don't be a moron
8 points ?
I give you 4 points
Only 4 points ??
If we gave you 8 points for this,
then it would be a part of an every day diet
Endo's 1st Dish: "Grape Tempura"
Endo's grape tempura fails to become part of a daily diet and receives 4 points
Endo's 2nd Dish: "Frisk Tempura"
His second ingredient is Frisk
Will Endo's prayer be answered ?
Endo's 2nd Dish
Frisk Tempura
What the hell....??
Isn't this what you find inside Donbei Cup Noodles ??
It certainly looks...
It certainly looks like it would be great with noodles
Itadakimasu
I can smell this already
This is like...
some kind of curse
The mint flavor has completely taken over
I'm simply stunned
Wouldn't you run home if you saw this in your bento box ?
And you'd do this at the door as your mom opened it
Endo's 2nd Dish: "Frisk Tempura"
Endo's prayer wasn't answered, and it received a skull and crossbones
Next up is Yamasaki
Tempura by Yamasaki
What did he choose ?
Shall I begin ?
Here they are !
They look promising
They are none other than
Donburi Bowls
First we have the Chicken Bowl
Ingredients
Chicken Bowl
Second is the Mabo Tofu
Mabo Tofu
Last is the Curry Bowl
Curry Bowl
Can we just have them as is ?
No kidding
Well, today's theme is to create Tempura so...
Anyhow, these are difficult ingredients for tempura
so I prepared them like this
These are the same as the contents in the 3 bowls ...
Are they frozen ?
Yes, they're frozen
Good idea
Yes, they're really frozen
Yamasaki's idea is to freeze the ingredients
before they're fried
And here's my second ingredient
What's this ?
This isn't good
Ingredient
Jelly-Beans
They are...
I'm frying them in a mixed tempura form
They sure look colorful and pretty right now
Yamasaki's 1st Dish
3 Frozen Bowl Tempura
First, Yamasaki fries up each member's choice of ingredients
Yamasaki's second ingredient, Jelly-Beans,
Yamasaki's 2nd Dish
Jelly-Beans Tempura
gets fried in mixed tempura form
They sure look colorful
It has nice color to it
Looks like mixed vegetables
Yamasaki's 1st Dish: 3 Frozen Bowl Tempura
Yamasaki's first ingredients are 3 different frozen bowls
How do they taste ?
I picked Mah-bo-Tofu
Yamasaki's 1st Dish
3 Frozen Bowl Tempura
Mabo Tofu
Matsumoto
Curry Bowl
Hamada
Endo
Yamasaki
Chicken Bowl
Tanaka
I had curry
I also chose curry
And I'm having curry also
I got the chicken bowl
Chicken Bowl Tempura
Are we good ?
Mabo Tofu Tempura
Couldn't you have picked something other than curry ?
Curry Bowl Tempura
What ?
I chose the Tofu and he got the Chicken
Why did you pick curry when two others already have it ?
Let's keep things balanced
My motto is to eat whatever I want...
I see you never grew out of selfish celebrity status
Itadakimasu
Man, this is still cold
You're right
This is cold
It's too bad because this is good
This is good
Seriously, try mine
It's so good
Let me get all that breading, too
You're right
It's delicious
I'm thinking 9 points
Yeah, 9 points
Really ?
That's good news
That made me happy
Yamasaki's 1st Dish: 3 Frozen Bowl Tempura
It could have received a perfect score if fully cooked
Yamasaki's 2nd Dish: Jelly-Belly Tempura
Yamasaki's second choice is Jelly-Beans Tempura
Here we have yet another artsy dish
Yamasaki's 2nd Dish
Jelly-Beans Tempura
It sure is colorful
Itadakimasu
How sweet is this ?
Go home, asshole !
This is way too sweet
Well...
It's edible ??
The heat...
The heat really brought out the sugary taste
I see
I mean, it doesn't help matters
that the Jelly-Beans are already so sweet
Yamasaki's 2nd Dish: Jelly-Beans Tempura
Criticized for being "too sweet," the dish received 2 points
Next up is Hamada
Tempura By Hamada
What are his choices for Tempura ?
Here's my first one
Ingredient
Dried Kelp Shaving
Oh, haven't seen that in years
It's Fujikko's Jyuntoro
C'mon, you must have seen this recently
This is Tororo (Dried Kelp Shaving)
Each packet contains one serving so ...
So you're frying that whole thing ?
I see you're frying one packet for each of us
You love the thick and gooey stuff
What do you mean by that ?
I've never seen anyone do that ?
It has more volume than I thought
Here's my second choice
Ingredients
Sliced Bread
Corn Soup
So instead of using conventional tempura batter,
I'm going to use this corn soup
I'm soaking the bread in the soup before frying it
That's really an old-fart's way of thinking
*Use Corn Soup as battering
How will corn soup turn out as the tempura batter ?
First step is to batter the dried kelp
Hamada's 1st Dish
Dried Kelp Shaving
Man, it looks like a cocoon
You're right
I see
It doesn't want to sink
You're right, it's floating
I have the soup ready in this pan
Hamada's 2nd Dish
Bread in Corn Soup Tempura
I'm going to coat the bread like so
I see you already have the soup ready in a pan
Yes
I've got a feeling that I'm going to like this
Corn soup is one of my favorites
What is this ?
I'm afraid this will be a hit
Very innovative if this works out well
No-frill frying
Dip your hand in !
That was close
I almost had him, too
With such high expectations for Hamada's dish,
how will it taste ?
Hamada's 1st Dish: Dried Kelp Shaving Tempura
First is the Grated Yam Tempura
How does it taste ?
It looks good so far
Hamada's 1st Dish
Dried Kelp Shaving Tempura
How do you like this presentation ?
Well, it sort of resembles a toupee
Yes it does
It has weight to it
It's fluffy
Itadakimasu
It's hot
I don't know what to say...
Hot !
I have to say...
this isn't that bad
If this was in smaller pieces, it could be a successful dish
Not like this one giant piece
You think so ?
The inside is still really dense and hard
Look at this
It looks like @#$%
Don't try to duck
Hamada's 1st Dish: Dried Kelp Shaving Tempura
The No-Holds-Barred grated yam receives 5 points
How will this creative corn soup batter idea do ?
Hamada's 2nd Dish:
Bread in Corn Soup Tempura
This dish could just be...
Hamada's 2nd Dish
Bread in Corn Soup Tempura
a breakfast food ?
Right, it could be
I'm getting a good vibe from this
I'm feeling this so far
It smells awesome, too
Very good so far
It does smell good
Really good
Itadakimasu
How about just 10 points for this, yeah ?
That was way too quick
Right, 10 points ?
This is way too delicious
This is awesome
How about starting a food-truck business with this ?
Sound good
Seriously, people on a lunch break would love this
I'm not kidding
I'm telling you this is superb
Put some salt on it
Yes, salt enhances the flavor
I would give it an "Angel" mark as the score
I wouldn't disagree
Shouldn't we consider marketing this ?
I bet we can
As a "Gaki No Tsukai" product
Let's do this
I'm telling you right now, in about a month or so,
when you're out and about shooting some show,
you'll find Hamada selling this out of a food-truck
You mean, Hamada-san will personally be running the business ?
He's running the business
Well, he ain't frugal for nothing
Are you saying he's a cheapskate ?
Hamada's 2nd Dish:Bread in Corn Soup Tempura
Hamada's second recipe receives an unprecedented "Angel" mark
Tempura by Matsumoto
Last up is Matsumoto
What is his ultimate recipe ?
First up is this
Pizza
Ingredient
Why not fry this whole thing ?
Fry the whole pie ?
May I say this is "An Assassin from Napoli, Italy" ?
Duly noted
Well, I wasn't expecting any response other than that
I would have done the same
Forget "An Assassin from Napoli"
And !
I'm fully aware of the risk, but...
What ?
Ingredient
Gari Gari Kun Popsicle
Gari Gari kun (a Popsicle)
Well...
I could see fried ice cream but...
I know, this is more like a Popsicle
Matsumoto's 1st Dish
Pizza Tempura
His first ingredient, pizza,
requires covering the whole pie in batter
I need to accept more challenges in life
Looks like a giant rice cracker
Matsumoto's 2nd Dish
Gari Gari kun Tempura
Second is the Gari Gari kun ice pop
I don't know what to say...
Since I saw that your sweet-themed ingredients didn't do well
Like the Frisk and Jelly-Beans
Wouldn't this just melt ?
Yes, it does
I thought so
You need to fry this with care
Well then !
Before we get to try these dishes
And like I've always done in the past...
Again ?
I have one more ingredient
Here it is
What the hell is this ?
Bee Larvae
Ingredient
Bee Hive
They're in a honeycomb
I see they're all in there
They're in the Larvae stage
I thought I'd fry this up
This is an expensive ingredient, isn't it ?
I believe so
Let me say this will be the world premier
of a residence getting fried
You're right
I suppose the honeycomb is their residence
Right, their house will be fried
After covering it in batter,
Matsumoto's 3rd Dish
Bee Hive Tempura
the chef fries the whole honeycomb
They're about to enter unchartered flavor territory
Matsumoto's 1st Dish: Pizza Tempura
Here's Matsumoto's Pizza Tempura
How is it ?
It looks delicious
Matsumoto's 1st Dish
Pizza Tempura
I've seen this kind of dish before
Can I say that an Italian would never think to do this ?
Let me just slice right into it
I don't know what to call this tool though
It really does look good
I'm into the crunchy sound
The pizza got crunchier from being fried
It's been crunched !
It's the crunchiest !!
I'd call this the "Anarchy in Crunch"
And don't forget "The Assassin from Napoli"
"Ah here comes the Assassin from Napoli"
That's what comedian Hikomaro would say about this
Itadakimasu
The crumbs are looking...
Delicious !
Good
This is fantastic
But this was...
I was expecting this to be good...
Don't get me wrong, this is great but
it was almost a given that fried pizza would be good
Well, I've always thought pizza needed more crunch
Now, you're just bullshitting
You're being "teacher's pet"
I'm serious though
Matsumoto's 1st Dish: Pizza Tempura
The crunchiness of pizza helps score a perfect 10
Matsumoto's 2nd Dish: Gari Gari kun Tempura
Matsumoto's second ingredient is the Popsicle
How does it taste ?
I believe this is a home-run
I don't know...
It's a result of thinking "outside of box"
Matsumoto's 2nd Dish
Gari Gari kun Tempura
As I said before, frying ice cream makes sense but...
Remember there's no loser here
That's cool
I recommend this as a dessert
Itadakimasu
What is this ?
This isn't so bad ?
No
Well, the ice Popsicle is OK but...
This one definitely missed the target
No, listen
We can't be fooled with this
Listen
This is OK once I take off the breading
Huh ?
Then you're just eating the "Gari Gari kun"
Matsumoto's 2nd Dish: Gari Gari kun Tempura
Gari Gari kun is better left alone and receives one point
The last item is fried honeycomb
Matsumoto's 3rd Dish: Bee Hive Tempura
How does it taste ?
Bon Appétit
Matsumoto's 3rd Dish
Honeycomb Tempura
Here it is
See ?
What do you think of this...
Is it a dish for royalty ?
You're slicing that, too ?
I really don't want this
This looks like Buddha's head
You're right
Is that soft ?
You saw something ?
Incredible
What's wrong with you guys ?
This is so edible
I can't do it
Rumor has it that once you try bee larvae, you'll be hooked
I heard they're sweet beyond belief
Let's do rock-paper-scissors, and the loser eats it
Matsumoto's 3rd Dish
Honeycomb Tempura
Why do we have to eat this ?
I don't wanna lose this one
I'm spared !
Hamada-san, I always knew that you had the balls to try this
Wait a minute
This piece should do
That is one terrifying looking food
Help me hold him down
Eat one like this ?
Good luck
That's a cute little mouth
Open your mouth, Damn it !
Hamada Sensei, please
I seriously don't wanna do this !
Why do you gotta be like @#%$ ?!
Bite into it like a man
Open wide
Try it, try it
Anybody want to try this ?
Anyone ?
Well, nobody seems to be really interested...
"Wait, wait for me !"
That voice !
That's a really familiar voice !
Heipo
Could that be... ?
That's Heipo-san
Don't be upset, Heipo !
We didn't forget about you !
You didn't need to shout out like that
Oh boy, that's really...
a larvae...
Yep, we've got Heipo-san here
Itadakimasu
Don't spit it out
Give me a sec
Who are you talking to ?
What's going on ?
What's he doing ?
What's with him ?
He's molting !
Stop Lion Dancing !
Why don't you just try a single one ?
OK, I'll just eat one
Make sure you taste it
Delicious !!
Tasty !
I'm not kidding, it's really good !
This is awesome !
You're kidding
You should try this, it's really good
Did you just reboot your brain or something ?
Wow, this is really good !