This is where we film Gakitsuka
It's a spring day and there wasn't a man who is usually in a dressing room like everyone else.
Tajima the manager came into the room.
Hamada san.
Matsumoto san asked me to call everyone immediately.
What do you mean?
We'll be having a talk show here today.
Why?
Matsumoto san said he will explain. So right away.
Where is he?
Um, I'm not sure...
How can we get there when you're not sure?
Please, I beg you.
I don't understand...
共同11
This way, please.
We should go back.
Is that him?
They set up something.
-You are late. -Huh?
You are late.
It's not like we're late.
Huh?
We came here soon enough.
We were gonna have a talk show but you suddenly called us.
I've been thinking about doing some challenge thing.
However, I think a challenge with the same degree of risk as before will not satisfy viewers, especially housewives.
Do you really have to do that?
I've been listening to you and I had enough of your bullshit!
What are you doing?
You don't have a sense of urgency!　A sense of urgency!
Hey,  bring that thing!
Yanaoka!
Why are you yelling?
What was brought is a doll looks just like Matsumoto.
What is he showing us?
I'm showing you what I'm going to do.
Complain afterwards.
Crossbow.
Crossbow?
I'm going to use a crossbow.
What Matsumoto is going to do is the following:
He will stand in front of 12 bolts, and push the button himself.
And at the same time he will dodge all the incoming bolts immediately.
You can't do this.
This is serious.
Well, let's see how lethal this weapon is.
In 5 seconds,
Scary!
I'm ....
It completely pierced the neck.
I will challenge this.
No, don't do it.
If something happened to you.
Why shouldn't I? Tell me 8 reasons, each of you.
8 reasons?
Why shouldn't I?
Why not?
Because you probably will loose your life.
Who gives you a guarantee that someone's not aiming a crossbow at you when you wake up in the morning!?
Tajima, what does the company think about this?
Is this okay?
Osaki is okay with this.
The boss said yes.
Just because he said yes...
When I clap, move to the side.
That's different.
You're too slow.
Clap.
Not really different.
What's that?
I have this on my arms.
You were weighing youself?
You should have mentioned that.
Clap again, please.
You didn't move your legs.
Only upper body.
Yet I'm a person who will show real power when the time comes...
as you've seen before.
Hey, why don't we do a different thing that can involve everyone here?
"A different thing that can involve everyone here"
Enough of whining!
What did he just say?
I don't know.
Worthless.
Asshole!
We're saying because we're thinking about you.
But if you insist.
We're just worried.
If you really think about me, you should watch over what I do, shouldn't you?
Prepare for it.
So that I can start.
The decision finally has been made.
While 12 sharp bolts are being set,
Matsumoto is trying hard to focus.
Matsumoto consitently simulates his evasion tactics.
What is his goal? What is his message?
Seeing his serious look, we have to do nothing but agree to participate.
Does he really overcome this challenge that threatens his life?
He'll do it.
Well then, I'll do it.
Watch me.
Of course.
It's happening.
It's time.
Once he push the button, all the bolts will be released towards Matsumoto.
"To little kids in front of TV: This is very dangerous. Do not try this at home."
I can't do this.
Huh?
I can't.
Why not?
Look down there.
Oh...
We put the warning just in case.
We do this because little kids may try this.
I think chances are low but we can't say it won't happen.
I... um...
Whatever happens, I absolutely don't want little kids to get hurt.
I don't want little kids to get hurt!
Well said, man.
You're the man, Matsumoto san.
He's the man!
We should celebrate!
Idiot!