Today, for all you viewers at home...
I have some sad news to deliver.
A part of our Gaki no Tsukai team,
ever since the second episode...
Yamazaki has decided that he will be
leaving the show, as of today.
- Well, he said this was "THE END".
- Ah, I see.
Well, let's bring the honored guess out.
I would like to introduce Housei Yamazaki.
Today is your last day, correct?
- Right. This is the end for me.
But, there's a really gloomy atmosphere.
- That's true, because what ever you did, there was always a joking air about it.
In actuality, something like this has a
sad part to it as well.
Like when we did the "5 Rangers" skits, you always had to be the Yellow Ranger.
- Hmm? This was his choice.
- It was his choice, I guess.
But neither Endo nor myself have heard any
reasoning behind you leaving.
Like, what kinds of things
made you decide to leave.
- I don't understand the reasoning behind it either.
- Well, I managed to get a girlfriend.
I just listened to her opinions some...
She watches the show all the time.
We're pretty deep in love.
- But still, you wouldn't have
to leave, would you?
- When you watch the way
I appear on shows...
I'm always a talk show guest or something.
I told that to the producers.
"I'd like to appear on a few
other shows", I said.
He basically said, "That
might be impossible."
"Might be impossible?"
Why would he say "impossible"
so plainly, Yama-chan?
- At that time, he probably wasn't thinking
about the best way to put it.
- Maybe you should have said
you weren't leaving...
- Right. Maybe if he'd added
"I'm okay here, but..."
"No, it's okay. You can
do all sorts of shows."
Then you could go all sorts of places.
- Because the "Yamazaki flower"
hasn't stopped growing.
Today, our own Hosei Yamazaki
has chosen some
famous clips from his time on Gaki no Tsukai.
It seems he's chosen five of them.
- Best Five.
Please watch the clips which Yamazaki's chosen.
Housei Yamazaki. Age: 33 years old.
Ever since the second episode of Gaki No Tsukai, he's appeared as a regular on the show.
Over his 11 years on the show, he's made several memorable clips.
This March, he graduates from Gaki No Tsukai.
He'll leave several bright marks on Gaki's history.
Number 5:
Yamazaki attempts to be a "Super Yogore" entertainer
After reaching the status of a shock entertainer, Yamazaki looks to improve to "Super Yogore" rank.
Yamazaki and a dresser that we took to a love hotel, bathe and share a moving love story.
Really? You're collecting a lot of water here.!
Wow. You're butt's exposed.
That's dangerous!
Cum!
Number 4:
Yamazaki and Jimmy Onishi's Feud
What the hell is wrong with you?!
While they were both employed by the Yoshimoto talent agency, Yamazaki and Jimmy did nothing but fight.
They wild fighting soon turned into a dogfight.
This is yours, Yamazaki?
- Yeah.  - It's nice.
This is nothing to get excited about.
- Be quiet.
*Note: This car is really Yamazaki's*
Why did you kick your own car?!
Why'd you kick my car?
- Don't get all defensive about something like this.
A natural idiot like you deserves crap like this.
- You're the "Natural Idiot" around here.
*Yamazaki and Jimmy call each other natural idiots*
What the hell are you doing?
- I was about to ask you the same thing, asshole.
Number 3:
"Yamazaki flirted with a scary man's girl" prank
Eh! Say something asshole.
Yamazaki finds himself in trouble with the older brother of a girl writer Takasou introduced him to.
This prank will go down in Gaki No Tsukai history.
It should be fine.  - He sounds really scary.
He's here.
Who is it?
- Open up.
*Yamazaki tries to escape through the kitchen window*
*Somehow, Takasou opens the door*
I'm the wrong guy.
- What the hell?! Which of you is Yamazaki?  -Him!
I'm sorry. So sorry.
- What the hell is wrong with you?!
I'm different. I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
*Yamazaki is quaking in fear*
Sorry. Sorry.
- Come on outside. I'll be waiting for you.
Sorry.
- You aren't getting out of it.  - Sorry.
- Good afternoon!
I was scared for my life!
Number 2:
Late-night Piano Concert in the Abandoned School
After being found guilty in a small-scale trial, the penalty Yamazaki got his guilty verdict...
was to give a piano concert in a dark, abandoned school.
Hold on... Komu!!! (One of the directors)
*He suddenly calls the directors name*
Next up is... a song by Beethoven.
* A loitering old man appears *
* A sound shakes the glass in: 3 *
* A sound shakes the glass in: 2 *
* A sound shakes the glass in: 1 *
* The doorknob is covered in lotion *
* There's a whoopee cushion on the seat *
"Hoshi ni Negai wo" (When you wish upon a star) by Leigh Harline
*From underneath the piano appears a mountain hag*
*The loitering old man`s locked the door!*
Number 1:
Yamazaki vs Moriman: Blazing Battle
Yamazaki and Moriman put their pride on the line in a battle of the sexes in this signature series.
For more than 1000 guests who gathered in Korakuen Hall, they battles in a moving fashion.
Out of all of them, this battle became a struggle:
It's got to be this one: Hot, hot ankake battle!
For Gaki No Tsukai's sake, you would go naked or in disguise as lots of different things.
You came to perform for us, and all for Gaki's sake.
Surely you have treasured memories of your youth here on Gaki No Tsukai.
Even though you leave us today, you've given us numerous moving moments that will remain in our hearts.
Goodbye...
and thank you for the memories.
- Looking at all those moments...
Now it's starting to feel like you're leaving.
... Because of the older clips of you were funny.
The show's producer, Mr. Suga, would like to give a parting message to you.
Yama-chan, thank you for these 12 years.
In 12 years, a lot of things can happen.
Things like aiming to be better than Downtown...
Back in Nihon TV's "Golden Days", I was choking on a pin.
I talked on and on about lots of different things, and was a pain in the neck for lots of people.
From now on at Nihon TV, my new producer and I will work as hard as we can. Thank you.
- And now we'll have a few last words from Yamazaki's show business juniors, Cocorico.
- Mr. Housei, thanks for all your hard work.
Before we came, it was you and Downtown here.
You make it comfortable by being talkative with us.
For that, we'd like to thank you.
Even places outside of here...
- Right. There's no reason that we can't meet up.
We'd just like to say "Thanks for your hard work".
- Well, we can go last.
- I was actually pretty happy to hear the news.
It was the person's decision to leave.
In order to move himself on to bigger things, he decided that it was time to leave Gaki No Tsukai.
This is sad, but I think you'll do well after this.
- At least it didn't come from the company.
It's different than being fired or told to leave.
- As for Yoshimoto ( their talent agency), we'll keep bringing in more and more new talent.
- Because we've got that kind of appeal.
- That's right.
- Maybe, if you hadn't said you were leaving...
I would have thought about leaving.
- Ah. You thought about it.
Well, Yamazaki... thank you.
Thanks for your hard work.
Lastly, we'll have a message from Yamazaki...
To all your viewers at home.
- Lastly, a message from Yamazaki to the viewers watching from home.
- Getting flowers on a night like this...
Who granted my biggest wish?
Those who've cheered for me over my 12 years on Gaki No Tsukai Ya Arahende...
From now on, even though I'm saying goodbye to Gaki No Tsukai...
I just want to appear on some different shows.
- Do your best. Thanks for your work.
- Well, if you think about it...
A five-person group is hard to work with.
- For just doing everyday stuff, right?
- And it's easy to split up.
- And easy to work as a team.
I think out of the viewers, there's about 7 or 8 people that are sad, but...
But this is something that couldn't be helped.
No matter what we said, he still would be leaving.
- Yama-chan...!
ain't leaving Gaki No Tsukai!
Hey! All you young ones!
Did I surprise you?!
This is something I asked Downtown and Cocorico to do.
I ain't leaving Gaki No Tsukai!
Today was just a big prank!
I'm not leaving! Not leaving! Not leaving!!
*Livin' La Vida Loca*
("Yama-chan Isn't Leaving" version)
Yama-chan isn't leavin'!
*TORA TORA TORA*
("Yama-chan Isn't Leaving" version)
YamaYamaYama Yama-chan isn't leavin'!
YamaYamaYama Not leavin'!
- We've met our part of the deal and did the prank.
Pranks have a part that surprises people.
I really wonder if this surprised anyone.
It's got an "unfortunate" feeling to it all.
It's a little more "social" than you'd think.
- It didn't really turn out to be a prank at all.
Yama-chan will always be...
completely revolting!