Subbed by funkygibbo
Genius Music Producer Yamazaki's 5th attempt at raiding the music industry!!
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Yamasaki Hosei
Hamada Masatoshi
Endo Shozo
Tanaka Naoki
So this is our fifth one?
Yeah it is
Our Fifth one huh
Yeah its the fifth
An explosion in the middle of the town
It looks like i no longer have a place to return to
These are some of the other songs that were written by the genius music producer Yamazaki Hosei
for when you cant reach our hand
Please try and feel this flower of love
we'll change the earth
In the 8 years since this series has started he has produced 13 songs
its been a while but the Genius actor Yamazaki is now going for his 5th attempt
his attempt at raiding the music industry!!
this time all the members were given different songs to sing
we've been looking forward to this havn't we?
i guess...
which song did you think was the best to produce?
if i'm being honest the first song sung by endo because he nailed it on the first attempt
seriously?
I nailed it because he thought my rehearsal and rock were both pretty good
you must have done a pretty good job
I wanted him to do it fairly quick so that his voice didn't get ruined
he met the image that i had perfectly
Yours?
Mine
I think we should watch Endo's first
I dont mind whos we start with
yeah we should
we should watch Endo's first shouldn't we?
I wanted to slap you so hard right then
a really hard slap at that
The members get to read the song lyrics beforehand
Heres the lyrics of the song that you have to sing
Okay, erm
Shouldnt this be "sung by a woman"? so do i...
you wont sing it like that
i dont sing it like that?
shouldn't i sing it in a womans voice so i can express the feelings
you wont sing it like that
seriously, you wont sing it like that
so i dont sing in a womans voice?
No
you'll start off like this
If you love me with all of your heart then i'll love you to my hearts content
Stop!
which bit was wrong?
its already perfect!
Its perfect?
Yes
But i havn't even finished singing the song yet
Its will be fine
now go and get changed
Eh?
go and get changed
but i havn't even finished rehearsing all of the song yet
Downtown no Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
Music producer Yamasaki's raid on the music industry!
Heres the Rock tune written by Yamasaki and is being performed by Endo
Eh?
Its me
Thats you?
Discipline 2012
Why the hell are you wearing that?
The producer chose it not me
I had the bad habit of starting to run but not being able to stop
when i seen you on your bike all night again
Your sweat, Your positive vibrations and Your lips
all make my hips, my breath and my heart go numb
Please love me with all your heart just this once
i'll do whatever you like if you do love me
From when i was a child i dreamed that i'd become somebody's plaything
What the hell are you saying?
This isn't a song about me
Whats with these weird lyrics?
This is how the girl feels
Please love me with all of your heart Tetla Pot
You and me will Dance all night without any limits
From when i was a child i dreamed that i'd become somebody's plaything
What the hell are you saying?
It was their dream from when they were a kid
from when they were a kid
To be loved by Tetla Pot
sure was a long dance for the end
your face looks a bit rough there
So thats how it is
Thank you very much!
that was done on the first attempt
just one attempt
thats impressive!
theres some weird lyrics did you have a clue what it was about?
not really, i just knew it was basically a girls song
Thats right, heres the lyrics
"from when i was child i only wanted to be somebody's plaything"
it might be considered normal for a man to say something like this
but a bit strange if it came from a woman
if you take a look at the title that i chose, it is Discipline 2012
My image of Endo singing this song was that he was being disciplined
so Endo was being disciplined by singing this song?
So the singing was me being disciplined?
it was, Endo was being disciplined by singing a woman's song
wait a second
So was Endo supposed to be a man or a woman?
he was a man
wait a sec, seriously?
yes
I understand it now
i had no idea because you never told me,  i was trying to sing it with a more womanly feel
You were being disciplined by being made to sing dressed as a girl
so being dressed as a girl was the discipline?
what did the bit about tetla pot mean?
well when i first wrote the lyrics here they were different.
this bit actually read " when i first seen you, you rode all night"
the bike was actually me
so you changed the original?
why did you change it?
i thought the lyrics would of been too adult rated
surely whilst you were writing the lyrics
thats one of many things you should of thought about
Endo did a great job on his song
thank you very much
i think theres a lot of places in which you'll think of that song
no need to say it more then once
then lets move on to the next song
eh?
Endo did a good job
Thank you very much
Moving onto our 2nd song is Hamada and Tanachi
so thats how you decided to do it?
thats right
yes its Hamada and me, the two of us
Hamada and tanaka is a combination i'd of never imagined
thats true, they are like water and oil
so this time the 2 us are going to be singing together aren't we?
You're wrong
Are you listening?
Tanaka is obviously best suited to be the guitarist
obviously
So i'm obviously the guitarist?
Yes
And the vocals go to Hamada
Eh?
So we aren't both singing?
No. only you
I dont want to...
You stop playing around!
its the producers decision
stop with the violence
This will be your guitar
I dont believe this
I dont believe this...
I seriously thought tanaka would have to sing half of the song
besides the viewers wont want to listen to lyrics like this anyway
i think you're right about that
"wont want to listen to this"
Everybody will be saying it, everybody will
all be saying that they dont want to listen to it
please stop saying that
that comes from the deaths of hell
i'll break through
from here you get ready
this is your big scene
my big scene?
you start playing
a guitar solo?
I knew you two could do it
I'm not sure if i got some of the timing right
No, no, no it was fine
so it was alright?
Now go and get changed
eh?
go and get changed
hes got to be kidding
that was quick
Hamada doing the singing and Tanaka on the guitar its time to watch Producer Yamasaki's Greatest Rock Unit
The red sun that is burning my skin
the black ground that looks like it comes from the depths of hell
i'll break through
i''ll make you tremble like a puppy caught in the midst of a storm
i'll put you wounded on a cross with only my blade made of glass
i'll Aim for his heart and Lock in down
i seriously wouldnt want to listen to this
in your dreams i'll make you laugh at my stories whilst i fight against my wicked opponents
i'll put you wounded on a cross with only my blade made of glass
i'll Aim for his heart and Lock in down Hi!!!!
who are you supposed to be?
i didn't understand a single bit of that song
yeah it was a little strange
tanaka did a little singing aswell didnt he?
thats right
a little
I thought they should both sing during the guitar solo
but we thought we'd be singing half the song each
thats what we thought initially
i never wanted you two to sing half each
i didn't have a clue what i was hearing
it just sounded like he was singing a bunch of katakana
what did you just say Endo?
a lot of katakana
his ears are useless
heres that bunch of katakana
but there isn't that much is there?
well theres this DaDa DiDi Da-Da
but that isnt Katakana
its English
its written in English
its written in English but
most people can convert it into katakana
well most people but Endo
Thanks...
After the thickness of Hamada's vocals
when he was singing you could feel his Strong aura
in front of other men
You're overdoing it
yeah
so thats what vocal thickess is
well i dont think anybody at home had seen something quite like that before
me niether
we should move onto the 3rd song
which is sung by Matsumoto
we've heard both of your songs now but i think mine could have most likely
surpassed both of them
oh really?
you feel that way?
i think so
i think his singings matured a lot from last time
lets watch it
Okay
Now lets enjoy listening to Matsumoto's song
Erm... how do you feel?
I'll do it this as many times as it takes
ah thank you!
but if i cant put my heart into this
or if i fail to remember any of the lyrics
no, you'll be fine
or something like that...
you and me have been working closely for 25 years
you should try and sum it all up...
you mean my feelings towards you?
yes
it think it would cause a big problem if those feelings came out
no, no
but thats why...
everybody watching would be shocked at what came out
it wont be like that
and thats when i turned around and saw you
and then from here your main part starts
to start you should let out whatever emotions you are feeling
just let out whatever comes to mind
just like that!
yes, yes, yes. not so cold, not that cold
thats pretty good
that was seriously cold
it wasnt cold, it was alright
didn't you say i could do whatever i felt after the bit with the wo, wo, yeah, yeah?
i did
then dont go saying things like "its alright, its alright, not that cold"
it makes me think that you dont like it
it makes me think " oh hes calling it bad"
not at alll
Thank you
1,2,3,4 and then Thank you
just like that!
as you say it you should be looking directly at the cameraman
and who am i saying this to exactly?
that would be your wife
this just seems unnecessary, this makes it too embarrassing you fool
Matsumoto singing a ballad for the one that he loves
this has the same feel to it as last time
same smoke affect as before
i didn't expect the set to be so similar to last times
this looks so embarassing
this was so awward
i bet it was
as i wandered around the middle of the town, i was walking, walking alone
as i walked in the darkness only wanting some light, i was walking, walking alone
and then, just as i  could no longer withstand this constant sense of loneliness
i turned around and saw you
Thank You for telling me just how you felt
but just seeing your smile was enough for me
Thank you
I'm glad i chose that song for him
was the final thank you on the lyrics sheet?
no that was Ad Lib wasn't it?
dont be so stupid
i seriously didnt want to do that bit
i remember thinking "I'm going to retire from the show"
retiring from the show?
it doesn't look like that long a song
whats the purpose of this bit?
these are just the words that i sang
it makes the song more fun
i just told him to sing "whatever he feels like"
you liar
for that part?
i told him to do whatever he feels like and then suddenly "ieieie" came out
that must of been the big problem he was talking about
lets move on, this is too embarassing
this was a song that not many people have seen before i'm sure
next up is our final song which has all of us singing together
everybody singing together, are you sure it will be alright?
i'm sure that this time we'll make a song that nobody will want to listen to
so far all the songs with all of us singing
no matter how many times i hear it i dont want to listen to it
Anyway, please get ready to start
we'll start with your standing positions
on this mic will be Matsumoto and Hamada
on this one will be me and Tanaka
Endo, you'll be on the drums
I'll be on the drums?
can you even play the drums?
not at all
yes you can
i can?
i'll be playing the drums?
yes
it will be impressive if he can drum and sing at the same time
we'll sing together until after Verse A
which part is that? i dont get it
sing until  "connected to our chewing gum"
and then Matsumoto
you sing it by yourself!?
yes
why does he sing his own name?
well it makes sense that in our song we say our own names
but they might think i am singing about Matsumoto Iyo-Chan
it just seems pointless
dont call it pointless!
this here is important
Tanaka, you'll be chewing on this throughout the song
you'll be chewing on this
and then after the shout at the end you'll blow a bubble
after the shout?
yes, you'll blow a bubble
another amusing part for Tanaka, you should just go and form a solo band
i'd like to see that
we are all connected to our chewing gum
he messed up again
it'll be impossible for us to finish at this rate
what the hell are you doing?
everytime you've messed up a little bit
what the hell?
it wasn't really that funny
i didn't think it was
Orange Cocorico Lemon Yamasa...
you messed up again
can you explain this bit to me?
we cant tell who should sing which part
who is supposed to sing this part?
who should sing this column?
Downtown should sing "Downtown Orange"
and then Cocorico sings until Lemon
and then i sing the next part
Downtown Orange
Cocorico
Lemon Yamasaki Strawberry
What the hell does this even mean?
we don't have a clue do we?
i don't understand any of it
we are all connected to our chewing gum
everybodys acting a bit maliciously towards my wig
everybodys looks like a mushroom
i think its more like they are acting maliciously to your existence
Transformed into The Beatles, heres the Gaki no Tsukai Band
we all feel connected to our gum
five vibrant colours of chewing gum
Matsumoto
Hamada
Yamasaki
Cocorico
Tanaka
Endo
they aren't meant for kids, they have an adults flavour
they are five little bulges of fun
Downtown Orange
Cocorico
Lemon
Yamasaki Strawberry
as we all take off laughing loudly
trying to see how large the bubbles can go
that was a good shout wasn't it?
harder then it looks isnt it?
it didn't look that bad
you reallly enjoyed that didn't you?
thats a long reaction
are you having fun?
my stomach hurts!
you enjoyed watching that back
yes i did
that was pretty good wasn't it?
you decided to call it Gaki no Tskuai ya Arahende?
thats right
before this we had an amazing song that went "ah Matsumoto-san"
it was this one wasn't it?
i remember it
that was 6 years ago
that song was actually called Gaki no Tsukai but in English
so thats what it means
and this time i decided to do the same thing but keep it in Japanese
you put a lot of thought into it didn't you?
yes
you just dropped the history of our songs
and now you cant pick it up
its not as if you need to use it anymore
thats true
so far i have produced 17 songs
so everybody please support them
but its not like our vocals were that good...
so please support us by searching this and watching all the songs
is there anything else we have to do?
no, we can go
everybody worked hard