Matsumoto-san, what are we doing today?
To be honest, I know almost nothing about today's theme
Except the fact that Endo is on fire
-He's on fire?
-Yes, Endo is on fire
So we are sitting here because Endo is on fire?
He's even having an undercut hairstyle now
That's all I know
Tanaka
Yes
Is Endo on fire?
Yes, he is completely on fire
What are we supposed to do?
So for today, there's this VTR that we really want to show you all again
Oh, I see
Please take a look
Endo Shozo, 49 years old
The gag that he created in his 29 years of career
Ho-ho-hoi
It has been used in the CM of various large corporations
The nationally known gag that can be seen on TV everyday
No it's not
The gag that has been loved for over 20 years, Ho-ho-hoi
However, it was actually a repetition of success and failure
This is a true story of the trajectory between Endo and Ho-ho-hoi
Ah, I see where this is going
The birth of Ho-ho-hoi
Wow, it's Lytton Commission
He was so fast back then
-His Ho-ho-hoi is so fast
-Yeah, he was young
Oh, it's Korakuen Hall
The glory he deserves
-Ah, the one about Yama-chan
-Yes
It's Shin-oni
The collapse of confidence
Get everything back!
The pride of Ho-ho-hoi
Put everything in!
The endless love towards Ho-ho-hoi
Project Ho-ho-hoi
What the heck is he saying?
What the heck is this?
I thought maybe you guys are looking down upon Endo's national gag Ho-ho-hoi
Of course we are looking down upon it
What are you talking about?
How is it nationally known?
Yeah, seriously
If that is the case, then you guys are wrong
So today, we want to show you guys how amazing is Endo's national gag Ho-ho-hoi
Eh, so that is today's theme?
Yes
That's unbelievable
So let's welcome today's protagonist
Endo-san, please come in!
The face when he comes in is important
What kind of face will it be?
This is actually the main point
Ah, so that's the face
The face of Mori-san
Yeah, I see
Subbed by Appieopie, more episodes at
www.laughseejapan.com/user/18797
Please excuse me for this
Did you hear what we said before you came in?
Yes, I heard it
-I was being completely embarrassed
-No, no, no
We didn't embarrass you
We're just being honest
That's just how it is
No, no, no way
-It was indeed really popular right?
-Yes, of course
Although it's strange to say this myself
In fact, many kids even took video of themselves doing Ho-ho-hoi right?
Yeah, that's true
-Really?
-Yes
So is there a VTR of that?
Is there a VTR of that today?
Well, not for today
Come on, you need to prepare that
-Ho-ho-hoi is also very popular on SNS
-No way
So how was it created?
-Let's watch the story of it once again
-Seriously?
-Let's watch it
-That's so aggressive
-In 1971
-Starting from here?
Endo Shozo was born in Osaka Toyonaka-shi
This little boy's dream was to become a professional baseball player
Yeah
He didn't even thought
about becoming a comedian
He even studied at a high school in Shikoku to learn about baseball
Yet, he couldn't make it to the National
High School Baseball Championship
The next thing that Endo aimed for, was Owarai
In 1991
He invited Tanaka, his friend since primary school
That's during the
Coming of Age Day
And went to Tokyo to become a comedian
They were employed by Yoshimoto, and Cocorico was established
In the next year, 1992
They debut during the stage show Battermon Club
I remember that
Although they participated in the stage show
They didn't get much work from TV shows
And they were struggling as one of the many juniors in Tokyo
Tanaka was so skinny
Nevertheless, an opportunity knocked at Endo's door
Hey
Oh my god!!
Endo
We have been chosen to do the introduction for Downtown no Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
Really!?
We have been chosen to do the introduction for Downtown no Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende?
Yes! We will be doing the introduction for that popular show Downtown no Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
No need to say it in full dude
It's like a dream to do the introduction for Downtown no Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
That's enough
No, it's not a dream
Let's do the introduction for Downtown no Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!!
Okay
This is where it all begins!
Everything starts here!!
Downtown was already one of the most famous comedian duo back then
Downtown was completely out of Endo's league
They are the admirable stars
They've been working really hard in the introduction, and then one day...
Matsumoto said something unexpected
By the way
For next week's theme
Matsumoto Hitoshi
Maybe Cocorico can join as well
Really?
Thank you so much!!
They received an exceptional promotion!
However, while they became the regular members
-I remember this
-Oh, really
I remember this
While Tanaka has successfully created many hilarious moments
Tanaka didn't
change at all
Contrarily, for Endo...
Ah, it's Shichi Henge
Is this Shichi Henge?
Yes, it's Shichi Henge
I'm Endo
I remember this
Oh, you remember this?
I'm Endo Shozo
I don't remember this
I don't remember this at all
That's the worst
That's truly the worst
I was so nervous at that time
Although he's giving a full effort, he still wasn't able to get a laugh
Tanaka was interesting at that time
Endo was struggling to find his own position
Yeah, he probably was
Hey, how are you doing?
Hello
Producer
What happened?
You look upset
He doesn't
look right
I'm unable to leave a legacy at all
He looks
much fatter
What am I lacking of, Suga-san?
Please tell me
Endo
Things will work out
Just try hard!!
He said things
will just work out
While Endo was still struggling, an opportunity knocked at Endo's door
It was a theme of the show, which triggered the creation of that gag
And that theme was...
To compete with their senior duo Lytton Commission for various physical games
And one of the games that they played was...
High mood battle
No problem, Cocorico can be very high
Come on, do it Endo
Ah, it's shaping up
And he's so fast
Yeah, it's fast
That's so fast
This is how it was born
-This is the first time?
-Yes, this is how it's born
It's getting so much laughters
Endo
Interesting!!
Oh, good for you
I was so happy about this
This was the first time that Endo felt successful as a comedian
Here starts Endo Shozo's strike back
Project Ho-ho-hoi
-That was where Ho-ho-hoi was born
-Yeah, I see
-This is a true story right?
-Yes
This is a true story
He was actually just forced to perform something at that time right?
Yes, it was improvised
-And Matsumoto-san said that it's interesting
-Yes, I did
So he thought this must be interesting and elaborated it further
Well, but I remember that
I had to say Endo is interesting because of how boring Lytton Commission was
I just thought I have to do something
In order to make the theme valid
But still, I was really happy that you said I'm interesting
Feeling like "he finally said that to me"
So this is how Ho-ho-hoi was born
And we will now watch how Endo transformed Ho-ho-hoi into a beautifully finished gag
-Eh, we need to watch that?
-Umm, that's enough
That's enough, that's seriously enough, Tanaka
This is embarrassing to him too
No, I want to watch this with you guys
-Seriously?
-Yes, together
During the High mood battle with Lytton Commission, Endo felt successful as a comedian for the first time
However, he was troubled about how to perform it in the show
Oh, Endo
It's him again
We'll be doing a battle like the one
with Lytton Commission for today's show
Please note that
A theme which is similar to that battle?
What could that be?
That theme was...
High mood
The best 10
A theme with juniors performing their high mood gags
The juniors who performed include
Gokuraku Tombo
Ameagari Kesshitai
Fujii Takashi
and a bunch of famous comedians
And the man who got the first place was...
Love ~Ho-ho-ho-ho-i~
Cocorico, Endo Shozo
Endo decided to put everything into this theme!
Seriously?
Do you know the rhythm of the Samba
So it's completed
at this time already
Do you know the rhythm of the Samba
Ho-ho-hoi
The movement was
incredible at that time
It's a lot more lively
That's really good
Yeah, it's completely different
He's moving a lot
He really is moving a lot
And it was
getting a laugh
Thank you very much
This is amazing
The studio was full of laughter
That was the first time
For the first time?
Endo's confidence has been reassured
This "High mood the best 10" theme has paved the way for Endo to start his strike back
Three months after "High mood the best 10"
During the theme "Yamazaki vs Moriman in Korakuen hall"
Let's do this again Yama-chan
-No way
-Let's do Moriman battle again
Before the battle starts
Let's watch the "Endo Opera" by Endo Shozo
The audiences are screaming
-He's so popular
-That was amazing
They are screaming like "GYAAA"
Do you know the rhythm of Samba?
He's moving a lot
He's on fire
He's improvising a lot
Yes, he is
Furthermore, during the "Kouhaku High mood battle" at the end of the same year
Using the big Japanese drum as the background music
Endo has been the key performer with Ho-ho-hoi
What the heck is a key performer with Ho-ho-hoi
I was moving a lot,
it's like 22 years ago
Endo got a laugh from the audience again and again with Ho-ho-hoi
This is the moment when he grasped the Ho-ho-hoi dream
What the heck?
Furthermore, for his private life, he was married as well
Endo has gained everything,
both the status and reputation as a comedian
However, this was just the start of an unforeseen misery
Ah, yeah it is
Project Ho-ho-hoi
-We all know about this
-Yeah
We all know about this already
What makes us concerned is that
While the gag is beautifully finished
And everything seems to be smooth sailing
However, it then talked about Endo's misery at the end
Yeah, we all know what happened
A lot of things had happened
Everyone knows about this
What happened to Endo who was smooth sailing
No, no, no
Let's take a look
What the heck is this?
With the nationally known gag Ho-ho-hoi,
Endo has entered his peak period
I remember this clearly
I remember this
What happened?
What's happening?
Was he carried away?
There's nothing for me to be afraid of now!!
I can always get a laugh with Ho-ho-hoi
However, Endo didn't even notice that things were slowly but surely changing
I see
I'm going to do the Ho-ho-hoi that everyone likes
Let's get started
Ho-ho-hoi
Hoi-hore-beep-beep
Hoi-hore-tsu-te
His movement was
already so slow
Ho-ho-hoi wasn't able to get a laugh anymore
He then started
to use some items
Endo didn't want to accept the reality
And he started to use various Objet d'art to muddle through
Yes, he did
I missed you so much
It's not the same
gag anymore
He started to depend on other things
That's horrible!
That's just horrible
It didn't get a laugh
Excuse me
Endo-san
There's another work about Ho-ho-hoi
What do you think?
Ho-ho-hoi is enough
I can get along without Ho-ho-hoi anyway
He's being arrogant
Endo dumped Ho-ho-hoi
In addition, this even affected his private life
His wife, who has been with him for 5 years, left him too
Endo is going through his worst times, and yet, something even worse happened
That happened during the No-laughing Newspaper Agency
For the wedding press conference section
Let's welcome the bride who grabbed happiness
-Chiaki-san
-Yes
What is the key reason for you to choose your husband?
Because he is much more unique than my ex-husband
Can your husband do something interesting please?
Ho-ho-hoi
It was very shocking
The Ho-ho-hoi that Endo dumped was getting a laugh from the audience
He's depressed
Yes, he was
It was just an accident for that gag to get a laugh
It's awkward for me to get naked and do Ho-ho-hoi again anyway
I dumped that gag already
-He dumped it?
-Yes
Endo gave himself up, however...
The arise of a comedian has fired him up again
He's Shoji Tomoharu, an original character by Shinagawa Shoji
Endo was shocked by his performance during the High mood competition
There's a lot of Pa-pi-pu-pe-po
The horizontal Pa-pi-pu-pe-po
The vertical Pa-pi-pu-pe-po
This is good
Ah, this is really good
He's in a good mood
Thank you very much
I've been watching his performance back there
His movement and rhythm was very similar to what I did back in my younger days
Endo felt something similar when he witness Shoji's gag getting a laugh
This reminded him of the passion he once had in the old days
Endo decided to pick up Ho-ho-hoi once again
And an opportunity came to him again
That was during last year's Youth High School
When they met the superintendent Amami Yuki
Yeah, right
You're looking pretty relaxed there, Endo-kun
Yes?
You have this thing where you put on a silly voice, slap your cheeks, get naked, and do a little dance, right?
Do that here, right now
Hurry up! Get naked and do it!
Okay, here I go
Do you know the rhythm of the samba?
Let's get excited for the new year, everyone!
Ho-ho-hoi
It got a laugh!
It was shining more than ever before
Ho-ho-hoi and Endo have shown their capability
Did it get a laugh?
And gave a sign of their strike back
Even more...
(I want to get back that agility in Ho-ho-hoi)
Commit to results
Rizap
It was used in the CM of various large corporations
Ho-ho-hoi has once again become a nationally known gag
And Endo will continue to shine from now on
Project Ho-ho-hoi
-So we now all understand the history of Ho-ho-hoi
-That's more than enough
Let's watch Endo's nationally known gag again together
Let's welcome him, Endo-san!
He's so fat now
So, Endo-san
Please show us the nationally known gag, Ho-ho-hoi!
Do you know the rhythm of the samba?
Ho-ho-hoi
I'll continue working hard
OUCH!
-He sprained his leg
-I think this is for real
-Yeah, his leg is stiff
-What can I do for you?
Just look at it
Look over here
-Look at it
-It hurts
Ouch! It hurts!
This is for real right?
This is for real...HAHAHAA
Can you stand up?
-No, I can't
-He have to do it himself
It's not our fault at all
-What the heck, dude
-No way
What the heck is wrong with him?
Let's just leave!!
I have no idea what's going on here
What's wrong with you dude
You're wicked!
What's wrong with him?
Did you tear a ligament?
Not at all, not about the ligament
You've completely torn the Owarai ligament though
He just sprained his leg right?
Yes, you're right
No big deal
It was sprained all of a sudden
So he's leaving like that
He's the one who wanted to do it
And now he's leaving like that
He's even blaming us