The series that nobody asked for :
Murakami Shoji's Class
For the first episode, they became ninjas;
Followed by the Green Berets.
In episode 3, they became pirates.
What could await them next?...
It's hot today, huh?
Yes, very hot.
35 C!
Why the hell are we wearing this necktie in this heat?
What the hell is a pilot classroom?
I've never heard of a pilot classroom.
Being a pilot is completely different.
He's been wanting to do this for a while...
Really?
I really don't want to be here!
Then let's just not do it.
Let's just sleep on the bus.
Murakami used to be amazing when we joined Yoshimoto.
He was part of "NG-II".
It was "NG-II", right?
It was really popular.
The Kombii "Shoji-Niichan" used to be in it.
He was with Yuji-san.
Is that so?
Really?
He was with Yuji-san.
It was SUPER popular.
NG-II?
NG-II.
Maybe it would be better if we don't discuss this now.
Yeah, you're right.
When there was a comedy competition...
NG-II will deninitely win, is what everyone thought.
Right as we joined... For about 4 years...
We were opponents in the finals...
...We beat them.
Don't mention it to him!
Translations by : Drageat
It's so freaking hot!
It's so hot!
I want to go home!
Why is it a sandy beach again?
Where should we go?
There's something written here.
That sign looks really cheap.
"Pilot Classroom"
Do you think if we wait here, he will come?
Us waiting makes it seem like we want to be here...
He came.
What's that?
There he is.
Pilot instructor, Murakami Shoji finally appears.
He's looking really sharp!
He didn't have to go to this extent!
The stewardesses also look real.
Good morning!
What's up?
It's good to see you all.
What?
What did he say?
I said, "IT'S GOOD TO SEE YOU HERE."
Look at all those stripes on his arm.
Impressive.
We only have 3 or 4 stripes...
These stripes are all you can think of?!
These stripes are for...
Airplane...
Helicopter...
Fighter Jet...
Fixing a bicycle tire.
I have all of these licenses.
If you don't have all of these...
...You can't call yourself a first-rate pilot.
Although, we thought we would do this series monthly...
It's been a while, so our rhythm is off.
I'm sure it is hard for you all to get used to again.
It's not that hard.
What the hell are you saying now?!
Your have to make up for your fathers mistakes.
Your dad couldn't become a pilot.
I hear he works in a school cafeteria now.
So your fathers dream... is now your own!
For now... Let us all become pilots.
Is it that easy to become one?
Shouldn't you say, "Let's do our best to become pilots"?
"Let's all become pilots" sounds strange.
I mean, let's all-
I can see you flying!
What was that?
What was what?
It- It's like how you greet your classmates when you were in school.
So, if we see a plane we should do that?
A pilot must do that.
I'm sorry, of course.
That is one of the most important rules as a pilot...
Actually, it is a mission.
It's common sense!
Of course.
Sorry, but what does she have to do with anything?
Her?
We just arrived, coming from Pinumpin.
The sky is looking lovely today, huh?
I understand warika...
What?
Warika?
The sky looks good today, huh?
I understand, Murakami.
She can't say it properly.
I brought you all presents today.
Really? Thank you.
I got you...
A very heart-felt gift.
You got it from "Duty Free"?
Looks like clothes...
Yeah I could only-
Look, a plane!
Hey! That's some good quality metal!
I said they were made of good quality metal.
You're saying that to a Boeing?
It's common sense!
Here
Beef jerky.
It's open!
Excuse me...
Everyone got a present but me...
You get no present, because of your father!
This is from Hakone...
(A town, 1 hour away by train.)
It's time to begin-
Another plane!
Hey...
Hamada, you try.
Hurry! It's going away!
Hamada-kun!...
It's leaving!
It's gone...
What do you mean, "It's gone"?
I was caught by it's beauty.
Another one will come.
It's not a big deal.
First, a pilot must build up the courage to fly.
What is a pilot?
What did humans want to be in the past?
Tanaka...
What did they want to become?
They wanted to fly, like birds.
~People might have been birds in the past~
See? The singer says it all.
Whether or not we were birds...
Another Plane!
Tanaka!
Here's your chance!
Say something.
It's leaving, again!
Tanaka, you let it get away!
I'm sorry, was distracted by the size.
Don't you have any feeling to shout?
(He said "Narita".)
[Narita = Tokyo's International Airport]
Huh?
He made a pun, right?
I did that on purpose.
It's all planned comedy...
They call it, "Micro-Comedy".
Next, begins the practical training of being a pilot.
Let's go!
Bring that over here.
Bring that machine here.
This looks amazing.
What is that?
This is a prototype for a future plane.
This is a plane, and at the same time, it isn't.
It's about 70% finished...
...But it can fly.
In 3 years when this hits the markets...
Pilots and even civilians will be riding these.
Then why are we training to be pilots?
Remember, it's still 3 years away...
Shall we give it a whirl?
First, Shoji demonstrates for the pilots in training.
What will happen?
This is really easy.
It's probably not a good idea to use this in your house.
You have to ask someone nicely to help lift you up.
You have to be popular to use this thing.
I'm taking off.
That looks scary.
Let's just go home.
This is getting ridiculous.
That looks weird.
What is he doing?
how far is he going?
That machine looks really heavy.
He's about to fall down.
He's going really far.
That thing can't fly.
He looks depressed.
Looks tough...
Yeah, he looks tired.
I thinks it's about 40 years...
3 years...
Is not enough...
Matsumoto, would you give it a try?
Let's become birds.
Use this trigger to accelerate.
Don't press it too hard, or you'll fly away.
Give it a try now.
Slowly press it.
Good Luck!
Looks tough on the feet.
It's really heavy!
Looking good!
You'll see when he comes back...
He'll talk of how beautiful the sky is up there.
I bet he'll say it.
Matsumoto-kun, come back!
He's making a new face.
Matsumoto-kun!
How was it?
It was...
Beautiful...
The sky is beautiful...
Did he fly?
I didn't think it would be this much leg work.
Matsumoto-kun!
You don't like to fly?
That's not what I meant.
I'm sorry.
In this next practice...
...We'll be flying real airplanes.
What??
Real ones.
In the next training, they will learn how to maneuver in the sky.
Here they are.
These planes belong to "Air Doon".
AIR DOON!
Air Doon...
First up, Hamada-kun & Endo-kun.
Get over here.
Do you understand?
Yes.
You see those cones over there?
These are enemy planes.
Enemy planes?
Enemy planes.
These are the other pilots around you, not just cones.
Hamada-kun, go ahead.
Let's all become pilots! Let's all become pilots together!
Starting from here.
This thing tilts like crazy!
It's a plane! Of course it will tilt!
Find the center of gravity.
I see. That's what makes it difficult.
Climb up the ramp!
He didn't climb it properly...
Hamada! You didn't climb it properly!
He didn't use the small bar...
It's okay if your slow, just don't hit any cones.
Only 200 more times to go.
Don't fall until you finish 200 laps.
Captain, this part is really hard.
Of course it's not easy...
You're flying!
It's too hard...
Who said you could take a break?
Why did you stop?
I never told you to stop.
No good... Sorry.
There is a proper runway line that you need to be using.
You aren't flying properly on that line.
It's really hard, captain...
You said that you wanted this, instead of the paper exam.
You said this is what you wanted.
Matsumoto-kun!
That one.
Let's-
HEY!
Hamada-kun!...
You're hitting the cones!
Sorry!
You think this is just a bicycle, don't you?
No!
THEN FOLLOW THE RULES!
Follow the rules!
I'm sorry!
You really think this is just a bicylcle!
They're planes, you guys!
Sorry.
Are you taking this seriously?!
The sky feels amazing, doesn't it?
I think this thing is broken.
Let's all fly to China.
We'll stop at China.
Carefully!
Something might come popping out of these cones.
Captain!
Are you alright?
Are you hurt?
You need medical assistance.
There's blood coming out.
No. No. I'm fine.
It's not blood.
It wasn't blood.
So, what was it?
Fish oil...
Just fish oil...
You don't think I'm lying, do you?
Sorry. You're right.
You all did well...
...Much better than group 5...
...Group 6.
We're group 6?
You guys have much more talent than group 5.
So we're group 6?
Yes, you are.
Let's go take a break.
Let's take a water break.
I'm so thirsty...
Yeah, because it's so hot today.
Thank you, very much.
It's cold.
Is it good?
Chief...
...Captain...
...I would like some tea.
I'm so thirsty.
You should try sipping it from the ground.
I remember that day well...
...With that 40-year-old woman...
She had 2 kids.
You asked me, "Why don't you get married already?"
What the hell was up with that phone call?
You never call me!
To my surprise, it was you.
I found out the truth...
In a nearby snack bar,
That woman was sitting there...
She had 2 kids... She was 40 years old...
That's when you called and asked...
"Why don't you get married already?"
What do you mean get married?!
She sent me a text message saying that she liked you.
I called her and do you know what she said?
She said there was no way it would work out.
She called the night after...
...Apologizing for how drunk she was.
She said, "Erase my number, I was only drunk."
Did that really happen?
You made me look bad, you idiot!
The next course will teach how a pilot should deal with a hijacking on the plane.
Now, what should you do when someone is trying to hijack the plane?
This here, is the key to an airplane.
If a hijacker breaks into the cabin and steals the key...
...Then the plane will stop moving.
It's your job to make sure they don't steal the key.
When someone tries to hijack a plane, do they usually go for the key?
Does that really happen?
So, if a hijacker pulls the key out of the ignition.
-untranslated-
A hijacker might try to take the key, so let's practice stopping them.
If you're able to stop them today, I'll recommend you as a pilot.
I'll be the hijacker.
I'll do it.
Count to 10.
1...
2...
3...
4...
5...
6...
7...
8...
9...
10...
He's running really fast.
I didn't know you could run like that.
What a weird way to run.
Come get me!
(Let's go home...)
Come on!
Man, being a pilot was tough.
It was really tough.
What about the flying machines?
I still have the key!