"The Ladies of the Kyogoku Family"
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Thanks.
Enjoy your tea.
Hey, Master Tokunin.
Yes?
About how far is it
from here to Hakone?
Ah, it is about a mile that way.
Ah, I see.
Hurry! Hurry!
Thank you very much.
Thank you!
Are you ok?
Thank you very much.
Are you hurt?
No.
Thank you so much.
Not at all.
What happened?
- Mother!
- It's Mother!
This nice samurai helped
me when I fell just now.
Oh, is that right?
Thank you so much!
Mother!
- Mother!
- Are you alright?
Look closely at the
face of that samurai!
You're Mitani Bokuzen, are you not?
Have we met before?
I am the wife of the now deceased
Kyogoku Muneharu!  Oshizu!
His daughter! Oichi!
His second daughter! Omatsu!
The third daughter! Otaka!
My husband fell in
battle at Nippombashi...
...and you insulted his memory
two weeks on that TV show!
Have you truly forgotten?!
These things happen in life!
You!!!
How could you!!!
Are you a comedy troupe?
Avenge Father's death!
Give us...
...your life!!!
Fear not! I've cut your kimonos off,
but left your bodies unscratched!