Translations: Zurui
Laying Eggs
Sorry for intruding
Please enter
It's dirty huh?
No, it's not
Sorry for intruding
Please enter
Leave your slippers here
OK
It's a simple room, right?
Hmmm... umm... well..  yeah
I'm kind of nervous
Oh
How about some coffee or tea?
Oh, let me get it
No, you're a guest today
No, really
No, no, really
I'll do it
Ok, right?
Yes?
Let's make love
Yuu-chan
Ah.. um..
Bedding
Lay out the bedding
Let's make space
What are you doing in my room?!
Let me give birth
What?
Like you let me last Fall
What happened last Fall?
I don't know
Hey!
You're making it wet and dirty
Take all of this home with you
Hurry up
What the hell are you doing?!
Hey, just get out of here!
Let me give birth
Let me give birth today
Huh?
My stomach hurts!
It hurts!
I don't care, just get out!
You're being rude!
I'm not saying anything, just get out of
here, you're making everything dirty!
Let me hug you
No!
No
Give me a hug
What are you doing in someone's home
Let me cry like last time
When is the last time?
He's an idiot
I don't know
Hey, what are you touching?
Leave!
Where does she take off her clothes?
Huh?
Why do you keep treating me like this?
I'm just telling you to get out
Forgive me
Huh?
What the hell?
Forgive me
What's wrong with you?!
Forgive me like last time
When was last time?
I don't know
Just go, hurry up!
This is a mess
Your grammar is a mess
You're a mess
I said to clean up your mess and get out of here!
Let me die
If you want to die, die
Get out of here!
Let me die like 3 years ago
What about 3 years ago?
I don't know, just get out!