Subtitles: Zurui
Mask
[Masao-kun is in danger!]
[If he doesn't get help, he will get hurt!]
[Come here, hurry! Miracle Ace]
Ouch! Ouch! That hurts!
Cut it out!
What are you doing?
Oh, sorry
I'm really sorry
Sorry
That's enough
You broke it
I said I'm sorry, really
I'll call you later
You getting bullied again?
It always happens, what's the problem?
Do you know him?
No, I don't
What's wrong with you and those guys?
I don't know what is going on
You must be an easy target
Maybe, I don't know
What's their problem
You guys are both the blame
That's not true. I don't cause trouble!
You have to stick up for yourself
They look so strong
They don't look stronger, it's your mind
You have to think positive
What should I do?
I wonder if I should tell you...
Huh?
Loud voice
What voice?
What?
W... what were you going to tell me?
Well...
I have a song that will give you courage
Huh?
I have a song
You were going to give me a song of courage?
You will become brave
Oh. I will become brave?
Well, is it ok if I can remember it?
Yea
Ok, tell me
"Miracle Ace Anthem"
If I sing this song. I can be brave, right?
Try and remember it, ok?
Yes, I will try
It's long
Really?
- Yea
I'll try my best
"Mirakuru"
"Faito de"
"Chi yo kakero"
That's the first line
Sing it, sing it
Sing the first line?
- Yes, the first line
"Mirakuru"
"Faito de"
"Chi yo kakero"
"Mirakuru"
"Faito de"
"Nagisa no Rock & Roll"
Say it
"Mirakuru"
"Faito de"
"Nagisa no Rock &  Roll"
"You"
"Should drink sake!"
Add some words in there
Huh?
Add some words in the song
Add some words..
Like.. "Do it!" "Do it!"
"DO IT!"
"Mirakuru... faito de"
Hurry say it
"You"
"should drink sake"
"Do it!"
"DO IT!"
"Mirakuru"
I got it
How is it? This will be fine
Really?
- Yea
I'm still kind worried
Mister, let me borrow a weapon
I would feel safer
Is that so...
Here take this
Stop it!
It's ok
It's ok, hold this in your hand
Wait a minute!
This is good
Why??
It's ok and don't forget the song
This is poo!
You said it's poo
The song, sing the song
What do I do with this?
When the bullets come, sing the song and show them this. You will win!
Really?
Ok, bye
What he said...
What he said was true!
So that's Miracle Ace!
He still has a lot of secrets!
To be continued