http://zurui.blogspot.com
Subtitles: Zurui
Tomiyoshi-san
I'm happy! We haven't eaten sushi in a while
It's nothing special just the sushi-go-round
What's wrong?
- Look!
Is that a person?
What are you doing?
What?
It's not "ahh"
The washing machine hose... hey!
What?
I said what are you doing?!
What with the "ahh"
Mizuno-san!
Mizuno-san look at this
Yes.. huh?
See?
What is he doing?
What the hell is this?
What are you doing mister?
What?
Get out!
Shut up stupid! It's none of your business
It does matter, you're in my washing machine hose right?
Are you "Ai Sai go"?
*Ai Sai Go - Washing machine manufacturer
No I'm not "Ai Sai Go"
That's wrong
I'm wrong?
That doesn't matter, just get out of there!
You're blocking my door, get away!
Shut up stupid, why do I need to get out?
You're right outside his door!
I warned you!
You didn't warn anyone
I warned you earlier
Me? We didn't hear anything from you
I sent a messenger to let you know I would be here
Messenger?
He told you...
If he really came, I would have refused!
Hurry and get out!
Just call the police
Can you call the police?
Hey, don't fall asleep!
- Don't sleep!
We're calling the police!
Shut up, I'm not calling them
We're calling!
Shut up stupid
What's the problem?
Look at this guy
What is he doing?
Mister
What?
Why are you in there?
Police?
Yes, it's the police
Get out mister
What?
Can't you get out?
Of course I can get out
How did you get in there?
You're causing trouble for everyone
If it's hard for you to get out, I'll help you
It's kind of complicated
Is it complicated?
Yes it is
When I tried to get out, I got in
You tried to get out but you got in?
That must have been hard huh?
Yeah
- Yeah
Let's get out
You're only thinking about me getting out huh?
Right?
Yeah
You should have asked me why I'm in here to begin with
Yeah I guess that's true
It seems like you really don't care
Sorry mister
Please tell me why you're in there
Marriage is like prison
My wife...
came from a rich family
I see
I have such a small paycheck, but she uses every last penny
And...
she really likes the high end boutiques,
so she spends a lot of money
It's OK if she like expensive merchandise but...
she should take care of herself from the inside as well
"Take care of yourself from the inside"
I told her
I thought she was going to apologize,
but she just said to keep quiet
So I told her to get out
She said not "me" but "you" get out
I was so mad
Well anyway, that has nothing to do with right now
Has nothing to do with this?
Nothing to do with this?
It looks like I have trauma
Oh, you're talking about being in here?
- Yeah
I have childhood memories
Yeah, you remember the past
I went on a field trip to the mountains in Nara
I didn't want to be in the group, so
I went with Sakata and Tsukaguchi
on a different path
We were walking and found a cave
We went into the cave to play, and you know
how kids always forget about the time
We didn't realize how late it was and soon it was
dark outside. Everyone was looking for us
They called my parents and the police
Everyone was so worried about us
Since then, dark and small places
I hate it
So what are you doing in there?!
That's strange what he's saying!
OK, are you alright now?
What?
Huh?
Herry and get away from my house
OK
We're going to eat sushi
I'll get out
I'm finally out
You're not out!
You didn't get out mister
Cant you get out on your own?
Leave me alone
Hurry get out
You're causing trouble
We can't leave with you here
What's the matter?
Are you hurt?
"Happy"
What?
What are you saying mister?
It's not happy, you're causing everyone trouble!
I'm causing trouble?
Right?
I see
Yes, you're committing a crime
Crime?
Yes, this is a crime
This is a crime?
- Yes, it's a crime
This is someone's property right?
You're causing trouble and they can't
use the washing machine either
Did you think about that?
You'll arrest me?
I will arrest you
You're going to arrest me?
Yes I will
If you do that, my wife and child will cry
Yes that's true
That wouldn't be good
Getting arrest will be a problem,
I can't show my face in public
Whatever
Whatever?!
Whatever? What is he talking about?
I'm going to arrest you and put you in handcuffs
I'm also causing you trouble huh?
Yes you are
The police
You must be busy
- Yes
You must be busy with guys like me
Somehow...
I'm sorry...
I'm sorry.. somehow.. I'm always just thinking about myself
Please forgive me!
"Police man"
Why only "Police man" in English?
Why just that part?
Mister, do you want to get arrested?
Mister!
You're going too far
OK?
- Yes
Also...
if I didn't go home, my family will be worried
Yes, they will worry
I didn't call or anything for the past 3 days
That's bad
I'm such a terrible husband huh?
I can't show my face huh?
I want to get married
You're not married?!