Subtitles/Timing: eChie
Visit http://zurui.blogspot.com
Napping 2
Shitamachi Bugyo, Toyama Saemonnojyo sama is coming.
*Hamada is dreaming that he is "Toyama
no Kinsan" based on the TV drama
Everyone face up!
Hey, Echizenya.
Do you admit that at the festival of Kajitsu Hachiman Shrine,
you received lots of bribes by taking advantage
of being the festival controller?
No, Obugyo-sama.
It is not true at all.
It is a made-up story by this girl.
Makun, Makun!
Makun, phone call!
Phone call!
What!
You got a phone call.
Not now!
Later?
Yes!
Shall I tell them?
Shoot, leave!
What! I'm just letting you know!
Close the door!
Hearing such words from your mouth,
that usually speak to the world,
I feel pretty ashamed.
So, you are saying...
that you have no connection to this matter, is that correct?
That's correct.
By the way, I heard this girl's father, Tomekichi,
was financially in trouble.
Isn't it Tomekichi that was receiving the bribes?
No, it is not true, Obugyo-sama.
My father was deceived by Echigoya..
What is it?
The festival controller..
Are you still reading such a thing?!
Study instead!
What the hell!
All you read are these magazines, so
No wonder your grades are getting better and better!
Such magazines, huh!
Get out!
And you guys better go home!
Echigoya..
It's getting late.
Shut up!
What?
I'm gonna kill you!
Go to bed!
OK!
After the festival, he got stabbed and died!
Oh, that's too bad!
You are lying!
Hm?
She is just making up the story. There is no evidence!
Come to think about it, Obugyo-sama...On that night...
What are you doing?!
Go to sleep already!
Electricity is not free!
I know, stupid! Don't turn it off!
What are you guy doing?
Be quiet!
Obugyo-sama.
Someone called..
Hm.
"Play boy Kinsan" helped us.
Who is Kinsan?
So, I think Kinsan knows everything.
Then, you better ask Kinsan to help you with your homework!
Ask him!
So both your tutor and Kinsan can help you.
What do you think about this?
So I would like you to call Kinsan here.
Call him then.
That's..
Call him!
You call him then!
You leave! What a bother..
What are you saying?
We need Kinsan, and you should just shut up.
What..
You really need to leave!
You shouldn't talk like that..
You go!
That's OK. Your mama just wants to join!
Itao-san, you're handsome, huh.
Want some rice balls?
No need!
Sit down and shut up!
OK, I'll zip my mouth..
Obugyo-sama...
Hm?
Seems I don't need to be here since Kinsan is not here.
So, I will be leaving.
Hey hey hey hey!
From what I hear, you're just saying whatever you want.
What are you saying?
If you want to see Kinsan so much,
Hm.
I'll let you see him!
Can't you just see...
this..
Sakura shower!
What are you doing to your body!
What are you doing!?
You..your mama told you never to do that!
Look at your body!
Your dad will be pissed off!
I will put you..
Oh my god!
Haritsukegokumon!
*Haritsukegokumon - Punishment
by being nailed to a wooden plank
You can't do such a thing!
Take him away!
No way!
You..where are you going?!
Is that all OK now?
Not OK at all!
- Thank you very much.
What..what have you done..
And with that, the case is closed!
Like a Yakuza punk!
What are you doing?
Nothing.
Get away!
That's fine. We used to sleep together like this..
Stop it. It's disgusting!
Nothing wrong to hold my son!
Disgusting! Get away!
What is so disgusting?
Are you stupid?
If I didn't exist, neither do you!
What are you talking about?
What?
Cook something, hurry!
Cook something? I want to sleep with you now!
You stink!
Not at all.
If I stink, you stink too!
What? You are not making any sense!
You were born from my stinky part!
No one is talking about it, stupid!
What are you saying!
Cook something, hurry!
OK, OK, zip your mouth!
Nonsense!