Translation: eChie
CINDERELLA
It's about the time to go to the ball.
Yes, mom.
I want to dance with Prince ASAP.
Me too.
Don't worry. You two are cute,
so he will definitely find you.
Mom, let's hurry up!
Wait, before that... Cinderella!
Cinderella!
Yes, mom.
We are going to a ball now.
Then I'm going too.
Do you think you can go to a ball? You are too ugly!
Don't be kidding.
Look at your face. Turn around!
Hey!
Cinderella, I don't like these shoes.
Please bring a new pair.
Yes.
Here they are.
Help me put them on.
Yes, sure.
Oh, Cinderella. These shoes are dirty. Lick it clean.
No I can't.
Don't you understand what I'm saying?
Wait damn you!
What did you just do?
Come here! Come here!
Come here.
What did you do?
Stop the camera.
Damn you.
What did you do?
Please calm down. I'm sorry.
Who told you to do it!?
I'm sorry.
Hold a sec. I'm sorry.
Don't monkey around with me. Who told you to do that!?
Hey. Don't touch me!
I said don't touch me!
Sorry.
Don't monkey around with me!
Let me go. Let me go.
Let me go! Let me go!
I'm sorry.
Let me go!
Sorry... Sorry...
Let go I said!
That's OK. Let me go.
Let me go.
Hey damn you!
Get them over here!
Why are you laughing?
Who told you to do that, huh?
Hey!
I'm sorry.
Just leave. Hurry.
Hurry up.
Get out!
Take them out.
I'm so sorry.
Never mind. Leave.
I'm sorry.
Leave already.
Where do you think you three are going?!
Where! Do! You! Think! You're! Going!
Where are you going?
Cameras were here and there and...
There are many.
There are many cameras filming!
Give me a break! All three were deceived!
Come here! Which camera shall we use?  Which one?
Please say "Gottsu Ee Kanji!" to the camera!
Are  you ready?
Gottsu Ee Kanji!
It surprised me.
It was scary!
I'm pissed off!
My stomach hurts...
I'm disgusted!
Who told you to do this?
I'm just playing along. I'm also a victim, really.
It was scary!
It was twice as scary as Umemiya-san.
I didn't know, so I was shaking over there.