ShinobiSubs
(Director Nishida is on holiday)
Our next letter is from a resident in Tokyo, a 52 year old male
The other day my wife goes to me, look at this~! Isn't it great?
It was a ceramic milk pot she had bought
On closer inspection, there was another ceramic pot inside the pot that was perfectly wedged inside and won't come out
Even though I used all my might, I was unable to remove the pot
It's like its cursed and won't come out!
Won't the wonderful detectives please help assist me in separating these?
If at all possible please don't send Detective Tamura Kenji
What the...
There are people who make requests like that?!
The client just doesn't like you
-Well you went to investigate it right?
We went to find out, but were we able to safely remove it?
Please watch and find out!
So here we have the problem in question from our client
As you can see it's quite the fit
It certainly is...
Totally in there tight
I thought it would move but...
It's perfectly snug in there such a tight fit
As you look at this on camera it's hard to tell so...
We have made a digital composition of it
An accurate recreation
This is the cross section of contents
It's easy to understand right?
This has made it set in place
And the handles are jarred so that...
They are keeping it fixed
This is the situation
And today's client is?
-He's here
The client arrives
-Thank you for helping
This is a regular off shoot
Wait, wait, wait... What's going on?
Hold on!
Detective Sawabe was unaware of whom the client was
I'm the person that sent the letter in
Hold the... Wait, wait!
The client this time is really Matsumoto Hitoshi...-San ?!
The real requester is Matsumoto Hitoshi-san
Pleased to work  with you
This is...
I'm a huge fan of the show
Yeah but... Really?!
Honest! Event hough I've been living in Tokyo for a while now
(Matsumoto is from Osaka and where Knight Scoop is shot)
Still?
-Yes
The pair discuss the favourite parts
Well I think it would have to be...
Do you remember that one with...
I was really surprised, the girl who could hear the 4 leaf clovers
That one was legendary
(Subbed, link in the description)
The other one was with the old lady who wanted to meet Ika-chan
(01-05-2015)
And the one where Ishida gets under the house
Where he lost his license down there!
(02-27-2015)
That was a really great piece
Even though I hate Ishida...
You hate him why?!
When he slaps your head, he hits too hard
I have felt it before so I understand...
The audience doesn't even laugh!
It really feels like I'm back in Osaka round here
It's not a good or bad thing, but it's like I've gone though a time slip coming back here in Osaka
It's not like I want to take Director Nishida's job but...
I'm sure he will be pleased
Please wait until Director Nishida returns
We get on really well I think!
What if it was you sat there!
This is... I mean, really, look at it
Have you felt how tough it's in?
My wife asked me to have a go at it...
I've looked and tried
But nothing was really effective
I have become kind of attached to it...
Well we have a few Knight Scoop standard procedures to test through
I see, the basic tests right?
The first will be heating and expansion. Then we will cool and contract
You will expand the outer and contract the inner part?
To shrink the inner part, we will place dry ice inside
Then place the whole piece in hot water to warm the outside
That is the experiment
So uh...
Please give it a go
Of course the detective will usually do it but...
Today is have the client experience day on Knight Scoop
The dry ice is -79'c
And the hot water is 100'c
The temperature range difference is 179'c !!
Well, look... I know we want to take it out but..
If it comes out like this first time
It will be a little disappointing
Well the objective of the show is to have some fun after all...
Yes, yes that is true I suppose
It feels like it should explode
-I'm scared, there is a possibility of that
Please remove it!
It won't budge!
Not at all!
Sawabe-san, seriously, not an inch!
Wait what
It's in there tight
We have the professor to help us
I heard him muttering earlier
He is here to help
He is well renowned as the Knight Scoop professor
Of course, I have seen him plenty on here
If we force it, it is likely to break
We need to increase the temperature range
Make it so the difference in temperature range is larger
Please make your way over there
What's this?!
This time we have a little...
Well you see...
Fire proof clothing
It's dangerous
Sensei! You are fully prepared
I think... It's Yamada-Sensei
That can't possibly be liquid nitrogen?!
That's right
Woah woah woah liquid nitrogen...
Liquid... Liquid nitrogen!
It will be turned into nitrogen!
This liquid nitrogen is -169'c
And the hot water is 100'c
Are you ok?
He has to be careful not to get the nitrogen in the hot water
Be careful!! Are you ok?!
Liquid nitrogen reacts violently in hot water
Can you, this way, with...
I can't do it from this angle
Like this
Is this going to be okay to put in hot water?
-I don't know
What do you mean you don't know!?
I'm so scared!
It's in! Damn that was hot!
And?
So...
With this hot and cold variance
We also add some vibration
We are going all out with this one then
Ready?
Then you will apply some movement to it
With this temperature variance we add vibration!
Ok! Matsumoto-san! Let's take it out!!
Is it okay to touch?
Damn that's hot!
Of course it will be hot!!
I'm pretty tense right now
It's completely stuck!
No way!
It just won't budge!
Why!
What will we do?!
But...
Shall we give that a go?
It's worth a try at least
Floss?
-Shall we give it a go?
Shouldn't we have tried this from the start?
This is pretty surprising these basic science principles
We have it looped round
All you have to do is pull?
See!
-Please observe everyone...
Completely stuck.
It's not moving
-It's soon time that Matsumoto-san has his next shoot...
What are you filming? Matsumoto's home on a day off?
松本家の休日
Well which Matsumoto has this as a problem?!
This is a real Matsumoto's home problem
-Do you wanna try yanking it out?
Try pulling it out in 1?
If it's Matsumoto-san...
Ready?
I'm disgusted.
Terrible
What is the bad sentiment about this?!
So it's possible to have failed investigations?
It's a possibility we don't succeed
We sometimes have those on Knight Scoop!
Well what are you going to do about this now?
I'll... Probably give up
WHAT DO YOU MEAN GIVE UP?!
Well, if you can't do this then, if we work together again on a different show...
To put it bluntly, I'll ignore the shit out of you!
That's not what a good senpai does!
Is it really impossible?
Well I'm going to the next shoot...
If you do it, bring it to me?
We don't usually have such unreasonable requests!
Well, I have to go...
Ah, this isn't my jacket...
Please I'm counting on you!
DON'T BREAK IT!
I'm not allowed to break it?
-Of course NOT!
Got it, good luck
Man this is a pain
So, Matsumoto has gone to film and now by myself
I shall prevail
We have warmed it, got the dry ice inside...
Now we need some lubrication
This is washing up liquid
If I can just ease it like...
WAIT!! THIS JUST NOW...!! IT MOVED! IT MOVED!
I got it out !!!
Alright!
Amazing!
Perfect
This is a perfect success!
Matsumoto's house on a day off studio
Hello, sorry to interrupt so suddenly
You did it?? No way
Really? That quick?!
The result...
You got it out!
It's out!
How? How? How? How?
Perfectly came out
How?
It still has dry ice in it!
-Don't touch it
We got it out perfectly in one piece!
Win!
But I want to see how it was inside can we...?
WHY?!
We haven't seen how it was inside it
You don't understand the troubles we had!
How it must have got inside is unbelievable
To get at that angle
Oh, it's in!
That was the one thing I didn't want !!!
You better get it out !!
-I can, I can!
Give it a go
It came out like sloppy seconds
Honestly thank you so much!
That is wonderful
We managed to remove it!
I have some other problems at home that might take a bit longer to resolve
Macchan was the requester!
He suddenly he came in...
It was really unexpected
But I honestly had no clue about it
I just saw this hench blonde guy in the corner of my eye....
I was so surprised, then I realised it was Matsumoto Hitoshi-san
It was a unbelievable situation that worked out well in the end!