All of you probably often go on remote shoots.
In "stroll-around-town" variety, TV talents go to restaurants ...
... where they have to get filming permission. - Right!
They'll go "Is it ok if we shoot here?". - "Are you ok with cameras?".
And if they get permission, they'll go "OK~!". - All the time!
All the time, right?
This time I have a theory that's related to this.
It's this one!
"If, in a stroll-around-town type variety where you have to go ask for filming permission, ..."
"... your co-host went inside and didn't return no matter how long you wait, ..."
"... you'll ultimately assume the worst!"
That's about as meaningless a theory as they come!
"If, in a stroll-around-town type variety where you have to go ask for filming permission, ..."
"... your co-host went inside and didn't return no matter how long you wait, ..."
"... you'll ultimately assume the worst!"
The comedy duo Kaeru-tei makes up the target (left) & instigator (right) of our investigation this time.
Until this point, they've participated in a stroll-around-town type shoot for around an hour.
They're shooting diligently!
The nuts taste great!
Uwah, a Chinese restaurant! - Chinese!
They're delicious, these hole-in-the-wall shops.
This looks great!
Our setting will be this Chinese restaurant.
Do your best!
I pray for your success!
She's hyped herself up!
They're this far away from the place?
How'll it go? Ah, are they even open? Seems they are!
Pretty far away!
She's inside! - Pardon me!
It's her first time asking for shooting permission.
I wonder if she'll be fine.
Nakano is worried for his partner, since she's not experienced with this type of shoot.
Naturally.
5 minutes pass since Iwakura entered the restaurant.
That's long! - 5 minutes is long for this.
Does it normally take this long?
It's taking longer than expected.
Another 10 minutes pass.
Scary.
This has gone beyond "she has trouble since it's her first time". - Right.
You'd get worried!
What should we do?
I want him to go save her!
It's taken quite long.
By this time I'm getting a bit worried.
Maybe I'll go have a glimpse? - Yeah.
That's right!
Maybe I can even see them from the outside.
She could've simply set up an "I've already eaten before you" kind of joke.
He moves to get a grasp of the situation inside.
When he opens the door to the restaurant ...
Eh, that's scary! - Terrifying!
... he will find the scene of a scuffle.
There are even bloodstains on the floor.
Creating suspense?
Moreover, Iwakura's possessions are all over the palce.
The staff at this show is messed up!
How will Nakano react?
That's terrifying! - I hate this!
This is awful!
Terrifying!
Eh?
Excuse me!
Ah, the owner's there!
Ah, excuse me!
Welcome.
But that's all the more scary.
I'm with a TV show for TBS.
We're walking around, filming in this area ...
... in the hopes of visiting some restaurants that look promising.
I believe that my partner came to visit you moments ago ...
Scary ...
Eh?
You don't know? Well ...
SCARY!
Didn't someone come here earlier?
No.
Eh, he's so scary!
Eh, but someone did come in here earlier.
No.
I'd be fearing for my life if I was him!
Ah ... is that so?
The ominous owner feigns ignorance ...
... and for an instant he backs away.
His face is saying "Damn, I screwed up".
But ...
But one person did come in here earlier.
Not that I know.
I've been watching the entire time, and she didn't come out.
I see.
No ... !
Somehow, Nakano hangs on.
Is there a 2nd floor? - Yes.
Is there customer seating in the 2nd floor? - Mhm.
Why does he talk like that?!
Ah, I see.
Could you perhaps show me the inside of the restaurant?
Amazing! He's trying to look for her!
On camera.
No ...
Would that be too much trouble?
Yes. - Ah ...
Did no one come here earlier? Really?
No one came.
Scary! - To be repeatedly told "No one came here" ...
But now ...
A voice!
Wh- ... what's that sound?
What? - What's that sound?
What are you doing?
- What kind of shoot is this?!
What sound? - This one.
What? What are you on about? - Could you just let me check?
What are you doing?!
- You gotta do something!
Check? Check what? - The back.
I can hear an unusual voice from back there.
What's your problem. - Sorry.
Is he going to go back there?
Don't bullshit me.
This is so scary ...
What the hell is wrong with you? - Please excuse me!
This is my store. - I know!
What the hell? - Ex- ... excuse me!
Amazing!!
What the hell is wrong with you?!
This is the worst.
What a reaction!!
Take that off!
What was that about just now? - It was like from a movie!
It'll probably come off even if you just open your mouth!
That was so scary!
That guy was terrifying!
You're a brave one!
Good work. - Don't just "Good work" me, that guy was terrifying!
He was so damn scary!
Now he looks kind.
At first I thought maybe she was preparing some kind of joke.
Just as you said!
But the wait kept getting longer and she wouldn't come out ...
... so I figured she must've been trapped somehow.
And then I went inside to find this scary guy waiting!
Well said!
Moving on to the next instigator & target pair.
This is quite the pair! - Are they gonna be alright?!
Hollywood Zakoshisyoh & Chance Oshiro.
Will Oshiro be ok?
Is Oshiro going to be alright here?!
Both of them have little experience with stroll-around-town variety ...
... but at this point they've already been filming for around an hour.
An exaggeration of Doi Takako!
It's not Doi Takako, I told you it was Renaissance!
And then ...
I'm heading in! Like this, right?
The shoot looks like a lot of fun though!
Shisyoh went inside.
Oshiro's going to be hopeless. - Yeah, Chance is not normal.
Excuse me~!
I wonder if he can get permission.
Ah, but this is fun!
When panicking he's capable of anything!
Chance is fully enjoying this variety shoot.
10 minutes pass without Shisyoh returning.
What is he doing?
Did Shisyoh get caught up in something? - Right ...
Maybe we should contact him.
Can you go check on him? - I'll go have a look.
Shisyoh's taking a long time.
This time ...
... the staff that's part of this shoot will also disappear one by one.
Scary!
We'll investigate how Chance will react once he's the only one left.
What's going on in there? - It's odd.
They're taking quite long, is it ok if we also go take a look? - Sure!
Please wait here a moment. - Will do!
And so the director & cameraman also head inside, completing our preparations.
All of them?!
5 minutes pass since he's been made to wait all by himself.
What will he do?
They're taking long! Maybe I should go?
Maybe they had their lights punched out by a dodgy employee.
Eh? Maybe that Chinese restaurant ...
"punched their lights out"?
... is a front for organized crime?
Do Chinese restaurants like that even exist?!
But there's no way the very first restaurant ...
... in a shopping district in Gotokuji would be a shady place.
Well said!
As no one returns from the restaurant ...
... he theorizes that this hole-in-the-wall Chinese restaurant is involved in organized crime.
I've never heard anyone say that! - Now he's eavesdropping.
He listens closely to get a feel for the situation inside.
What should I do ...
He won't go in?
Ah this is scary, what should I do ...
No choice but to go inside!
He can't bring himself to open the door.
And so, Chance, unable to muster the courage to go inside, ...
Seriously?
... buys tea from a convenience store ...
Eh, why? - Why would he ... ?
... and bread from a nearby bakery.
Scary, scary, scary!
He opens the door just a little to get a glimpse of the inside.
What's he doing?!
This is scary ... super scary!
I told you Chance is not normal!
You're the scary one here!
He walks up and down in front of the store to get his thoughts in order.
Finally ...
Alright, I'll go.
I'm prepared for the worst.
You've gotta go!
- Yeah, something clearly happened in there.
Everything in disorder.
This is so scary ...
This time the owner of the restaurant won't even show himself.
Ah, there was definitely a scuffle here ...
There was definitely- UWAAH!
That sure is scary.
Shisyoh ...
And then ...
Move the chair at least!
Shisyoh?
Ah, he's going!
Shisyoh!! What happened?!
Surely you can tell what happened.
Eh?! Who did this?!
He still can't tell?
Are you ... are you alright?!
Was it ... an employee here?
Thank goodness! I was so scared, I was sure you'd gotten involved with someone shady!
I mean surely you can figure it out by now!
Who did this to you? The owner?
He thinks this is organized crime after all.
Where did he go?
Aaaah, no way! WAIT!
I GOT IT! I GOT IT, ALRIGHT?! JUST WAIT!
JUST WAIT! WAIT WAIT WAIT WAIT!
WAIT A SECOND! JUST WAIT!
He's taking out money!
IT'S ALL OK, JUST WAIT!
Money?!
I GOT IT! JUST WAIT!
He laid out money!
7000 yen! I counted 7!
Why 7000 yen?!
What are you doing?
That's just a bit over 1000 yen per person!
I'M SO SORRY! We were just filming!
But I'm ... I'm really sorry! I am!
Were they rude to you?
I'm sorry! NO WAIT! PLEASE JUST WAIT!
Please wait! I have someone I love!
A girl I want to confess to! Please wait!!
I've never even been to an amusement park!
I'm begging you, wait, please!
At this point we reveal everything.
He wants to go to an amusement park! - What should he wait for, seriously?!
But he wants to go to an amusement park!
- With the girl he loves!
I simply thought I had no choice but to go inside!
You say that, but you couldn't bring yourself to do it for the longest time! - It was scary!
I thought I was going to get stabbed!
I thought this was it for me. My life would end here.
I thought "So this is how it ends".
"At last they put me on TV more and then I get killed"
That's just my life, I guess.
By the way, the girl Chance wanted to confess to is the 3 o'clock heroine, Yumecchi.