Welcome to Wednesday Downtown,
Let’s get on with our first presenter please
Anyone?
Fujimon
Today is the Toudaiou vs Wednesday Downtown quiz!
A collaborative one-hour special
-Ah, so that's it
Wednesday Downtown, which is intellectually inferior to Toudaiou
But maybe tied in terms of physical strength and perseverance
I don't think we're any less intelligent than they are.
-Of course we are!
Not even close
-Not even close
So today we have prepared three matchups
The first matchup is this
Loud voice x Q&A
By the way, these are the people representing Wednesday Downtown
Ah, not bad! These are the masters
Looking good
-I think we may win here
These people can be considered the top three in the entire show business
-Pretty much
Although perhaps not comparable in terms of Q&As, in terms of loudness, these three are strong
Smart people have small voices
Ah yes yes yes
-Seems that way
That's really true
Why are you suddenly so quiet
Shameful
-You really suddenly lowered your voice just now
What follows is three mixed rules matches
Toudaiou vs Wednesday Downtown Showdown
Wednesday Downtown VS Toudaiou
The first matchup is Loud Voice x Q&A
Very loud voices!
Do you have confidence, Wednesday team?
Looks pretty cold
Of course
Where's our "Welcome!"?
"Welcome"!
There it is
Who's Yamaguchi?
On the one hand, there should be no problem with the knowledge of the Toudaiou team
The problem is the volume
-Yes
You haven't spoken out loud much in your entire life, have you?
-No. Absolutely not
Just a few times
I had to sing a song once
Who understands this? Your little story
This year's Loud Voice x Quiz takes the form of a group of three
There are girls in this competition.
The first person reads the question out loud
The second person shouts out the answer to the question
If the answer is correct, points will be awarded for each meter of distance added up
We have prepared three questions for each team
The Toudaiou team will start first
So upon determining the approximate distance that sound can travel
The East King team decided to challenge first with a total distance of 225 meters
The sky is cloudless and its a sunny day
The temperature is 9 degrees Celsius and there is no wind at the venue
This is the perfect environment for shouting
It's too far away, right?
Held at Bando Golf Course, Ibaraki Prefecture
They all went to Ibaraki!
Loud voice x Q&A begins
Then, please read the question first
In which magazine were Boboboubo Boubobo and Midori no Makibao serialized?
Can only hear so much
Such a long question
I heard the question clearly
Eh? Really?
So, please answer
But does he know the answer?
Weekly Shonen Jump!
Audible
Then please show the question board
Ah, impressive!
Weekly Shonen Jump
Such a quiet voice
Correct answer!
It doesn't matter, right?
Great! Yeah yeah yeah!
Toudaiou's first question is correct
No matter how you put it, it is a loud Q&A
Toudaiou did a great job and answered the first question correctly
Earning 225 points
The comedians can surely win
Basically, I didn't miss anything.
-Great
I heard the two titles clearly
Maybe its ok to dare to go a little farther away
In contrast, the Wednesday team chose to stretch a little further
They can totally go further, right?
They choose to take on the challenge at 250 meters
No problem at all
Testing it out
So, Loud voice x Q & A. The first is Oda
Please read out the question
Who said the famous quote "Let them eat cake"?
Awesome!
Can surely hear this clearly
Ok, I heard clearly
Then, Fujimoto, please answer
It's a little shameful to be so loud if you're wrong
-Very shameful
Does Tsuda know this...
Please show the question board
Marie Antoinette
Correct answer
Awesome
Great, great, great!
As you can see, this team also answered correctly
Earning 250 points
The second question from Toudaiou team
Girls team
They challenge 300 meters
Please guess together with the audience
This is hopeless, right?
Can hear a little bit
What is it supposed to be?
Sounds like something, then something
And then at the end its "What's next?"
By only hearing a list and then "what's next"
There are too few clues
Can she deduce the answer?
What will the answer be?
Please guess together with the audience
Perfect
Here it is heard
Shinzo Abe
Wrong answer
Ah, its not right
The full question wasn't heard
Ah, that's right
By just a list and "what's next?" she guesses its about Prime Ministers
Impressive
With this clue
The correct answer is "Hatoyama"
Although the answer is not correct, it is still very impressive
But unfortunately they don't get any points
What a genius!
I'm sorry
Next, the second question for the Wednesday team
200m directly
They challenge the longest of 350m so far
Tsuda is very good at it
Please guess together with the audience
Curry Rice
In order to keep the feeling of a week, what do the Maritime Self-Defense Force crew eat every Friday?
Correct answer
-Great!
Awesome, isn't it!!!
-Awesome!!!
The excellent answer to this question widens the score difference to 375 points
So, Toudaiou team
What're they gonna do?
We are aiming for a tie
Betting on the opponent's incorrect answer for a tie
With the quietest participant Okamoto asking the question
They challenge 375m
Recently used as an ingredient of protein, what is the moisture floating on yogurt called?
You've never spoken so loudly before, right?
Please answer
The first time
The questions are quite difficult
He heard
Ok
Impressive
Whey
Correct!
Toudaiou team gets 375 points!
Ah great...
So, the Wednesday Downtown team
Challenges 400m for their last question
For rolling sushi, what type of gourd
is used in the speciality sushi of Tochigi Prefecture?
Tochigi Prefecture Specialty Rolled Sushi
What?
Thin...
It's understandable, right?
Come on
What kind of expression is that?
What?
That word... where is that... what?
danbo
Incorrect!
What a pity!
Oi!
Say it again in the same tone as before
Kanpyo!
It's clearly "danbo"!
Therefore, both sides have the same score at this point
Next is the second match
Same score?
Same
Indeed
Well, comedians are still great.
-Yeah!
Hamada
Next time we have a loud voice x quiz, please be sure to participate
That is doable
Why else would you maintain a loud persona to this day, right?
When we shoot Gaki
When he says "the first time" he's super loud
Who cares?
When you say "the first time"
-The voice is very loud
The voice is very loud
Can you give us a quick "the first time"
What the hell!
-Please
I just say it normally!
Please give us a "the first time"
Just go to "chiki chiki"
The first time on Gaki no Tsukai ya Arahende!
It feels like, WAH, right in your ear
Really
-Great!
It makes you wonder what the second time will be like
The sound is so loud for the first time
So, let's get on with it
Please take a look at the next matchup
Extreme Cold x Q&A
That noise was also deadly
Sorry sorry sorry sorry
Shouting "the first time" warmed him up
There is no need to shout so loudly here
-He's fired up
Forgot to turn the volume back down
Usually its at a 4 but he went to 8
The stage shifts to Tsumagoi Village in Gunma Prefecture, where the quiz competition is held
Extreme Cold x Q&A
Looks so cold
That's enough. Stop clapping.
-I can't. Let's get started already
By the way, the temperature is minus 12 degrees.
-Stop talking about it
Just put a subtitle at the bottom
The youngest on our side is 37 years old, okay?
The oldest is 50
I'm 50 years old
You didn't get into Toudaiou for this kind of work, did you?
The second game is a scattered flower quiz held at a snow mountain
Super cold
10 points for one correct answer, the more correct answers, the more points
But if you hide in a cabin because you can't stand the cold, you will be deprived of the right to answer
Moreover, the winner is determined by the total score of the three games
What will be the result of this extremely cold quiz?
So, Extreme Cold x Q&A begins!
Wow, impressive
So tough
-Awful
-This is it
So cold so cold!
Swarming all over the place.
-Inch by inch
The leader is really fast
So fast!
Please listen to the question
3 for 210 yen. How much for 10?
2000 yen!
Wrong answer, the answer is 700 yen
What are you doing?
-I couldn't get it
Really what the hell, think a little will you
Scary scary scary scary
Please listen to the question
What is the medical term for a buzzing headache after eating something cold?
Migraine
Wrong answer
-So hard!
It's ice cream, right?
-Ice cream headache
Please listen to the question
Which language is Gelände, which indicates a ski resort, in?
It's German
Correct answer. 10 points to Toudaiou
-Yes!
Wow, it's cold, it's cold, hurry up!
Please listen to the question
The diameter of a 1 yen coin is exactly how many centimeters?
1cm
Wrong answer
-What are you doing?
How can it be 1 cm
How many centimeters? Tell me the answer!
Please listen to the question
What is the rightmost color of the 4-color button of the TV remote control?
So hard
Yellow
The answer is correct.
-Great
Team Wednesday scores 10 points
-Great!
Please listen to the question
What is the name of the snowman who looks forward to summer in the movie "Frozen"?
This is too easy
Olaf
Get 10 points
-Too easy
It's cold. I can't.
-I can't do it
What's in the envelope depends on luck
Please listen to the question
い ろ or は, which are not in the human body?
ろ
Correct, 10 points!
-OK
15 minutes have passed since the start of the game, the current score is shown above
Nose is all red
Right at this moment
Please listen to the question.
-Guys, I can't do it
I'm not even thinking straight
Answer 1 more question
You can still answer one more question. You can do it.
-I got several questions right
I got 3 questions right.
-Believe in yourself
3...how many correct answers did you get?
-Answer 1 more question
What's the point of your bickering here?
Answer 1 more question
One more!
Get back here, Komiya!
The person to answer the most correct answers for the Wednesday team gives up here
Komiya knows a lot
Ha...
Gave up after 16 minutes
Ah, really can't stand it
My brain won't work in this situation
Looks pretty cold.
-It really was
After this
-Listen to the question
Can't think straight
Who is the Moroccan traveler known for his book "Travels in Three Continents"?
Ibn Battuta
Who?
Correct!
Wow
-Never heard of him
"Raw wheat, raw rice, raw chicken, raw eggs", how many times did I say "raw"?
So fast
Correct
-Awesome
The Toudaiou team keep scoring while the other team...
Ice is a solid of water, what is dry ice a solid of?
Air
Wrong, the answer is carbon dioxide
-Really?
His wife is Ando Sakura, father is Emoto Akira, brother is Emoto Tokio, who is the actor?
Emoto...
Emoto Akira
Incorrect
Already said it!
What the hell?
Emoto was in the question
- You didn't realise?
Emoto Akira
Though the leader is second to none in physical strength, with his low intelligence, he drags the team down
In the first 40 minutes of the game, the deficit is already quite large
Toudaiou are pretty persistent
Not only that, but Fujimoto is also reaching his limit
Fujimon, you can do it!
I'll withdraw if the answer is right
I've already made up my mind. Answer right and I'll give up
It's blank
Okay, next one, next one
Never seen this expression before
It'll kill...people
-Please give up before then
This...this show will not be broadcast
If it doesn't then I can't manage...
Maybe Wed Down will be cancelled
I wanted to finish with a correct answer!
He said he would give up if he answered one more question. Will Fujimoto be able to end up as he wishes?
I'll be at the cabin in a minute
Answer this question correctly I will go to the cabin immediately
-It's blank
Consecutive misses are very impressive
Come on, come again, come again, come again
One more question. Go on, go on
What's wrong with that guy? Are you crazy?
-GoGoGoGo Fight Fight
Please listen to the question
What is the official name of the highly popular game "Motomori"?
Animal Crossing
Correct!
I can't do it
My hands, my hands...
I'm sorry, Fujimoto
It's enough already, Shoji.
-Thanks
Did good, Shoji.
-My hands...
I'll be right there
50 minutes from the start, Shoji gave up after answering 5 questions correctly
Go!
-Three of the Toudaiou team also quit in quick succession
The leader might be suffering brain problems
Even if we say "no more" and plan to give up
He will get down on his knees to keep us
That guy is a bit of a problem
Why?
The theme has changed
Please listen to the question
The larger the amount, the higher the tax rate. What kind of system is this?
What?
Consumption tax
What are you talking about?
Incorrect
-Incorrect?
What? I don't know
Let me go, I can't do it anymore, I can't feel anything
Let me go
This question has to be answered correctly
Please listen to the question
What is the sum of kinetic energy and potential energy called?
It's gotten to this point...
Gravity
Wrong answer
-Too hard
Please listen to the question
The Ministry of Health, Labour and Welfare provides the "Novel Coronavirus Exposure Confirmation APP" called?
COCOA
Correct answer
-Great!
Please give me the right to stop
Bad luck too, the questions were too hard
Stop messing with me
Can I quit?
It's so hard, I can't...
At this point, Ito, the last member of the Toudaiou team, gives up after 1 hour and 5 minutes
On the other side
What is the essential fish in the Hokkaido specialty "Ishikari Nabe"?
Salmon
Great, it's finally over!
You can still answer one more question
Impossible, impossible
Come back!
I don't know what he's talking about
Wow, this is... it's not even my own hand
Finally, only this man remains
How small can the gap be reduced in the face of the King of the East, who finished with 460 points?
The magician brothers who are famous for "Magic~Meow" are?
Kudo Brothers
The American (British) physicist who discovered universal gravity was?
This should be known, right?
The Apple one
Not this one
Edison
Who is it? It's the Apple one, right?
Thinking of William Bale
It was an hour and 40 minutes after the start of the game when the team failed to close the gap.
This man is so desperate
What is the Japanese translation of student's shoes?
Leather Shoes
Loafers
Incorrect
Leader, leader, let's stop here
That...everyone is shocked
Although this is not appropriate to say to a senior, this is abnormal
I've never seen anyone like you
The more you try, the more you are hated
Am I hated?
-Yes. The crowd is already booing
Is it true?
-Yes
One more question
Don't...
-Just one question
Hey, leader, leader, leader!
-Just one question. Just one question
Then one question. ah OKOK, last question, OK
Please listen to the question
What is the new station on the JR Yamanote Line that started operation last year?
Takanawa Gatecity
Incorrect
Eh？Gatecity
Gatecity
-Wrong answer
Yamanote Line...eh?
Gatecity… eh？
Bad bad bad bad
Leader...
Leader, leader, leader!
Hey, leader, please!
Leader, wait wait...
What the hell, you said just one more
Not only that
-Listen to the question
The female host is also very hard working
Who was the youngest person to win the Akutagawa Prize for the novel "I Want to Kick You in the Back"?
Matayoshi
Risa Miya
No, it's not!
Leader
-Hello
Enough!
-Okay
Please let us go
OK I will try my best
Please listen to the question
What is the name of the event that occurred at the beginning of the universe about 15 billion years ago?
Big Bang
Correct answer
-You see!
Can't catch up
He ran again
This guy is amazing
No one can stop such a leader
It's turning around, it's turning around
-You'll die.
Please listen to the question
Poor host
What family of animals are jaguars, cheetahs, and lions?
Cat
Hopeless...
He continues to fight alone despite the dissuasion of teammates
Answer this question correctly and you'll tie with Toudaiou
-Great!
It's on him alone
Please listen to the question
What is the cured product of sturgeon eggs, which is known as one of the top three delicacies in the world?
Caviar
Correct answer
At this time
Great, great, great, great!
Great, great, great
Reversed, reversed
-It's okay. It's okay
It's fine
OK OK OK
Leader, do you know what time it is?
Don't know, reverse!
It's 4:00.
-Really?
Its 4 now
-Reverse reverse reverse
It's already 4:00
Last one. Come on.
-Thank you
The staff must be anxious
I thank you
Please listen to the question
Which of the following is Italian cuisine?
Meat Buns, Thin Cut Raw Meat, French Pudding
Thin cut raw meat
Correct answer
Reverse
Okay, let's go back. Let's go back.
Let me widen the gap
As the Wednesday team completes a comeback, they are forced to end the quiz
It is entirely thanks to the leader
The group leader is really great
But I refuse to be on this show with him again
Impressive
It was already 8:00 am when I got back to TBS
I went straight to this one after the Loud Q&A
Not easy
-Then back at 8:00
After a little bit of sleep, I started recording a 3-hour special
Then went straight to the next place again
Yasuda Circus is really something!
The only normal person is HIRO
-He really is the most normal one
Yes
The group leader said, "I want my children to see me in a good light."
Worked so hard to let his children see think he's cool
-Even so...
But he was awful at the actual Q&A aspect
Didn't look good in this regard at all
Everyone should be careful around him in the future, I mean it
Try not to meet him on the road
The next matchup is
Sleepless x Q&A
Say it properly!
What?
Really?
-You're really...
Hey, Hamada...
Say it properly
I said it properly!
-No, you didn't
That's not your way, is it?
-No, no, no
You'll complain again
He's suppressing it
The volume is set to 2
It should be something on top of the remote control
Only these two modes? The sound is either very loud or very small
The volume should be 4
About 4 is just right
Make some adjustments
Ok got it
Answer 1 question every 10 minutes without stopping
But the question time for that quiz is 48 hours
▼48 hours, 1 question ever 10 mins             ▼Even if you fall asleep  questioning continues
So long!
This is terrible
If you are sleeping, you can not answer the question
Sustained sobriety is the key to victory
So hard
-Questions asked every 10 minutes
This time, Wednesday Downtown sent this person
Audrey's Kasuga
Another different type
What do you all think of Kasuga?
The endurance he has shown in this program is really...
Right!
Very strong
And his amount of knowledge is good
-Yes
I remember he is good at quizzes
Strong in both areas
He took the exam for University of Tokyo.
-Yes
Is that so?
Perfect for him
So the participants of the sleepless quiz were
20-year-old Inomata and Audrey's Kasuga, who is famous for his endurance
However
This is a ready-for-sleep pose
Is this what's happening?
Calm environment
▼Dim lighting
▼Recliner
▼Healing music
More than just being awake
Have to resist this environment
-Indeed
So that's it
So 48 hours to stay awake quiz begins!
So at 10pm
The endurance quiz with 288 consecutive questions has begun
First category selection... although I understand the need to hurry up and select
But there are still 48 hours to go
▼Every hour a new topic is selected
I just don't feel like thinking about it
Even if we speed up here its useless
I'll take physics.
-Physics?
Suddenly?
Already sleepy
Ah, there it is
Questions appear silently from the monitor every 10 minutes
Thinking time is 3 minutes
After being re-asked
The German physicist known for his theory of relativity was?
I thought, "Can I just answer that person?"
Ah, so dangerous, physics is difficult
But every question is important
Einstein
Albert Einstein
Write the full name
This is still question 1
Questions are now asked from level 1 to level 6 in each category
A system where the difficulty level rises slowly over the course of 1 hour
Well, if you don't get it right
Even if you are awake, it is meaningless
So if you plan your sleep schedule
It is better to be asleep when the 6th question appears
But, ah
That wouldn't be Kasuga!
It doesn't matter if you get it right or not
Can just brag at the beginning
It's time for a Q&A
Ah, I'm sleepy...
Already sleepy
Sleepy already?
-Sleepy
Yes, in fact, these 2 people
By the way, how long did you sleep today?
Around 9:00 am... I started to wake up
So its actually a 60-hour challenge
I'm looking forward to it
I also got up at 7:00 or 8:00
That's great
I am "61 Hours Q&A".
-That's great!
Starting from a state that has been awake for half a day
It's actually a challenge of over 60 hours
Can they stay awake and keep answering to the end?
The three primary colors of light are red - blue and what color?
It's here
Suddenly it appears
Eh?
What was it?
Eh...
Can't be sure anymore
Is this it?
I got it right!
Who was the first Japanese person to receive the Nobel Prize in Physics?
Physics Prize?
Kasuga is great!
-Awesome!
It's written in Chinese characters!
Very capable
But it doesn't matter
What is the gravitational force acting between molecules called?
Don't be ridiculous. What's this?
Feeling at ease
I do not know gravity, I only know this
Van der Walik
What's this? I don't know
This is so hard
Got it right? That's awesome!
Impressive
So smart
The phenomenon that
the resistance of a
metal, etc. suddenly
becomes zero if it
is cooled to absolute
zero is?
Superconductivity
Ujirou Nakatani
Who was the first
physicist to create
artificial snow,
leaving the famous
quote "Snow is a letter
from heaven"?
Knowledgable
Here
Please draw a hypnosis card
Hypnosis card?
This time there is an opportunity every hour to exchange attacks
Attack props can be used to trap the opponent
Kasuga attacks first
Want to make it a one-two punch
Start
Electric blanket
Very warm
Oh~
Warmer than expected, the same feeling as in the furnace
Not bad
You'll fall asleep. The heater is the place where you fall asleep without realizing it.
-Yeah
I will try my best
Good, good, good, good
Drew a good one
Then 8 hours passed very quickly after the start of the Q&A
The Sleepless Quiz has seen its first morning
Ah, stayed up all night
Hypnotic prop - Movie
What is this? No subtitles either
No dubbing either?
Kasuga, who has been awake almost a whole day
Is attacked by the Sandman
This side too
How many members of the House of Representatives are there in Congress?
Almost at the limit...
It's only been 9 hours
Here
Opportunity knocks
Toudaiou's Inomata finally falls asleep
It's up to you now
Score double when opponent sleeps
So, from now on, Kasuga will be rewarded with twice the number of points if the answer is correct
Chance!
Who was the Prime Minister of Japan at the end of the war?
Unfortunately, the question is level 6 difficulty
Kijyuro Shidehara
No idea about this one
While Inomata continues to sleep
Kasuga chose to specialize in Japanese history
Earn some points here
In 1582, Akechi Mitsuhide's attack on Oda Nobunaga was called?
The Charge of Honnoji Temple
What was the system established
during the reign of Tokugawa
Iemitsu that required
the daimyo to leave the
domain and live in Edo
Account for attendance
Anatomische/Tabellen
What is the name of the
Western medical book that
Genbai Sugita translated
as "New Book of
Disintegration"?
Anatomische
Tabellen
Kasuga gets 60 points for 3 consecutive correct questions
Suddenly the score begins to increase
But here
What's wrong?
Accidentally fell asleep
Inomata woke up after only 30 minutes of sleep
This one is a bit...
11 hours have passed since the start
By the time of the first meal
If you eat enough, you may be attacked by drowsiness
Long-term plan in mind
Both people here choose to eat
12 hours after starting
Kasuga's 5th hypnosis card is
Foot Massage
This is a tough one
Ah, it's so comfortable.
This is bad
Very likely to fall asleep
Really?
Very comfortable
Not bad
Here, the selection is memory
And the Toudaiou team suddenly loses it
Please memorize the following graph in 10 seconds
What color is the circle?
Wow, really?
No idea
Ah, it's yellow!
Great!
Are there acupoints that make you forgetful?
This is the result of a foot massage
Wrong answer to the question at level 1
And
How many balls are there?
Eh...
Can't do it at all
What is the color of the word "white"?
Sleepy...
In the Reflexology and Memory Q&A
Because of the complete mismatch, surprisingly 4 consecutive answers are wrong
But after that
After waking up from sleep
Both stay awake for 10 consecutive hours
Impressive
22 hours after start
Already the 2nd night
Not sleepy at all?
I've been in a daze!
After a certain period of time there is no difference
Eating shabu-shabu!
No sleep for 35 hours in a row for Kasuga
The next hypnotic prop is
It's coming
Shoulder rub
-It's here!
What will happen?
It's not good, right?
What is the card that is shown when the referee orders a player to stop in a sport such as soccer?
Having your shoulders rubbed after a full meal
Can such a double attack be endured?
Red
That's it
After 40 minutes of shoulder rubbing
Oh, no!
No, no, no
You can do it!
Kasuga's first crisis!
So dangerous
Desperately trying to stay awake
Then the sleepless quiz finally passes 24 hours
Finally halfway through
By the way, the current score is 1060 points to 1070 points, almost the same score
I forgot about it
Why?
This matchup
-It's a duel!
I'm sure I lost a lot of points in physics
It's not something I know much about
The scores are now shown in the graph
After that is also the same story
Both spent 9 hours awake
What a long time!
33 hours after start
The Sleepless Quiz ushers in the 2nd early morning
So funny!
Such hard word
Hypnotic prop
-head massage
What is the act of saying the same line repeatedly?
Here Kasuga chooses the comedy category
Rintaro and Kanakin
are which popular
comedy duo.
What is the term
that refers to
young entertainers
who have been
active since the
latter half of
the 2010s.
What is the act
of saying the same
line repeatedly?
Both get 3 questions right in a row
But Toudaiou's Inomata
Sleeps for the 2nd time after 24 hours
Not waking up
What is the name of Daisuke Miyagawa's group?
Looks sleepy
Do you know?
Ah, you know, right?
Should be ok, right?
Chuppachapusu
Kasuga has a great opportunitiy
But answers only 2 out of 8 questions correctly
Should've been a good opportunity
Later
Woke up
After an hour and a half of sleep, Inomata wakes up
Need to earn points here
38 hours after the start
10 hours to go
This guy's always sleeping
Sleeping is normal, right?
-True
Inomata sleeps for the 3rd time
This is normal and he really tried hard
The difference is now 190 points
You can do it!
Can Kasuga reverse the scores at this point?
Kasuga is awesome
The ingredients placed in the center of "Hinomaru Bento" are?
How can he stay awake?
Dried plums
Really impressive
The new French red wine
that was unveiled on the
3rd Thursday of November
is?
Beaujolais Nouveau
Mustard
What are the ingredients
for the "tear roll" sushi?
What cream cheese
is used in Tiramisu?
Mascarpone cheese
He answers 4 questions in the ingredients category correctly
Not bad not bad
And
The Chinese wine with golden mignonette flowers infused into white wine is?
Osmanthus Aged Wine
Awesome
He answers 6 questions in a row correctly
Awesome awesome
During the period when Inomata was still asleep
The next category is...
选择了第一天正确率不错的娱乐圈
Last year's M-1
victor was?
Magical Lovely
Erika Toda
Sakurazaka46
Zu group
Who married actor
Momochi Matsuzaka
last December?
Last October Zelkova
46 changed her
name to?
In Takarazuka Opera,
there is the Hana,
Moon,  Snow, Star
and what group?
然后在这里
4 questions in a row here too
Finally he catches up to only 10 points difference
What traditional art begins with an ape and ends with a fox?
Ravings
Wow
Overtaken?
-Yes
After 40 hours
Kasuga finally overtakes Toudaiou
Kasuga's great!
No sleep at all
Inomata slept for two and a half hours
After sleeping for so long
Here
Oh no!
-Overtaken!
If you fall asleep here
He drooled loads!
So much!
Kasuga who hasn't slept for 53 hours
What happened?
Falls asleep with water in his mouth
He's in such a state
Spilled all over himself
Yeah
Awesome
-Shocking
What came out?
What is the radical of the character "祝"?
Demonstrative
But after answering 1 question correctly
Not bad not bad
Awake again
After sleeping for about 3 hours, Inomata woke up
And
You can do it, Kasuga!
Don't sleep, Kasuga!
What's happening
Pretending?
Kasuga!
Damn
Is he faking?
40 hours and 25 minutes after the start of the Q&A
Ironman Kasuga finally falls asleep
He's sleeping!
Despite intending to pretend to sleep to make the opponent let down his guard...
In doing so, he accidentally fell asleep
And woke up 1 hour later
For the next six and a half hours, the two fight continuously
Still so long!
After 48 hours
So impressive
Finally, the last question
What'll happen?
The law that shifts the country's
industrial structure from primary
to secondary and tertiary industries
is called?
What?
Level 6
Jungle TV Tamori's Law
Suddenly making jokes
It is normal not to know
Paddy Clark's theorem
What the...
Ah…
Even in this state, the answer is correct
Amazing
I have feeling of "it's over" and also reluctance
It's not the feeling of "it's over, what a relief"
Did I overtake him in the last 24 hours?
Because he was asleep, did I overtake during that time?
Maybe in the second half
I think I did a little better
What was the result?
I'm not happy.
What a shame!
I lost by a lot
No... no...
This isn't just lost by a little
So in Toudaiou vs Wednesday Downtown
The winner of this round is Toudaiou
I want revenge
Another duel of patience between me, Inomata and the leader
I see.
-Great!
Although Kasuga worked very hard
Overall, Toudaiou won
Will Fujimon be bungee jumping?
Why?
Why would I?
-For losing
I wasn't the team captain!
I'm not the leader of Wednesday Downtown either
It's tough
I can't bungee jump
I will talk to the staff
No, no, no.
I'll tell them not to make you
You better!
Tell them angrily!
"Don't make Fujimon jump!"
Thanks for watching. Support me and get subs early at patreon.com/zwanster03