WDT Project
Timers: KannibleKlown Translators: GakiNoSuitGuy, SugaDuckGaa
Wednesday Downtown, pleased to see you all.
Hamada Masatoshi
(Downtown)
Kondo Haruna
(Harisenbon)
Bakarhythm
Matsumoto Hitoshi
(Downtown)
Let's get started. Please welcome our first presenter.
Who's there?
It's Kamaitachi!
Pleased to meet you.
We brought back a past theory that was well liked, here it is:
If an angry caller says "I'm heading over right now so you better stay put!",
you can't point them out no matter how ridiculous they look.
Very interesting.
Yamauchi played a big role in this one.
Yes, I did this last time.
I went over to GAG's Fukui
completely soaked and pissed off.
Round 1 OA last year 12/23
He disregarded everything for the entire three minutes.
GAG Fukui Shuntaro
I was dripping all over the floor!
Last time the result was
Yamauchi was the only one who succeeded.
Kamaitachi
Yamauchi Kenji
FUJIWARA
Fujimoto Toshifumi
Daiyan
Tsuda Atsuhiro
Viking
Nishimura Mizuki
Cunning Takeyama
GAG
Fukui Shuntaro
Korochiki
Nadal
Rice
Sekimachi Tomohiro
Yadan
Honma Kid
Soaking wet
Full-face
Barefoot
Injured
Huge backpack
Ignored
Acknowledged
Oh that's right.
Most of them noticed and said something.
They commented.
Right.
By the way, if people saw the episode
firsthand, they might get suspicious
(This theory was filmed before airing to avoid suspicion.)
and guess the theory, so we already
filmed today's theory before the episode aired.
I kind of have something to say, though.
It was super cold that day.
If I'm going to get soaked, the water could've been warm.
So I asked for warm water, and they said "of course".
Then filming started and I poured it on me.
It was super cold water!
I was so upset!
That's upsetting.
That kind of trick isn't necessary!
I would understand if they included a "mini-prank" in the episode.
But no, they just made me dump cold water on myself for nothing!
I was SO upset for a quick second!
Yeah, the staff here
are all psychos.
Yeah they're insane.
After this, we test if the ridiculous appearances will be pointed out once again.
Furthermore,
Special project!
Something where 100% of males but 0% of females know of exists!
I'm seriously going to kill you.
Noooo stop!
Theory: If an angry caller says
"I'm heading over right now so you better stay put!",
you can't point them out no matter how ridiculous they look.
Jichō Kachō Kōmoto Jun'ichi
Jungle Pocket Otake
Lady Dewi
Yukipoyo
Kandori Shinobu
These five are up for the challenge today.
Otake!
Junior comedian
Singer mentee
Junior gal model
Junior wrestler
They each pick their closest juniors
and start the challenge without looking suspicious.
Panther
Ogata Takahiro
Kuki Kaidan
Suzuki Mogura
Kawana Rumi
Hana
Endo Mizuki
That being said, we invite them for a fake meeting.
We begin after leaving them alone.
Why did he go "Shh"?
Ah, thank you for your hard work!
Mogura?
Last time remember you slept over?
Yes.
And remember my Yogibo pillow?
You slept on it and
Yes.
it was drenched in sweat the next morning.
Right.
Then after that it got moldy.
Mold...?
Yeah it grew mold. What are you gonna do?
I can't even use it anymore.
Otake-san...I think the mold is from the room's humidity.
That's irrelevant! It's not humid.
Are you seriously mocking me right now?
No no, I'm not.
Next, Kandori
targets his assistant junior wrestler.
Ah, Kandori.
about getting his meeting times mixed up.
This is pretty scary.
The time for my meeting is different!
So it's not 4 o'clock?
Yeah! What are you doing?!
I'm going to clarify with Kameda-san real quick.
You don't need to go check!
So upset.
That must be so scary.
Scary!
Then, Yukipoyo
targets her junior gal model.
How do gals get
angry at each other?
Like when we went out for some grub. It was last time but
Yes
Say "dinner".
You said "Yukipoyo-san, if you were skinny you'd be pretty cute."
You kept calling me "fried chicken" or "fried chicken bento".
She's probably looking
down on her so much.
I apologize, I was just joking.
Seriously? Are you mocking me?
Meanwhile, Lady Dewi
Scary.
Yeah, scary.
You arrived immediately
Singer mentee
Kawana Rumi
A singer she's mentoring?
And you...
What is she upset about?
took up "associate"-san and "associate"-san's
offer quickly and left.
Who?
Ah, yes yes.
You know, I really think that was very rude of you.
There's one person who's in another realm.
So funny.
She lectures on the singer's poor interaction with an important affiliate.
Lastly, the 5th member Kōmoto.
What the heck did you do now, huh?
That's scary.
So upset!
I'm serious here, you hear?!
He's mad.
Wait a minute, hold on.
That's so scary.
Seriously...
I really don't understand what you mean.
I heard from another junior about it.
What?
Scary.
That's terrifying.
You told people things I told you not to speak of again.
Here it comes.
About what? The Korea thing?
What is it?
I didn't say anything. I only talked about myself.
I never said that you went.
It boomeranged on him.
I only told my side.
This is really not good.
Kōmoto planted this on himself.
Don't laugh, man.
You can't laugh.
Yeah, hold it in.
Wait, or is it about Osaka?
Another one?
That's awful.
Is it Osaka then?
I'd be busted too, so I didn't say anything about that one.
He did something too?!
What did they do?
Don't laugh!
That was the sneak peak of the five challenger's angry calls.
Kōmoto's got
something going on.
Where are you right now?
I'm in the meeting room....uh at TBS waiting for the producer.
She's panicking.
Nervous, yeah.
Waiting here, yes.
I see.
And you being able to work with TBS is thanks to me, right?
Yes of course, of course.
I'm nearby right now.
I'm going to go over to you right now, so wait.
I need to talk to you in person about this.
You better wait for me, bastard.
You wait there, I'm coming right now!
Kōmoto-san I'm really sor-
Okay, well I'm going to go over now.
I don't care that you're in a meeting.
Send me your location right now.
This I really can't let go.
I'm going to head over right now.
It's just a Yogibo right?
Whatever...you..
I'm gonna mess you up. Seriously.
I'm not gonna wait. You wait.
Otake is so weak!
Now that we've sent an angry aura, stand-by is complete.
That said,
first up for the challenge is Kōmoto.
And his transformation is...
Oh, he chooses now.
Covered in mud.
Please go to Ogata-san completely covered in mud.
I'm going to distract him from all this mud
with my words.
So if he looks away even once, I'm going to yell "Look at me!"
He was only supposed to act upset,
but ends up getting actually upset from getting his secret spilled.
Kōmoto now heads over filled with rage and mud.
He goes for the kill.
That's a good
amount of mud!
Yeah it's a
good amount.
Same as last time, the target has to clear 3 minutes without commenting.
Three minutes
is so long!
What will await?
What the heck did you do?!
I'm sorry.
What is wrong with you?
You're so full of crap.
I'm sorry.
Full of anger, Kōmoto was able to keep the target from commenting.
He looks concerned
though.
Everyone knows everything all because of you.
I'm sorry.
I trusted you. What the heck?
And you don't even remember because you were drunk.
My eyes are up here!
Where are you looking? Look here!
I'm sorry.
He can do this.
Your junior
on YouTube and a bunch of other people.
I got together with them
and I treated them out for dinner and drinks
and they told me "Ogata-san told me"
and I doubted them saying "no, you're bluffing" so many times.
I'm sorry.
I can't trust you or talk to you anymore.
Look at me!
I said look over here!
He's laughing a little.
Kōmoto-san...
Stop screwing around, seriously.
Oh no.
Because of the multiple "look over here,"
Ogata can't help but to start laugh.
That's understandable.
I trusted you and Kanada so much.
Kōmoto-san, is everything okay? That...
Stop screwing around seriously!
Kōmoto-san wait a minute please.
Why did you tell them? Tell me why you said it.
Kōmoto-san...
What happened to you?
I said look this way.
Forget about "what happened".
I said look over here!
What is all of this?
What happened?
Jichō Kachō Kōmoto Jun'ichi:  1 min 7 sec
Ogata unusually notices that this is a prank.
Kōmoto at 1 min 7 sec, fails.
Prank reveal.
I told you everything!
See, I knew it
I knew something was up.
See!
There's no way this is normal.
I said look here.
Saying "look here" so many times.
"Look here."
While explaining our theory,
we ask the to clarify the other incident.
I have something I want to ask.
The other thing.
What were you talking about the Osaka thing?
Why did you say that?
Osaka...
I swear...
Please let the Osaka thing go.
What happened?
Right, Kōmoto-san?
But you should make it clear that you didn't cheat on your wife.
I didn't cheat, I promise!
It's kind of... like a brothel.
No that sounds confusing.
If you say "it's like a brothel" then they'll think something else.
It was a brothel.
Next up, Otake's challenge.
Is Otake gonna be ok?
Barefoot.
Following Daiyan Tsuda's barefoot from last time,
a second barefoot challenge.
He has such a
funny face.
"Mogura's sweat made my pillow grow mold"
was Otake's reason of rage, but
how will it turn out?
I mean he looks
funny but...
You're totally being condescending towards me.
No no no.
Wait a minute.
This is not right, don't you think?
This is wrong.
Please, hold on.
This is outright wrong.
The mold on Yogibo.
Wait wait wait.
You used it didn't you?
Uh, no. Let's calm down for a sec.
I'm calm.
He got closer
to his feet.
No, no you're not calm.
I'm calm. I mean what can I do?
But the...
What are you gonna do then?
What are you gonna do about the mold on Yogibo?
Mogura smoothly goes into defensive position.
He's used to
apologizing.
His line of sight is clearly at his feet,
but for some reason doesn't comment.
You were the one that grew the mold.
The mold...
"Grew it."
What are you gonna do if it molds?
But mold forms because of the humidity.
Humidity isn't the only thing, seriously.
He disagrees.
The bacteria is reacting to YOUR sweat.
It doesn't happen from just humidity;
it's a scientific reaction from the bacteria.
But mold...
Explanation on mold.
But mold feasts on moisture and humidity...
Humidity? Why do you keep...
...why do you think my house is humid?
Okay fine, Otake-san.
There is no moisture!
Otake-san, there's moisture everywhere.
Well there's none in my house!
I make a conscious effort to not have moisture!
No room is moisture-free.
I open windows!!
Okay okay.
Okay, I get it.
They continue to have an argument about humidity and mold like idiots.
They're really idiots.
Can he make it?
Even after one minute has passed since starting,
he shows no sign of commenting on being barefoot.
It's going good.
I see.
You're completely looking down on me.
Please, calm down.
Don't say "humidity" anymore.
Then don't say "mold".
You grew the mold!
So stop mentioning "humidity".
Well I'll stop mentioning "humidity" so stop saying "mold".
Otake-san it doesn't make sense.
This prick is so condescending.
A conversation between two idiots.
The argument continues on the mold growing incident.
Oh he made it.
He passes the three minute mark without getting his bare feet noticed.
Prank reveal.
I'm always keeping my windows open so there's no moisture at all.
But moisture exists outside too.
NO THERE ISN'T!
What's this?
This was a tough battle.
This guy, seriously.
He looks down on me so much.
Did you notice something unusual?
Uhm...
Mold will grow...
Are you still on that?
You're still on that!
There's nothing strange going on with him?
With him?
Take a good look.
He never noticed.
Bare....you're barefoot!
No way.
He was barefoot this whole time?
Seriously...this guy man.
He didn't notice.
He's mocking me.
You don't really look down when getting yelled at.
I don't think that's the case.
Next challanger is Yukipoyo.
This is going to be fun.
Party glasses.
This?
This looks super stupid.
Ah okay.
She'll definitely say
something.
Get mad? With this?
She'll be lecturing on her over-friendly attitude.
Complete opposite from the rage.
she flaunts this celebratory appearance.
She'll think she came
from a party.
Yeah true.
She'll say it.
And then...
There's no way.
See she's laughing.
She laughs from the contrast.
Or so we thought...
What are you crying for?
She's crying?!
You think I'd forgive you just because you're crying?
I'm so sorry.
Huh?
Unforeseen real tears.
Maybe she's actually scary?
This is definitely not the first time this has happened.
You took advantage of me staying quiet.
That's so ridiculous, speaking like that to your senior.
Saying stuff like "you're fat" or "if you were skinny, you'd be cute."
Can you say the same thing to other seniors?
I was messing around and I misspoke.
This is unforgivable. You're mocking me aren't you?
You can see the history
between them.
"There's no way" and "mocking" is clearly her but
the sobbing junior seems to be in no position to comment on her seniors' appearance.
That's expected.
Wow, that's crazy.
She's been crying
the whole time.
Yukipoyo, easily cleared.
Prank reveal
I thought she'd
comment right away.
Is she okay?
Why is there a camera here...
She gently explains that she's not upset.
I'm so sorryyyy.
and reassures her. And then...
Did you notice something unusual while getting lectured?
Right now?
Well... this.
So she knew.
But was too upset.
Let's still be close during 2021.
Yes please, I'd like that.
That was so terrifying!
Since there were more instances of non-commenters this round,
next up we used his normal transformation instead of assigning a random one.
And thus,
Alrighty!
You ready?
Yup, ready!
Kandori has transformed into Great Muta with his makeup.
Great Shinobu
Hello? I'm gonna hang up, you bastard!
He enters the ring, completely on a different level than the others.
He's a maniac.
What the heck do you think you're doing?
Why is the time so wrong?
Why did you tell me the wrong information?
I'm always telling you "time is important!"
The junior stays silent despite this ridiculous circumstance.
I'm always saying "time is important".
Hey!
Why can't you comprehend "time is important?"
What about eating?
Eating?
If I said I was gonna eat now,
and couldn't, then my food would get cold!
Am I wrong?
He's not used to lecturing people?
Why does the food get cold?
Why did the time change?
A lot of stuff would get ruined!
The food is gonna get cold, too.
He sticks to that
so much!
Where did his main point of rage go?
That's his only point.
His point shifted, yeah.
For some reason he starts lecturing his junior about food.
I won't be able to eat fresh cooked rice!
Still?
This is not good.
Hey!
I won't be able to eat fresh cooked rice!
I'm very sorry.
It's almost as if she's getting lectured.
about not cooking rice.
He can't eat fresh rice!
Sticking to this point, he clears the 2 minute mark.
False charges.
Prank reveal
Maybe she's relieved.
She was holding
it in I guess.
She's crying.
This is wrong.
Why didn't you think anything after seeing this face?
I thought maybe you rushed over here.
The last challenger is Lady Dewi.
And her transformation is:
Here's Matsumoto's suggestion from the last round...
Like with a parrot on their shoulder.
That being said,
It looks good on her.
"you embarrassed me in front of an affiliate" will be her lecture.
She arrives with rage and a parrot on her shoulder.
What will happen?
I wonder.
Good morning.
Sit down.
Did you even think anything through?
Yes.
Go sit down.
She completely notices the parrot on her shoulder
but remains silent.
Well yeah.
"Associate"-san has the capability of gathering 500 people.
Who is she
talking about?
And that person likes music and is a good singer
and kindly offered to co-star with you.
What do you think is more important?
You should have come with us.
Yes of course.
"Associate"-san came out to see us
She makes her
sit down.
so don't you think you should take care of that first?
You can't just show up only when it suits you.
They give you some connections
and you become affiliated with them.
You were with a very important business customer
so you definitely should have come with us.
Ouch!
You need to be more aware of that.
I'll be more careful.
She didn't laugh.
It bit her.
Though surprised at Lady Dewi getting bit,
she doesn't comment about the parrot.
Ah I see.
And after,
since you're going to be doing business as "Mini Dewi",
you need to
take this seriously and be more careful.
That's not good.
Three minutes go by without any mention.
She couldn't, huh.
As a result, most people will stay quiet, unless they're a comedian.
That's how it is.
So we incorporated more intense transformations this time.
What did you guys think of it?
Kawana-san was pretty interesting to me.
She's gonna be "Mini Dewi"?
As "Mini Dewi"?
She said so, yes.
I think she already debuted as of now.
Really?
Doing impersonations, yes.
What the heck is "Mini Dewi?"
Kind of like "Mini Inoki."
Like Mini Inoki.
Also don't forget that Kōmoto-san went to a brothel in Osaka.
Yeah I almost forgot.
I wonder if you lay hands on them?
What do you mean?
Like since I'm angry,
He quickly uses his fists.
Like getting upset and kicking them would seem more authentic.
Well, not really authentic.
That's would just be you getting upset for real.
Well yeah but...
It wouldn't be a prank anymore.
But then I'd look funny.
That doesn't matter.
Getting upset in a strange costume.
Yeah just plain getting upset in a strange costume.
Let's test out our theory: There are things that 100% of men know but 0% of women know.
Which means this special quiz starts now.
First off the male team.
Presenter
Kawashima Akira
(Kirin) [comedy duo]
Hamada-san, Matsumoto-san, Bakarhythm-san, Kamaitachi Hamaie-kun and Suzuki Fuku-kun.
And then the female team
YOU-san, Ohashi-san, Haruna-chan from Harisenbon, Fuwa-chan, and Inoue Sakura-chan.
In this quiz we test
for things that men will know that women don't.
And the opposite too. Both teams should aim for this situation.
The two teams will take turns asking questions.
And the winner will be the team with most 100% vs. 0% wins.
To ensure we focus on topics advantageous for each gender instead of generation, these are our team member selections.
So Hamada remembers that Fuku is too young to know certain things from previous eras.
That's right.
And dirty jokes and sexual differences are prohibited.
Since it's Reiwa-era now.
That's right.
Otherwise the male team would use those.
It's what men excel at to begin with, right?
That's right.
We will start with the male team. Who will go first?
The important role of starting.
Then I will.
Bakarhythm-san!
To start.
I'm entrusting you.
What is the real name of Kinnikuman?
What is Kinnikuman's real name?
And the question is: "What is Kinnikuman's real name?"
Full name?
Huh?
No no no no no.
Don't ridicule us.
We're not from the Kinnikuman generation!
That's right
But you definitely should've heard it.
What is Kinnikuman's real name?
It's definitely a manga that's popular among men.
It's a very elaborate universe.
It's still being serialized.
Young...
Since it's still being produced even the young would know.
Yes, I think it's a well-balanced question.
Let's see the answers from the female team first.
Reveal them at the same time.
Motomiya Seichi
Like a regular dude.
Ohashi-san wrote: Kinnukuman Taro
Kinnuku Taro
Kin Nikutaro
Sato Hanamichi
What is Kinnikuman's real name?
Bakarhythm, are there any correct answers here?
There are not.
That's how it turned out.
If all male team members get it right they will score a point.
I didn't see my answer in theirs so that means...
Me too.
Let's have a look. Reveal your answers!
Kinniku Nikuo
Matsumoto-san wrote: Nikuman Taro
Bakarhythm-san: Kinniku Suguru
Kinniku Suguru
And Fuku wrote Kinniku Taro
No points rewarded since the answers don't match up.
Answer: Kinniku Suguru
This is really difficult.
Perhaps our generations are too different.
Next up is the female team.
Who will do it?
Can I?
Ah, Ohashi-san
Ohashi-san will pose the question.
When painting our fingers it's called a manicure. What is it called when it's the toes?
What is it called when you paint your toe nails?
I think the girls can answer this.
This is nice.
You all appear so confident.
What a great question.
From the male team: reveal your answers!
Pedicure, pedicure, pedicure, pedicure, foot nail.
Oh no, Fuku!
Hey! Stop messing around!
Answer: Pedicure
Quit it you bastard!
I'm sorry.
I love you, Fuku!
He wrote "foot nail."
It's fine that he didn't know.
Do you want me to end you, lightly?
Please stop!
He will be taken off the job,
What is it called when you paint your toe nails? Answer: Pedicure
forcing him to quit.
Let's see the girls' answers.
Pedicure, pedicure, pedicure, pedicure, peeeeediiiiiicure.
But it should be 0% vs. 100%
Since four got it right you do not get any points.
And on the male team Kamaitachi will ask the next question.
What is the name of the company that uses this logo?
Red on the left and blue.
What is the name of this company?
It's the squares that are colored
What surrounds the white stars, right?
Hamada is looking like...
He's watching his own house burn down
I'm begging you, Hamada!
He's trying to remember.
No no no. You know this.
What does the logo signify?
Eh, what?
This is no good.
It's the logo of a company...
Men should know this one.
And now Hamada...
No way.
Looks like you've warped through time
What company is this?
Hold up
Based on this it's impossible for him to get it.
He asked it because men should be able to answer.
That is indeed the theme of this quiz.
I KNOW THAT!
So it's red there and blue there.
If it had colors you would immediately remember.
That's right.
Please try to imagine that part.
Tanabe's catchphrase?
How come?
A Borujyuku reference.
What company is this?
There it is!
Did it come out, Hamada?
From deep inside!
He's choking.
He started choking.
He choked cause he let out a loud voice.
But if this is wrong I would look so lame
What company is this?
First you need the opposing side to answer entirely wrong.
With that reveal your answers in one go.
Converse and Tamiya
Haru-chan and Fuwa-chan said Tamiya and then... TENGA!
Are you messing around?!
Stop that!
We made the promise, remember?
No dirty jokes!
I said to not include dirty jokes!
Everyone has kept it inside!
But I thought it was something that only men would know.
You went there!?
Let's see the answers from the male team.
What company is this?
Hamada-san Tamiya. Matsumoto-san Tamiya. Tamiya. Tamiya. Tamiya
Answer: Tamiya
We did it!
Ah, but they also got it.
That's right.
Ohashi-san, Haruna-chan and even Fuwa-chan got it
Which means that you get no points.
Why do you know?
I have a younger brother.
Yeah, I have a male sibling.
I have a big brother and he used to make them.
Why did you write that?
I heard it was something that guys would get.
It's a toy that your **** will get.
Talking about men.
Next up from the female team Haruna from Harisenbon will ask the question.
About KinKi Kids
Before they became KinKi Kids what were they called?
What was the group KinKi Kids named before their debut?
It's a well-known name.
I've heard it before.
Looks like the male team is struggling.
And with that...
Are you ready? Reveal your answers all at once.
Hamada-san: Osaka Brothers
Matsumoto-san: Kansai Young Boys
Bakarhythm-san: Kansai Boya
Hamaie-san: Kansai Boys
Fuku-kun: Doumoto Brothers
Now, we're all divided.
The group name KinKi Kids had before their debut is?
Female team. Reveal your answers in one go.
YOU-san: Toukai Bro
Ohashi-san: Kansai Boys
Haruna-chan: Kansai Boya
Fuwa-chan: Doumoto Brothers
Sakura-chan: Buunboobun
That's something they did.
Yeah, the band, right?
It was Kanzai Boya.
Answer: Kanzai Boya
Bakarhythm got it right.
Eh?
And the female team...
only Haruna got it right,
which means that you do not know your teammates.
Which is a larger problem at play.
That's right. This is no good.
It can't be helped if this side doesn't get it.
It's so incomprehensible that only the questionee gets it right so...
We have prepared a penalty.
Nice!
Go ahead.
For whom?
It hurt.
The worst.
This is also part of it?
It hurt.
I don't like it.
Hold up...
Why are you doing these things?
Like a divorce conversation.
How it is in the park at night.
Even...
It's been 30 years since this kind of thing has happened to me.
It hit hard.
That's right.
So...
It really hurt.
So you end up getting an electric shock.
I'm scared.
That's no good when only the questionee knows the answer.
That's right.
I think it's a topic that would be fine if no one knew the answer.
Indeed.
No need to know.
Can you clearly walk us through the rule?
If only the questioner on your team knows the answer,
or if all of the opposing team get the correct answer then there is a penalty.
So if the opposing team all get the answer right we will also be punished?
And it goes both ways?
Yes, both sides. If only you know it.
If it's not common knowledge then that points to a bigger problem.
Well, something like that won't happen very often.
Ohashi, do you have any experience?
I was like...
Why did I quit my job for this?
So please be careful, Haruna.
I was asked to sit here
and put out a quiz
and now the mood has turned sour.
It's not only about me but now my teammates are wrapped up in this.
Collective responsibility.
My apologies.
Please stop those things.
It's fine.
Please think of your team.
Let's get to the male team.
Can I do it?
And the penalty rules also exist for you.
Oh no wait...
Does Hamada have to do it?
But every team member needs to have a question ready.
So everyone has to go at least once?
That's right.
So Hamada HAS to go once.
Of course. Everyone will ask.
Then it can't be helped.
If we could've avoided it I wouldn't want him to pose a question.
Please be good friends. I feel sorry for him.
But he failed the boat race exam.
He failed immediately.
Before you moved to Osaka?
I didn't fail immediately.
I even went to the interview part.
You failed at the interview part?
So the interview didn't go well?
Even though you have the proper knowledge.
What type of person would fail when riding the boat?
And yet he failed the interview part.
The third questioner on the male team will be Hamada.
Fuku plays baseball.
Yes.
So it could be baseball related.
So if we try that they might not know the answer.
Girls are usually weak in that area when it comes to sports.
That's right.
In pro baseball,
Good one.
who and who is ON?
In pro baseball, who and who is ON?
We've got this.
What does it mean? ON?
Do you understand?
They are called ON.
This is hell.
Don't give too much away.
They are totally talking it out.
Were you discussing it?
That's no good.
I didn't.
Please stop it!
That's a penalty!
Stop it!!!
I wasn't.
You again?
I wasn't!
Stop it. I wasn't!
This happened last time too!
I was just confirming what the question was!
That's confusingly similar.
That's ambiguous.
You should refrain from these whisperings.
It's no good.
I was only saying "who and who!"
That's right.
In pro baseball, who and who is ON?
Let's see the answers from the male team first.
(O)u and (N)agashima.
Answer: Ou, Nagashima.
How splendid.
As expected from Hamada.
Nice question.
This is exemplary.
Fuku did well too. You knew it.
Thank you. This made me go: "ah, I know this one".
That's right.
However...
Unless everyone in the female team gets it wrong you won't get points.
Reveal your answers in one go.
Ou and Nagashima...
I hurriedly wrote it.
I wrote it in a hurry.
It's Nagashima, right.
No no no.
But it says Naka.
No, it's Nagashima.
I was hurrying.
You were trying to cover it up.
Answer: Ou, Nagashima.
Ohashi knew this one.
Makes sense. Ohashi would know this one.
Ohashi, you know a lot about baseball.
I refuse to answer this during the quiz.
That makes sense...
We ask because we know it.
Huh. Is that so?
Don't turn this into a court proceeding.
We are asking rhetorically.
Huh?
There's tension between us now.
Please stop.
Let's all have fun.
And on the female team Inoue Sakura will ask the next question.
Around Christmas a seasonal variety box of makeup is sold. What is it called?
If only one of you get it right then they won't score a point.
Bakari, please get this right.
Do you know, Bakarhythm?
This is so tough.
But no one in the male team was able to get it.
If everyone in the female team gets it right they will get a point.
Please reveal your answers.
Cosmetic kit.
Christmas coffret (makeup set).
Haruna: Event gift.
Fuwa: Holiday Assorted Bag.
Sakura: Coffret.
Since Ohashi was able to answer this one...
Answer: Coffret
You barely escaped the penalty.
That's not the point of this game!
You've mixed up the gist of it.
Answer: Coffret
How great. Yaaay.
What the heck are you doing?
Next up on the male team Fuku will pose a question.
We are relying on you, Fuku.
It will be in the same vein as last one.
In the same vein?
I can't hear at all, Fuku!
In the same vein, right?
I'm sorry.
Let's have fun.
In baseball...
How nice.
What other katakana word is there for "double play?"
I see.
What's another katakana word for "double play?"
Double play.
Another way of saying it.
But "double play" is also katakana.
For real.
Another saying.
There was another one.
There definitely was.
The male team please reveal your answers at once.
Hamada: Get two.
Matsumoto: Horseplay.
Bakarhythm: Get two.
Hamaie: Get two.
Fuku: Get two.
And the answer is of course: Get two.
The female team.
They won't get it.
Answer: Get two
Since Ohashi is there it's interesting to see.
Get twoo. Ohashi: Get two
Catch and release.
Yep. Worst answer of them all.
Fuwa: Second game.
Sakura: Second.
Does it count when she mispelled it with an added "u"?
But since Ohashi got it right...
Answer: Get two
In that case you did not earn a point.
Their team is so strong.
Matsumoto.
Isn't...
"catch and release" just horrible?
That's right. The meaning is wrong.
That's right.
You're just messing around.
Punish them.
If that's the case then...
Then what about your "Kinnniku Nikuo?"
No no no.
Or "Mantaro?"
That's right.
It's completely off.
Isn't "catch and release" just terrible?
It's completely wrong.
That's a fishing term.
No no no.
It's not that kind of thing!
If she was horsing around...
She is clearly fishing for laughs.
If I was...
I would've written something funny!
If I was horsing around.
That's a penalty.
Only she got it.
Only me?
That's right.
As is should be.
Makes sense.
That's how it is.
Everyone else was doing it seriously.
Are you okay?
This kind of option was available?
Next on the female team Fuwa will ask a question.
For people that are dieting there is a single superfood...
which looks like this.
Alright. What is it?
What is the name of this superfood?
Please write down your answers.
Is it really dotted like this?
This is indeed how it looks.
I drew it perfectly.
What a mischievous act from her.
Will the female team know this one?
Female team, reveal your answers.
You, please put your answer forward.
I see...
You: Omega 3.
That's right. That's also a thing.
There is also Omega 3.
Ohashi: Chia seeds.
Haruna: Quinoa.
Fuwa: Chia seeds.
Sakura: Chia seeds.
And if everyone on the male team gets it right then you will be punished. Please reveal your answers.
Answer: Chia seeds.
Hamada: Foam.
Matsumoto: Super thingy.
Bakarizm: Açaí
I hear it said often.
In smoothies etc.
Hamaie: Açaí .
Fuku: Chia seeds.
Amazing amazing.
I knew this one.
Amazing, he blocked the team from earning a point!
You knew it?
Answer: Chia seeds.
Yes, I did.
For real?
No one is getting any points.
No points given.
Zero vs. zero.
It's difficult.
This is the result so far.
Neither team has been able to get a 100% vs. 0% win.
How will it turn out in the last round?
What kind of question should I ask?
Probably shouldn't be baseball related.
Yeah, because she's there.
Please do ask a baseball related question.
Don't mind that at all.
Go ahead.
Kamen Rider...
Yes, Kamen Rider.
Can Fuku answer that?
What is the name of the third Kamen Rider in the series?
This is good.
What type of Kamen Rider?
Alright.
What is the name of the third Kamen Rider?
Thank you.
Fuku...
Fuku, you actually love Kamen Rider, right?
I love Kamen Rider to bits.
Hamaie, no way!
No way.
Hamaie, no way.
There it is! No problem.
No but...
All of the names came to me all at once so let me think about it.
He said that it's the 3rd one.
He gave a hint by saying that!
What is the name of the third Kamen Rider?
That's not it.
Does that call for a punishment?
It was the question.
I was just repeating the question. What Matsumoto already said.
I will kill you for real!
Stop it! It's been years since you've threatened my life.
My last one has been valid the entire time.
Oh no no. I hate this.
Scary.
"Valid" as if he has "accommodated" the threat the entire time.
Please stop.
What is the third Kamen Rider?
If everyone gets it right you might get a point.
Yes, we can.
There's no way the opposite team
Yeah.
Male team. Reveal your answers.
V3.
Answer: Kamen Rider V3.
Well done Matsumoto.
Amazing.
With this we can do it.
Matsumoto hit the jackpot.
What a great question.
But if even 1 person gets it right then you won't receive any points.
But if they all answer wrong then you will get a point.
Did you just fart?
That caught me off guard so much!
But uh... he's a good guy. Can't stay mad at him.
Answer: Kamen Rider V3.
The male team all answered correctly.
However...
Reveal your answers at once.
You: V3.
Ohashi: Kamen Rider Taiga.
Rider Rider and Kamen Rider Megaton.
But there was a correct answer.
That's right. She's an old hag so she would know.
She's an elder sister.
As expected from YOU to know it's V3.
This is not good.
No, it was a good question.
It was good.
Hamaie, you recalled it?
I did recall there was no "No. 3".
While there was a No. 1 and No. 2.
Well remembered.
Which means that YOU from the female team will ask the last question.
The kind of accessory that you put here is called a bracelet.
It's a bracelet but...
What is the name of the accessory that you put around your ankle?
Please think about it.
Will you remember?
What was it now...
Of course you have heard it before.
I wonder if Sakura is fine.
If you get a point then the female team has won it all.
It might be this.
Since it's the last both teams reveal your answers simultaneously.
For real?
I hope I will get this one.
I think I got this one right maybe.
Are you ready?
Both teams, reveal your answers.
Hamada, Matsumoto, Bakarizm: Anklet.
Hamaie: Ankle.
Fuku: Thread.
You: Anklet.
Anklet.
Haruna: Leglet.
Misanga.
So old-fashioned.
But you can indeed put it around your ankles.
I'm so sorry.
How old.
Answer: Anklet.
Which means that neither team managed to get 100% vs. 0%.
I see.
If you count the most correct answers it must've been the male team, right?
Why are you trying to win in such a cheap way?
Please tell us.
Let's count the correct answers.
The male team got 30 correct answers.
And the female team got 24.
So the male team won.
Thank you.
Since we finally have arrived at a victory somehow it means that the female team will be punished.
Go ahead.
That one looked like it hurt.
She looks so pissed.
Looks so handsome.
Rokudenashi Blues​ [Boxing themed manga].
Amazing.
What a rough look.