Best shoe-kicker in the world
Here he is, the self-proclaimed best shoe-kicker in the world.
Sakamoto! You're 20, and, a student?
Yes
Which school?
Gu- i-, uhh, - ahh- actually
I'm, a stu- uhh  working part time.
HUH??
sorry, I got a little excited...
what's that?
a mirror
(blue text: he's obsessed with his hair!)
let me see your back...
its flat!
are you wearing something under there?
yeah
it's HEAT-TECH (uniqlo longjohns) huh?
yeah i think so
a young-look
whose longjohns are these???
they're uhh, hand-me-downs
...wh-
my grandpa's...
hey, why don't you do this yourself...!?
why was i doing it the whole time??
when did you realize you were good at shoe kicking?
pretty soon after i got into elementary school...
is when i started... but this is really, like, poor people's culture
poor... po-
well, poor people kinda just make games and play with what they've got, right?
that's kinda, the background that i got into it with
will i... be playing against you?
oh, really?
but... to beat me, just investigating here... would be too easy, huh?
yeah you're right
i want to play against someone better
well, i'd like to introduce...
weclome! this is Morishima Hiroaki! a goal scorer in the soccer world-cup representing Japan!
oh
Cerezo Osaka’s... ambassador
his face doesn't really look like he cares huh??
well, i think he doesn't know who you are!
sorry
are you interested in soccer?
not at all
what are you most interested in then?
something i'm interested in?
BUT! what is it that you were confident in??
i think i will definitely beat you at shoe-kicking
you think?
uhh.. no, uhh.. i will definitely win!
what will you do if you win then?
i'm gonna take off somewhere
where will you go??
he's gonna take off??? he's a part-time worker!!
take off!! hahah
you're takin' off????
well then, if you lose to Morishi...
you can go, but in your long johns.
got it
we'll be using sakamoto's shoes for the entire thing to keep it fair.
what do you kick like anyways? without launching your shoes please..
kinda like this...
and...
that was...!
one more time?
oh one sec uhh...
oh!! your lower back!!!
are you ok??
your lower back?
uhh no uhh...
my thighs kinda...
that's not your thighs!!
these are the thighs!!
what's this part called then?
there??? that's your lower back!
(first up is Ishida)
its going far!!!
measure it!
18m!
exactly 18m!
you ok?
yeah ill be ok
really???
well i used to be a soccer player so i'll show off my clean technique here
let's go!
wow! it went far!
really far! really far!
28.8m
why are you holding your mouth?
alright after you then
huh?
his foot is wet lol
24.5m
what are you doing???
i lost!
hey man, you lost, look at him not me
the man over here, who played in the world cup, what was his name?
umm
mr... world cup.
i guess we gotta help him with everything!
oh, Nippon Ham...!
no!
its a sponsor!
well then, let's get going
ok
good luck!
sakamoto!!
yeah?
what's your dream sakamoto? what's your life goal?
my dream is..